<?xml version="1.0"?>
<menu>
	<game name="007 James Bond (Japan) (Othello Multivision)">
		<description>007 James Bond (Japan) (Othello Multivision)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Tsukuda Original</developer>
		<publisher>Tsukuda Original</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>007 James Bond is a shoot-'em-up game developed and published by Tsukuda Original for the SG-1000. It was
			ported from Parker Brothers's 1983 game of the same name, which was published for various American
			computers/consoles.

			007 James Bond was the last SG-1000 game to be produced by the company.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Bank Panic (Japan)">
		<description>Bank Panic (Japan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>Sanritsu Denki</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>0.9</score>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Bank Panic is an arcade shooting game developed by Sanritsu and manufactured by Sega in 1984. It was
			later ported by Sega to the SG-1000 and Sega Master System. An unlicensed clone called West Bank was
			released for several home computer systems. The same hardware would also be used for the later Sega/Sanritsu
			game Combat Hawk.

			The player takes on the role of a sheriff in 19th century USA, protecting a bank from armed robbers. There
			are twelve doors arranged in a circle, with the player in the centre, which can be viewed three at a time.
			Robbers who appear from the doors are to be shot (after they draw their weapons, for a higher score) and
			customers are to be ignored while they make a deposit. Once deposits have been made from all twelve doors,
			the level is complete.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Black Onyx, The (Japan)">
		<description>Black Onyx, The (Japan)</description>
		<year>1987</year>
		<developer>Bullet Proof Software</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>The Black Onyx is a role-playing game developed by Bullet Proof Software. It was released, among other
			consoles and computers, for the SG-1000 in 1987. It was the last SG-1000 game to be released in card form,
			and the last to be published by Sega, but it is currently unknown as to whether it was the last SG-1000
			game. PC-8801 and MSX versions had been released in 1984 and 1985, respectively, meaning this version is
			unusually late. The game was followed by The Black Onyx II: Search For The Fire Crystal, which saw its
			original MSX release in 1984.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Bomb Jack (Japan, Australia)">
		<description>Bomb Jack (Japan, Australia)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>Tehkan Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Bomb Jack is an arcade game developed by Tehkan which was later ported to the SG-1000 by Sega in 1985.
			The aim of the game is to collect all the bombs in the playfield while avoiding monsters. Extra points are
			awarded for collecting the bombs in a specific order.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Borderline (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)">
		<description>Borderline (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Borderline is a VIC Dual arcade game developed in 1980 by Sega. It is a shoot-'em-up in which the player
			controls a red jeep who must destroy the enemy refineries.

			Borderline was ported to the SG-1000 in 1983, and has also been released as part of the Sega Ages 2500
			series in Japan. The second gameplay section was also recycled for the Atari 2600 release of Thunderground,
			though instead of driving a jeep the player controls a tank.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Cabbage Patch Kids (Taiwan)">
		<description>Cabbage Patch Kids (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Aaronix</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>It's exercise time! Anna Lee, one of the Cabbage Patch Kids, is warming up for a day of athletic
			adventures in the park--and she's taking you along! So stretch your muscles and get ready for a workout.
			This adventure is no picnic! As you stroll through the park, you'll encounter obstacles they never told you
			about in the Cabbage Patch. You'll leap onto floating lily pads, jump over cabbages and bouncing balls, and
			hop over puddles so deep they could float a ship. And that's the easy part! By the time you get back to the
			Park entrance, you'll know just what kind of physical shape you're really in. Are you ready for the workout?
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Castle, The (Japan)">
		<description>Castle, The (Japan)</description>
		<year>1986</year>
		<developer>ASCII Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>The Castle is video game developed by ASCII and released for the SG-1000 in 1986. It is a port of an MSX
			game of the same name, and is largely identical due to the similar hardware between the two machines. Due to
			the decline of the SG-1000 and emergence of the Sega Master System, the game was not released in Europe or
			Australia like many other SG-1000 games. The game has a fairly standard plot of rescuing a princess from a
			castle, though the game itself was considered very large for the time. It also contains a map system similar
			to that of later Metroid and Castlevania games.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Chack'n Pop (Japan)">
		<description>Chack'n Pop (Japan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Chack'n Pop is an arcade game developed by Taito which was subsequently ported to the SG-1000 in 1985. It
			follows a yellow creature named Chack'n who must traverse across several mazes blowing up monsters.

			The SG-1000 version of the game includes extra cutscenes and a training level not seen in the arcade
			version.

			Though Chack'n Pop was not a particularly successful game for Taito, it would go on to inspire the success
			of Bubble Bobble, which shares many of the same characters and devotes a stage to Chack'n Pop. Chack'n has
			also cameoed in numerous Taito games since, including Bubble Bobble, Fairyland Story, Parasol Stars, Puzzle
			Bobble (and sequels), Bubble Symphony, Bubble Memories and Arkanoid DS.

			Curiously this SG-1000 version uses the katakana script for writing Chack'n Pop as opposed to the hiragana
			script used in almost every other version.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Challenge Derby (Japan) (Rev 1) (Othello Multivision)">
		<description>Challenge Derby (Japan) (Rev 1) (Othello Multivision)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Tsukuda Original</developer>
		<publisher>Tsukuda Original</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Challenge Derby is a horse racing game for the SG-1000.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Champion Baseball (Japan, Australia, New Zealand)">
		<description>Champion Baseball (Japan, Australia, New Zealand)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Champion Baseball is an arcade baseball game developed by ADK. Sega distributed the game worldwide, and
			produced an SG-1000 port in 1983. Alpha Denshi also made a sequel, only released in arcades.

			Champion Baseball is said to have been a hugely successful arcade game in Japan, even receiving its own
			dedicated parlours in the country (of the sort first seen with Space Invaders in 1978).</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Champion Billiards (Japan)">
		<description>Champion Billiards (Japan)</description>
		<year>1986</year>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Champion Billiards is a simplistic billiards game built for the SG-1000. It is the first game in
			Compile's "Lunar Pool" series. It was not released outside of Japan.

			Unlike the other Champion Sports games, Champion Billiards is not an accurate representation of it's sport.
			Instead, Champion Billiards is a level-based physics game. The goal of each level is to use the red cue ball
			to sink the other balls.

			Trivia: Breaking open the yellow ball can release a yellow Flicky.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Champion Boxing (Japan) (Rev 1)">
		<description>Champion Boxing (Japan) (Rev 1)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Champion Boxing is a simplistic boxing game built for the SG-1000. It was later re-released in arcades
			for SG-1000-based arcade hardware. An MSX version was released in 1985, published by Pony Canyon.

			There are five difficulty levels, and the aim is to knock out the opponent. 1 attacks, 2 selects an attack.
			Interestingly, if a player wins Pengo will make a cameo.

			Champion Boxing is also noteworthy for being the first game coded by Yu Suzuki in his first year at Sega.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Champion Golf (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)">
		<description>Champion Golf (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Logitec</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>If it's raining on Sunday ... it's CHAMPION GOLF day. You can enjoy hitting the ball with the appropriate
			club to match the shot, walking around the course with the considerate caddie over its extensive fairways,
			roughs, greens, ponds and bunker areas. Getting a "Birdie", "Eagle" or an amazing "Hole in One", or the even
			more miraculous "Albatross" will make you feel like you are on top of the world.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Champion Ice Hockey (Japan)">
		<description>Champion Ice Hockey (Japan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Champion Ice Hockey is a simplistic ice hockey game built for the SG-1000.

			You play as the Red team vs. the Blue team. One button shoots, while the other button passes. Up and down
			control not only your goalie, but also the direction of the scoring shot.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Champion Kendou (Japan)">
		<description>Champion Kendou (Japan)</description>
		<year>1986</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Champion Kendou is a simplistic kendou game built for the SG-1000 and MSX. It was only released in Japan.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Champion Pro Wrestling (Japan)">
		<description>Champion Pro Wrestling (Japan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>To play for a rank you 'll have to fight three matches. Winning two out of three matches promotes you t
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Champion Soccer (Japan, Europe)">
		<description>Champion Soccer (Japan, Europe)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Champion Soccer is a simplistic football game built for the SG-1000. Pony Canyon later brought it to the
			MSX.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Champion Tennis (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)">
		<description>Champion Tennis (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Champion Tennis is a simplistic tennis game built for the SG-1000.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Championship Lode Runner (Japan, Australia)">
		<description>Championship Lode Runner (Japan, Australia)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>This package contained 50 of the most challenging levels ever designed, and was intended for expert
			players only. It did not include the level editor, you had to play through the levels in</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Choplifter (Japan, Australia)">
		<description>Choplifter (Japan, Australia)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Choplifter is a 1982 Apple II game developed by Dan Gorlin and published by Broderbund. In the game you
			pilot a helicopter and must rescue people from prisoner of war camps. Sega were responsible for an arcade
			remake on both the Sega System 1 and Sega System 2 hardware in 1985. This version was ported to a variety of
			platforms, including the SG-1000 in 1985 and the Sega Master System in 1986.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Circus Charlie (Taiwan)">
		<description>Circus Charlie (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Aaronix</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Circus Charlie is originally an arcade game. The MSX port that was brought to the SG-1000 in Taiwan and
			South Korea.
			You are Charlie, a member of a circus troupe. Your job is to please the crowd by performing five
			death-defying stunts:
			Stunt #1: You and the lion must jump through several rings of fire. Remember to avoid the jugs that emit
			fire. You must do this for 100 meters.
			Stunt #2: Walk the tightrope for 70 meters, avoiding the monkeys that get in your way. Jump the cyan monkeys
			for 500 points.
			Stunt #3: Roll on a ball for 80 meters, jumping from ball to ball. You can move balls backwards if the
			target is too close to make a successful jump. Avoid contact with the ground.
			Stunt #4: Ride a horse for 200 meters, bouncing on trampolines along the way. Be careful not to miss the
			jump or go over the tops of trampolines. You can speed up or slow down the horse.
			Stunt #5: Finally, trapeze from swing to swing for 50 meters. If you miss, make sure that you land on the
			platforms below so you bounce back on a swing.
			Once you have completed all five stunts, you have to do them again and hopefully, more points will be
			awarded.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Complete Arcade Pack Collection, The (New Zealand) (SF-7000)">
		<description>Complete Arcade Pack Collection, The (New Zealand) (SF-7000)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Congo Bongo (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand) (Rev 1)">
		<description>Congo Bongo (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand) (Rev 1)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Congo Bongo , originally known as Tip Top, is a 1983 arcade platformer game developed by Sega. It is
			often considered an isometric equivalent to Nintendo's Donkey Kong, as it stars a protagonist chasing after
			a large ape (in this game, called "Bongo"). However, unlike Donkey Kong, the game is set in a jungle, the
			graphics are more detailed and there are more enemies and traps.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="C_So! (Japan)">
		<description>C_So! (Japan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>C_So! (C-SO!) is a 1985 SG-1000 game developed by Compile and published by Sega. It is a port of an MSX
			game from the same year, which was published by Pony Canyon.



			The game has the player collect various items and defeat monsters by using see-saws. In order to progress,
			all items must be collected and all monsters must be destroyed. There is also an edit mode, allowing the
			player to create their own levels.



			The game was only released in Japan.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Doki Doki Penguin Land (Japan)">
		<description>Doki Doki Penguin Land (Japan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Doki Doki Penguin Land is a 1985 game initially developed by Sega for the SG-1000. It is a platform-based
			puzzle game, where a penguin must guide an egg down the screen making sure not to break it.

			The basic aim of Doki Doki Penguin Land is to guide an egg from the top of the screen to the bottom. To do
			so means digging downwards, making sure it does not smash in the process. As a puzzle-platformer, everything
			is affected by gravity, and if the egg falls from a great height, it will smash. Success is achieved by
			making your way down the playfield carefully.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Dragon Wang (Japan) (Rev 1)">
		<description>Dragon Wang (Japan) (Rev 1)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>The protagonist is Wang (inspired by Jackie Chan and/or his character Thomas), hence the unfortunate
			title Dragon Wang. Wang is Chinese for King.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Drol (Japan, Australia)">
		<description>Drol (Japan, Australia)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Drol is an SG-1000 game released in 1985. Originally developed by Broderbund for various home computers
			in the west, it was brought to the SG-1000 by Sega and released exclusively in Japan. You play as a robot
			who must rescue his children.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Elevator Action (Japan)">
		<description>Elevator Action (Japan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>The player assumes the role of a spy infiltrating a 30-story building filled with elevators. The player
			is pursued by enemy agents who appear from behind closed doors. These agents must be dealt with via force or
			evasion. Successful completion of a level involves collecting all the secret documents and traversing the
			building from top to bottom. In the lower floors of the building, the elevator systems can be complex enough
			that puzzle-solving skills are needed. The controls consist of a 4-way joystick and two buttons, one to
			shoot and the other for jumping and kicking.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Exerion (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)">
		<description>Exerion (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>The FIGHTER EX rushed in and out attacking the monstrous enemy groups in the 6 mysterious, diferent
			DIMENSIONAL worlds.
			The enemy is constantly in pursuit of the FIGTHER EX.
			The figther's missile attacking the enemy come down like showers of hail. Be on the alert !!
			The "Dual Beam" allows you to shoot downn the enemy, and the "Single Beam", to speedily and continuously
			attack it.
			See how successful you are in battling the enemy through the 6 dangerous worlds !</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Flicky (Japan) (Rev 1)">
		<description>Flicky (Japan) (Rev 1)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Little baby birds, PIOPIOes, are seen basking on the bright sunny terrace. It's now time for the little
			PIOPIOes to take their midafternoon snack. FLICKY, your mother, is coming to take all of you back home.
			Let's return skipping merrily hand in hand with mama FLICKY. Oh, oh, we've got a big problem!! The
			ill-natured stray cat (NYANNYAN) is coming. Escape by jumping over him and throwing hammers and mugs in an
			effort to hit and destroy the big bad cat. FLICKY, you'll feel really relieved when you have successfully
			taken all of your baby PIOPIOes back home, won't you?</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Girl's Garden (Japan, Australia)">
		<description>Girl's Garden (Japan, Australia)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>In order to prevent her boyfriend Minto from going to another little girl named Cocco, Papri must collect
			ten different flowers and return them to her boyfriend's house. Flowers must be caught in full bloom so that
			the number of flowers in her possession will increase; catching flowers too early will consider the flowers
			to be wasted and flowers caught too late will be wilted. Wilted flowers will ruin the bouquet, causing the
			player to lose half of the flowers.

			Bears have a taste for honey and cause the player to lose one of two hearts if one of them attacks the
			player. However, the honey can be dropped in order to render the bear temporarily harmless to the player.
			Bees appear as the player's ally, giving her bonus items occasionally and extra honey if the player catches
			it on a flower.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Golgo 13 (Japan)">
		<description>Golgo 13 (Japan)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Golgo 13 is a shoot-'em-up game for the SG-1000 based on the Japanese manga of the same name.

			The game has you shoot at windows of a passing train. Hitting objects that get in the way will make the
			bullet rebound and potentially kill you.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="GP World (Japan) (Rev 1)">
		<description>GP World (Japan) (Rev 1)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>GP World for the SG-1000 and MSX, is a loose conversion of the 1984 LaserDisc-based arcade game, GP
			World. It was released in 1985 exclusively in Japan.

			Gameplay in this "8-bit" version of GP World is similar in concept to the arcade GP World but given the
			wildly differing hardware, different in execution. Most notably all graphics in the game are generated in
			real-time by the SG-1000 rather than streamed from a LaserDisc, which in turn leads to more predictable car
			physics. The concept of racing in four different types of GP is scrapped, replaced instead with a GP that
			spans the world and three selectable difficulties.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Gulkave (Japan)">
		<description>Gulkave (Japan)</description>
		<year>1986</year>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Gulkave is an SG-1000 shoot 'em up game developed by Compile and published by Sega in 1986. It is a
			horizontal shooter, in which the player controls a spaceship that must destroy the 8 fortresses of the
			Gulbas Empire and several various enemies. Despite the limitations of the console, there are 30 "acts", and
			each "act" has a different background and there are numerous powerups available, setting it apart from most
			other SG-1000 shooters at the time.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Guzzler (Japan) (Othello Multivision)">
		<description>Guzzler (Japan) (Othello Multivision)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Tsukuda Original</developer>
		<publisher>Tsukuda Original</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Guzzler is an arcade game developed by Tehkan. It was ported to the SG-1000 by Tsukuda Original and given
			Othello Multivision branding. To this day the SG-1000 version stands as the only home port of Guzzler.

			You play as a character who needs to absorb water to put out fires dotted around a maze. The fires also
			spawn fire-based enemies which can be defeated in a similar fashion. You can only store up to three shots at
			one time.

			Compared to other SG-1000 games, Guzzler shows some very poor production values. It thrusts you into
			gameplay without warning (which can result in cheap deaths) and it has a broken pause feature, which
			although appears to work, will unpause the game after a few seconds. There are only three maps and far fewer
			enemies than in the arcade version and it is also a much louder game, as the SG-1000 omits a high pitched
			squeak every time you make a step.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="H.E.R.O. (Japan)">
		<description>H.E.R.O. (Japan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>H.E.R.O. is an action game originally developed and published by Activision. Sega brought it to the
			SG-1000 in Japan.

			The objective of the game is to rescue trapped miners in a volcano. 1 drops a stick of dynamite to blow up
			barriers and kill enemies. 2 shoots a laser-like thing, which you can use to kill enemies. At the bottom of
			the screen, there is a Power meter showing you how much energy you have left; energy goes down as time goes
			on. Simply touch a miner to rescue him and move on to the next level.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Hang-On II (Japan, Australia)">
		<description>Hang-On II (Japan, Australia)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Hang-On II is an SG-1000 sequel to the critically acclaimed Hang-On.

			Despite the name, the game is meant as a direct sequel to the Mark III version of Hang-On, and is virtually
			identical to that game. The only difference is downgraded graphics and the addition of music from the arcade
			version. Meanwhile, Super Hang-On is the direct sequel to the arcade game.

			It is compatible with the BH-400 bike handle controller, and would be the only SG-1000 game designed for it
			(though the peripheral is compatible with the Sega Master System and Sega Mega Drive).</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Home Mahjong (Japan) (Rev 1)">
		<description>Home Mahjong (Japan) (Rev 1)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Board Games</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Home Mahjong is a mahjong game for the SG-1000.

			The game was sold with a plastic screen that sticks to the TV during a 2 player game to hide the other
			players tiles from view.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Hustle Chumy (Japan)">
		<description>Hustle Chumy (Japan)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Hustle Chumy is an SG-1000 and MSX game developed by Compile and released in 1984.

			In Hustle Chumy players control a mouse named Chumy who needs to collect apples (and other food) in a sewer,
			avoiding other critters as he goes. As Chumy eats more food, his speed decreases, but his fireballs are
			given a longer range. Levels have varying layouts.

			There are several types of enemies in the game, most of which can be defeated with fireballs.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Hyper Sports (Japan)">
		<description>Hyper Sports (Japan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Hyper Sports is a sports game developed by Konami and released for the SG-1000 in 1985 (following a 1984
			MSX launch). The game has the player compete through a number of olympic events.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Hyper Sports 2 (Taiwan)">
		<description>Hyper Sports 2 (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Aaronix</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Kamikaze (France) (SF-7000)">
		<description>Kamikaze (France) (SF-7000)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Loriciels</developer>
		<publisher>Loriciels</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Kamikaze é um jogo de shoot-'em-up para o SC-3000 e foi lançado exclusivamente na França.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="King's Valley (Taiwan)">
		<description>King's Valley (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Aaronix</developer>
		<publisher>DahJee</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>King's Valley for the SG-1000 released in Taiwan by Aaronix. This game requires a special adapter
			released by DahJee that extend the SG-1000 memory to 8 KB (read more about the DahJee adapter for SG-1000).
			Else it would work on a normal Asian Master System. King's Valley is pretty much in the vein of
			pre-scrolling item collecting arcade game, Think Lode Runner meet Pac-Man in Egyptian tomb adventure theme.
			A very game by Konami.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Knightmare (Taiwan)">
		<description>Knightmare (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>1987</year>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Jumbo Team</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Knightmare is an MSX vertical shoot-'em-up by Konami. It was brought without a license to the SG-1000 in
			Taiwan. In Knightmare, the player takes control of a brave knight named Popolon, who has to rescue his
			sweetheart Aphrodite from the clutches of the evil Hudnos. The game is essentially a top-down shooter.
			Popolon can shoot arrows at his enemies, and at the end of level face bosses, such as witches, etc. Shooting
			monsters, avoiding obstacles, passing the bridges and collecting upgrades for his weapon leads him to glory.
			Digitized music and sound add more to the arcade-like gameplay. This game may also be about two brave
			knights - you and your friend, who does the same for the victory on one screen.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Legend of Kage, The (Taiwan)">
		<description>Legend of Kage, The (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>1986</year>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>DahJee</publisher>
		<score>0.45</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>The player takes the role of a young Iga ninja named Kage ("Shadow"), on a mission to rescue Princess
			Kiri (hime) - the Shogun's daughter - from the villainous warlord Yoshi (ro Kuyigusa) and fellow evil
			samurai Yuki (nosuke Riko). Kage must fight his way through a forest, along a secret passageway, up a
			fortress wall, and through a castle... rescuing her twice (three times in the FC/NES version) in order to
			win the game. Each time the princess is rescued, the seasons change from summer to fall to winter and back
			to summer.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Lode Runner (Japan, Europe, Australia)">
		<description>Lode Runner (Japan, Europe, Australia)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>In this game, the player is required to repeatedly "think" and "take action" to go through and clear the
			maze scenes by solving their mysterious riddles while averting the enemy's guards who are relentlessly in
			pursuit of him. After collecting all of the gold chests, you must come up with fresh new ideas in order to
			successfully challenge the next level scene. Although your experience gained from the previous play action
			will help you overcome some of the future maze scenes, you still have to constantly be on the alert. You can
			also enjoy creating your own games by using the keyboard. This is an intriguing game which requires
			intellectual depth to skillfully maneuver the unknown maze structures that consecutively develop one after
			another.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Magical Kid Wiz (Taiwan)">
		<description>Magical Kid Wiz (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>1986</year>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Aaronix</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Magical Kid Wiz for the SG-1000 released in Taiwan on a beautiful green cartridge. Developed in 1986 by
			Sony for the MSX, this is among the MSX games that Aaronix ported to the SG-1000 for the Taiwanese market.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Magical Tree (Taiwan)">
		<description>Magical Tree (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Aaronix</publisher>
		<score>0.55</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Magical Tree is a vertically scrolling platform game developed by Konami for the MSX home computer, and
			published in 1984. The player character is an 'Indian brave' stereotype who wears a tanned vest and
			trousers, and a headband with a feather. The player ascends a magical tree by hopping from branch to branch
			and climbing vines and ladders—while also dodging larvae, owls, and lightning bolts. The player can jump and
			dangle from branches. He earns points by gathering apples, arrows, daggers, and coronets.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Mahjong (Japan) (Rev 1)">
		<description>Mahjong (Japan) (Rev 1)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Board Games</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>This is the first mahjong game released for the SG-1000, developed and published by Sega in 1983. Unlike
			later mahjong games released for the system, this game is for one player only.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Monaco GP (Japan, Europe) (Rev 2)">
		<description>Monaco GP (Japan, Europe) (Rev 2)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>A red formula car travelling at high speed through the streets, speeding up, jumping, maneuvering to the
			right and left to avoid the cars obstructing the way and reckless cars coming close to your machine,
			........ Be on the lookout for an ambulance suddenly passing by ......... And keep an eye out for the
			signposts!! Thrill-packed challenges such as the slip zones, dangerous construction sites as well as sharp
			curves and narrow bay bridges also appear. When in the tunnel, the headlights of your car are the only thing
			you can rely upon. After improving your skill by going through the beginner's level 1, you can move on to
			the more difficult high levels 2 and 3.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="N-Sub (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand, Taiwan)">
		<description>N-Sub (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand, Taiwan)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>A big battle develops on a cobalt blue sea. Fire a torpedo when you find the enemy's ships. Avoid the
			destroyer's attack by using your missiles, torpedoes and depth bombs. Counterattack and sink the enemy's
			ships. The enemy attack becomes more intense with each new round!</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Ninja Princess (Japan, Australia)">
		<description>Ninja Princess (Japan, Australia)</description>
		<year>1986</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Ninja Princess known as Sega Ninja in the west, is a Sega System 1 arcade game by Sega. It is a top-down
			shooter/action game, in which you play as a princess disguised as a ninja who is attempting to stop the evil
			tyrant Gyokuro.

			The game was ported to the SG-1000 in 1986 exclusively for Japan, with an MSX port following shortly
			afterwards. It was also brought to the Sega Master System as The Ninja, however The Ninja makes several
			adjustments to the story and characters, as well as updating the gameplay.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Okamoto Ayako no Match Play Golf (Japan) (Rev 1) (Othello Multivision)">
		<description>Okamoto Ayako no Match Play Golf (Japan) (Rev 1) (Othello Multivision)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Tsukuda Original</developer>
		<publisher>Tsukuda Original</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Okamoto Ayako no Match Play Golf is a golf game for the Othello Multivision, released by Tsukuda
			Original. It is also compatible with the Sega SG-1000.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Orguss (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand, Taiwan)">
		<description>Orguss (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand, Taiwan)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Orguss is a shoot-'em-up game developed and published by Sega for the SG-1000. In the game, the player
			takes control of a robot which can transform into a starship. It is based on the science fiction anime
			series Super Dimension Century Orguss.

			The player can swap between robot and starship modes freely, though both come with their own set advantages
			and disadvantages. In robot mode, you are able to destroy ground targets and have greater freedom across the
			screen at the expense of being a bigger target for enemies. You can shoot rapidfire, but move slower. In
			starship mode you cannot destroy ground targets, but are less likely to be destroyed thanks to the smaller
			surface area of the ship.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Othello (Japan)">
		<description>Othello (Japan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>Tsukuda Original</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Board Games</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Othello is an SG-1000 video game based on the board game Othello.

			Two versions of Othello exist for the SG-1000. The first version, released in 1983, was built into the
			Othello Multivision (which is where the system gets its name from). Sega would later re-release this game in
			cartridge form in 1985, offering significant graphical and AI improvements over Tsukuda Original's version.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pacar (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)">
		<description>Pacar (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>PACAR, a mischievous car, runs through the 3D routes freely advancing and reversing at fast and slow
			speeds. Try to delete all the dots on the screen while avoiding the 2 kinds of enemy cars. When you pass
			through the special dots, PACAR becomes more and more invincible as it increases its power and will be free
			from damage even when it crashes into the enemy car. Keep up the torrid pace and destroy as many of the
			enemy cars as possible!</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pachinko (Japan)">
		<description>Pachinko (Japan)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Pachinko is an SG-1000 game developed and published by Sega in 1983. It is, as the name suggests, a video
			game version of Pachinko, a popular game in Japan. The game did not see an international release.

			Pachinko is an extremely rare game for the SG-1000. Soon after release, it was recalled from sale due to a
			game-breaking bug (need to verify) and very few copies remain in the hands of collectors. This is probably
			the very first instance of a recall in Sega's history (?).</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pachinko II (Japan)">
		<description>Pachinko II (Japan)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Pachinko II is the bug fixed version of Pachinko and a "sequel", which was released for the SG-1000 in
			1984.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Ping Pong (Taiwan)">
		<description>Ping Pong (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pippols (Taiwan)">
		<description>Pippols (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Jumbo Team</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Pippols is an action game by Konami. The MSX version of the game was brought to the SG-1000 in Taiwan. It
			requires the 8kB RAM Adapter to run.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pitfall II - The Lost Caverns (Japan) (Rev 1)">
		<description>Pitfall II - The Lost Caverns (Japan) (Rev 1)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Pitfall II: The Lost Caverns is the sequel to Pitfall and was released for a variety of systems during
			the mid-1980s including the SG-1000 in 1985. Gameplay is similar to the original game, but the levels are
			more maze-like.

			Sega's version of Pitfall II was tweaked significantly from its western counterparts released for the Atari
			2600, ColecoVision etc. The gameplay is largely the same, but there are many additions. These include a
			Lives system, mine-carts, balloons, and a final Demon boss. The SG-1000 version is directly inspired by the
			arcade game, and though cannot match the same level of graphical quality, it is arguably the nicest looking
			home port of the game.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pop Flamer (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)">
		<description>Pop Flamer (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Jaleco</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>"POP FLAMER" is a mouse which operates a flamethrower.
			You as a player attempt to break balloons and supply fuel for the flamethrower while eliminating the 3 kinds
			of MONSTERS and the obstacle FROG which is obstructing the routes. However, be carefuk of the tranquizing
			beam from the "HARADON". When you are exposed to this beam, you will not be able to move temporality! When
			the POP FLAMER takes a "power-up drink", it ohanges into a "SUPER MOUSE" and you can score high points by
			swallowing the nearby MONSTERS in one gulp!!</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Poseidon Wars + Space Panic + Rambo (France) (SF-7000)">
		<description>Poseidon Wars + Space Panic + Rambo (France) (SF-7000)</description>
		<year>1989</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>0.45</score>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>In Poseidon Wars 3-D, you have just entered the navy as a cadet and you must make your way up to Admiral.
			To do this, you must go out at sea with a submarine and destroy several enemy targets. Once you have
			defeated each enemy target, the mission is completed, and, upon completing some of them, your rank
			increases. Before defeating each target, however, you also need to destroy enemy jets, choppers, and
			submarines who will launch missiles or rockets at you. If you are hit by any of these, damage is inflicted
			to the submarine, but you can shoot down any of the missiles or rockets. You will need to keep an eye on the
			built-in radar and sonar to find out where enemies will hit next. Your fuel is limited, and can be increased
			by destroying certain enemies. The game ends when your submarine is destroyed or you run out of fuel.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Q-bert (Japan) (Othello Multivision)">
		<description>Q-bert (Japan) (Othello Multivision)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Tsukuda Original</developer>
		<publisher>Tsukuda Original</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Q*bert is an arcade game by Gottlieb. It was ported to the SG-1000 by Tsukuda Original, who marketed it
			for their Othello Multivision console.

			The objective of the game is to turn all the cubes on screen to a desired colour by moving Q*bert on top of
			them. Q*bert can only move in diagonals, and the player needs to be careful not to either send Q*bert off
			the edge or have him collide with enemies/obstacles. Occasionally cylindrical platforms appear on the edge
			of the screen, which when jumped on, will take Q*bert to the top.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Rally-X (Taiwan) (English Logo)">
		<description>Rally-X (Taiwan) (English Logo)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>DahJee</publisher>
		<score>0.55</score>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Rally-X is a 1980 arcade game by Namco which was brought to the MSX in 1984. It was subsequently ported
			to the SG-1000 in Taiwan.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Road Fighter (Taiwan) (English Logo)">
		<description>Road Fighter (Taiwan) (English Logo)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Jumbo Team</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Road Fighter est un jeu de course développé par Konami. Jumbo a porté la version MSX du jeu sur le
			SG-1000 à Taiwan sous le nom de Huojiàn che. On ne sait pas s'ils avaient une licence pour cela. Plus tard,
			il est sorti en Corée du Sud en tant que cartouche pour la Sega Master System sous le nom de Paiteo Lodeu.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Rock n' Bolt (Japan)">
		<description>Rock n' Bolt (Japan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Before you awaits the construction world's most complicated, confused mess of mind-boggling blueprints,
			bolts, beams and girders.
			You and you alone will have to figure it all out and put it all together. And you don't have all day.
			It's a dazzling, dizzying, incredibly exciting high-rise challenge. All 100 floors of it.
			You'll spin, leap and dance your way from beam to beam, puzzle to puzzle. Earn bonus wages and hire extra
			workers.
			So, grab your hat and strap on your boots. You're about to discover how hot music and high energy can help
			fill a very, very tall order.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Safari Hunting (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)">
		<description>Safari Hunting (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Go deep into the jungle and hunt fierce animals. Your weapon is a mighty tranquilizer gun. Capture the
			sleeping snakes, gorillas, lions and elephants by putting them in a cage. Capture as many animals as
			possible, while considering the effective time of the tranquilizer and the available quantity of fuel.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Safari Race (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)">
		<description>Safari Race (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>On the vast savanna plain, the SAFARI RACE has just gotten underway. Keep running at full speed, passing
			other cars while avoiding various wild animals that cross the road. Drive fast, ever onward, taking into
			consideration the limited time, fuel consumption and dangerous sharp curves. Pass through the checkpoints.
			Run your car at full throttle towards the goal with the engine operating at its maximum capacity.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="San-nin Mahjong (Japan) (Othello Multivision)">
		<description>San-nin Mahjong (Japan) (Othello Multivision)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Tsukuda Original</developer>
		<publisher>Tsukuda Original</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Board Games</genre>
		<players>1-3</players>
		<story>Sannin Mahjong is a mahjong game for the SG-1000. It is sometimes also known as 3-nin Mahjong, meaning
			three player mahjong. This number of players is not possible in either of Sega's own versions of the game,
			Mahjong and Home Mahjong.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Sega Flipper ~ Video Flipper (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)">
		<description>Sega Flipper ~ Video Flipper (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Sega-Galaga (Japan, Australia)">
		<description>Sega-Galaga (Japan, Australia)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Take control of a fighter space craft and shoot down the invading aliens. Watch out for the swooping
			motherships, which will try to steal your fighter. Rescue captured fighters to double your firepower. Earn
			Perfect Bonuses as you battle your way through wave after wave in different challenging stages.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Serizawa Hachidan no Tsumeshougi (Japan)">
		<description>Serizawa Hachidan no Tsumeshougi (Japan)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Serizawa Hachidan no Tsumeshogi is a 1982 arcade game by Sega. It was subsequently ported to the SG-1000.

			The arcade version is extremely rare and poorly documented.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Shinnyushain Tooru-kun (Japan)">
		<description>Shinnyushain Tooru-kun (Japan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Shinnyuushain Tooru-Kun is a game for the SG-1000. It was originally an arcade game by Konami known as
			Mikie outside Japan.

			An unlicensed version was released for the Sega Master System in South Korea.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Sindbad Mystery (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)">
		<description>Sindbad Mystery (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Sindbad Mystery is an arcade game developed by Sega for Sega G80 (raster) hardware in 1983. It was ported
			to the SG-1000 in the same year. It follows a boy named Sindbad who must avoid monsters while piecing
			together a treasure map, similar to Pac-Man. He can also use a digging mechanic to trap enemies, similar to
			Heiankyo Alien and Space Panic.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Soukoban (Japan, Australia)">
		<description>Soukoban (Japan, Australia)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>Thinking Rabbit</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Sokoban is a puzzle game developed by Thinking Rabbit. Sega ported it to the SG-1000 in 1985. Neither
			version left Japan.

			Sokoban is the basis for Shove It! ...The Warehouse Game, released for the Sega Mega Drive.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Space Armor (Japan) (Rev 2) (Othello Multivision)">
		<description>Space Armor (Japan) (Rev 2) (Othello Multivision)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Tsukuda Original</developer>
		<publisher>Tsukuda Original</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Space Armor is a 1984 shoot-'em-up game developed and published by Tsukuda Original. It was built with
			the Othello Multivision in mind, but like all Multivision games, is also compatible with the SG-1000. Space
			Armor was not released outside of Japan.

			The game is built similarly to Namco's Xevious, in that it is a vertical shooter where one button fires at
			flying targets and the other at ground targets.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Space Invaders (Japan)">
		<description>Space Invaders (Japan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Earth is under attack from rows of bomb dropping aliens, and you need to defend it! The rows of aliens
			begin at the top of the screen, and you control a laser cannon at the bottom of the screen. Your goal is to
			earn points by shooting the aliens before they can land. The aliens march back and forth, and each time the
			end of the screen is reached they will drop one row closer to the bottom. Shoot them all, and you move on to
			the next (tougher) level, but if even one of them lands the game is over.

			Surprisingly the SG-1000 port of the game was one of the most accurate of its time, surpassing the NES and
			MSX versions which were the console's main competitors. Though it adds more color (the arcade version was
			simply black and white, with translucent overlays to mimic color), the SG-1000 version retains all the
			original graphics, whereas other ports (especially for Atari systems) re-drew the invaders due to various
			graphical restrictions.

			The SG-1000 version does not appear to have been released outside of Japan.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Space Mountain (Japan) (Othello Multivision)">
		<description>Space Mountain (Japan) (Othello Multivision)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Tsukuda Original</developer>
		<publisher>Tsukuda Original</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Space Mountain is an SG-1000 game developed and published by Tsukuda Original with the Othello
			Multivision in mind. It is a very primitive third-person space ship shooter, in which the player has to gun
			down enemy craft before infiltrating a base.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Space Slalom (Japan)">
		<description>Space Slalom (Japan)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Orca</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Space Slalom is a video game developed by Orca and published by Sega for the SG-1000 in 1983.

			Though on the surface it appears to be a space-themed vertical shoot-'em-up, there is actually no shooting
			involved. The player controls a shuttle and must navigate it through a course defined by coloured stars,
			similar to ski slaloms. The player must also avoid obstacles, and will be awarded with extra points
			depending on on his/her speed across the course.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Star Force (Japan, Australia)">
		<description>Star Force (Japan, Australia)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Star Force is a 1984 arcade vertical shoot-'em-up developed by Tehkan (now Tecmo), which was later
			brought to the SG-1000 in 1985.

			The SG-1000 version of the game was released on both cartridge an on Sega Card.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Star Jacker (Japan, Europe) (Rev 2)">
		<description>Star Jacker (Japan, Europe) (Rev 2)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>A "new feeling" space game. Glorious space troops fight against invading "Dester" army. Avoid UFO's
			continuous attacks weaving left and right, up and down. Counter-attack by using your fire button. Lead the
			space troops to the Carrier passing through the various mysteriy zones.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Star Soldier (Taiwan)">
		<description>Star Soldier (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>Hudson</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Starbrain, una súper computadora gigante programada para la destrucción, está amenazando al Imperio
			Galáctico. Como un soldado estrella experto y experimentado, necesitas pilotar al César en la estación
			espacial que Starbrain ha ocupado. La estación espacial está fuertemente custodiada por naves enemigas y
			extrañas criaturas robóticas. Podrás encontrar diferentes armas en el camino para encender al César y
			aumentar las posibilidades de una misión exitosa. Star Soldier es un shooter de desplazamiento vertical
			estilo arcade para un jugador.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Super Tank (Japan)">
		<description>Super Tank (Japan)</description>
		<year>1986</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Super Tank is a shoot-'em-up game for the SG-1000. The player drives a tank and is tasked with shooting
			at and destroying enemy units and structures.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Tank Battalion (Taiwan)">
		<description>Tank Battalion (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>DahJee</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Tank Battalion is a 1980 arcade game by Namco which was brought to the MSX in 1984. It was subsequently
			ported to the SG-1000 in Taiwan and Sega Master System in South Korea.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="TwinBee (Taiwan)">
		<description>TwinBee (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Jumbo Team</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>TwinBee is a 1985 arcade game by Konami which was brought to the MSX in 1986. The MSX version was
			subsequently ported to the SG-1000 in Taiwan.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Wonder Boy (Japan) (Rev 1)">
		<description>Wonder Boy (Japan) (Rev 1)</description>
		<year>1986</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>WONDER BOY starts off a long and hazardous journey in pursuit of KING, who has kidnapped his girlfriend,
			TINA. KING lives in a faraway place, inhabited by monstrous creatures and full of many surprises. On the
			way, our hero has to collect food to increase his energy. WONDER BOY's ultimate mission is to rescue TINA
			and prove to one and all that true love always triumphs.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Yamato (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)">
		<description>Yamato (Japan, Europe, Australia, New Zealand)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Avoid the enemy's attack by torpedoes and missiles. Shoot down the missiles. Be careful, YAMATO will
			explode if it is hit broadside. Aim at the enemy and fire the guns. Attack enemy's planes by using your
			quick-friring guuns. Can YAMATO survive through this fierce battle?</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Yie Ar Kung-Fu (Taiwan)">
		<description>Yie Ar Kung-Fu (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Yie Ar Kung-Fu II (Taiwan)">
		<description>Yie Ar Kung-Fu II (Taiwan)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>DahJee</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Beat-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Yie Ar Kung-Fu 2: The Emperor Yie-Gah is a sequel to the MSX / Famicom (NES) version of Yie Ar Kung-Fu,
			rather than the versions directly based on the arcade release. The game follows the quest of Lee Young, the
			main character from the previous game, to become a kung-fu master. This involves fighting with a wide range
			of opponents in a traditional one-on-one 2D environment. Lee Young has a wide range of attack moves he can
			use to lower his opponent's life bar, including traditional punching and kicking attacks as well as jumping
			ones. Opponents are well equipped with unique weapons and attacks.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Zaxxon (Japan, Taiwan)">
		<description>Zaxxon (Japan, Taiwan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>ZAXXON thrusts you into the depths of outer space. Test your pilot skills as you strap into the command
			position. Prepare for an action-packed challenge of space survival. Score points as you dive, climb, and
			swoop down to destroy the enemy's floating fortress. Dodge deadly laser barriers, enemy missiles, and rapid
			gunfire! Destroy enemy fuel tanks and your own supply is replenished. Survive the enemy's fighter fleet
			attack and face the ultimate challenge... the powerful, armored ZAXXON ROBOT.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Zippy Race (Japan, Australia)">
		<description>Zippy Race (Japan, Australia)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>The player takes control of a motorcyclist who's in a race to be the first to traverse the United States
			from the west to the east coast, starting in Los Angeles and ending up in New York City.

			Gameplay consists of the player dodging cars and other roadway hazards on their way to the next checkpoint.
			Players can either accelerate or hit the brakes on their motorcycle so they can avoid getting into an
			accident. Accidents cause the player to lose fuel and running out of fuel can end the game. So players must
			keep an eye out on the fuel gauge, which can be refilled by fuel barrels littered throughout each stage.
			Each car the player passes betters their ranks which increases their score.

			The SG-1000 version of the game is one of two SG-1000 releases to see four separate Japanese releases (the
			other being Monaco GP) - three on cartridge with each of the SG-1000's box designs, and one on Sega Card.
			Despite this it did not see a release outside of Japan.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Zoom 909 (Japan, Taiwan)">
		<description>Zoom 909 (Japan, Taiwan)</description>
		<year>1985</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Zoom 909 is an arcade game developed by Sega for VCO Object arcade hardware. It was released worldwide in
			1982, however after obtaining a license for Buck Rogers, western versions of the game became known as Buck
			Rogers: Planet of Zoom. Both Zoom 909 and Buck Rogers: Planet of Zoom are largely the same game minus some
			minor graphical differences.

			Though most home ports of the game are based on Planet of Zoom, Zoom 909 was brought to the Japanese MSX in
			1983 and SG-1000 in 1985. These versions take more liberties with the formula, introducing a top-down stage
			as level 3.</story>
	</game>
</menu>