<?xml version="1.0"?>
<menu>
	<game name="Baseball Stars Color - Pocket Sports Series (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Baseball Stars Color - Pocket Sports Series (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Big Bang Pro Wrestling (Japan) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Big Bang Pro Wrestling (Japan) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>S-Neo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Only a handful of top wrestlers can be show their face on the TV for their fans at home. In the I.E.W
			mat, this rule is no exception. In an event practiced for 300 years, only the best performances are in
			demand. This year, the great king of the I.E.W, Joseph Steel, returns to defend his throne. The story of
			eight top wrestlers competing for the greatest prize on the ring, the I.E.W champion belt, is about to
			begin...</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Bikkuriman 2000 - Viva! Pocket Festival! (Japan)">
		<description>Bikkuriman 2000 - Viva! Pocket Festival! (Japan)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Biomotor Unitron (USA, Europe)">
		<description>Biomotor Unitron (USA, Europe)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Biomotor Unitron is a RPG for the Neo Geo Pocket Color.

			After a meteor brings a new source of energy to the world, the construction of giant robots begins. These
			robots are used for entertainment and fight in arena fights against one-another for the title Master of
			Masters. You play a duo of characters that participates in these gladiator battles. You can control both
			characters and have to explore and perform quests to earn money and items to upgrade your Unitron robot
			with. You can talk to inhabitants of the city and buy new items at stores.

			The Unitron changes visibly when you apply upgrades and a great deal of upgrades are at hand. Over two
			hundred different weapon configurations are possible. Each weapon and part has a certain material and
			element. Fire weapons will work better against wooden robots than water-based robots.

			Beneath the city there are large dungeons where most quests will have to be solved and most items will be
			found.

			The battles are like in Pokémon, completely menu based. You pick whatever powers you want to use from a
			drop-down list.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Bust-A-Move Pocket (USA)">
		<description>Bust-A-Move Pocket (USA)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>The classic game Bubble Bobble is the ancestor of Puzzle Bobble. Your aim in each stage is to break all
			the bubbles, by breaking 3 or more of the same color. The game contains a two-player mode where each player
			tries to break all bubbles first.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Cool Boarders Pocket (Japan, Europe) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Cool Boarders Pocket (Japan, Europe) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>UEP Systems</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.45</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Cool Boarders Pocket differs to other games in the Cool Boarders series. It features an isometric
			(overhead) view instead of a third-person perspective. The game features two play modes a free-ride mode
			where the player navigates an obstacle course with no restrictions until he/she reaches the goal, and a
			survival mode where the player snowboards through the obstacle course until they run out of health. The game
			allows the player to choose one of two characters; a female or male snowboarder.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Cool Cool Jam (Japan)">
		<description>Cool Cool Jam (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Rhythm</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>Cool Cool Jam is a rhythm video game which appeared on the Neo Geo Pocket Color in 2000. Cool Cool Jam is
			comparable in gameplay to other rhythm games such as: PaRappa the Rapper, Donkey Konga or Beatmania.

			The storyline involves a boy and a girl who are transported 1,000 years into the future. To return home they
			must form a successful and popular music band.

			The game can be played by one or two players. In two player mode the game plays like a duet; the players
			take it in turn to play tune and receive a message after completion. The game also features a single player
			storymode which has adventure game elements. Various instruments can be played in the game. Each instrument
			has a different playing style. The instruments include:

			Clapping to a beat - a bar moves across the screen the player taps a button when they see a red dot. If
			successful the dot glows.

			Violin - The player taps either the A or B when a red light (button A) or a green light (button B) appears.
			The power can be altered by moving the joystick up and down.

			Bluesharp - The player moves the joystick to coincide with the position of the lights. The player then
			pushes A or B depending whether a red or green light appears.

			Guitar - The player pushes A or B to play the strings and the joystick controls the pick.

			Saxophone - The player moves the joystick and the buttons to control the pitch as the symbols appear on
			screen.

			Trumpet - The player moves the joystick in four directions to change the pitch to coincide with the coloured
			symbols. The player then pushes A or B when the marker appears. A bar indicates air pressure.

			Guitar 2 - Plays the same as the previous Guitar game only upside down.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Crush Roller (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Crush Roller (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Crush Roller is a game for the Neo Geo Pocket Color based on the 1981 arcade game Make Trax, which was
			released as Crush Roller in Europe and Asia.

			The object of the game is to color the entire maze-like playing field with a paint brush. While you paint,
			two enemies walk around in the maze, when they hit you, you lose a life.

			A level has rollers which you can push forward with your paint brush. If you capture an enemy in the path of
			the roller he dies and is temporarily taken out of the game. This scores you extra points. Each subsequent
			enemy rolled over is worth more points.

			Every once in a while another creature will pop up, it will run around leaving behind track marks in your
			paint. Painting over this creature removes it from the game and scores you additional points. His tracks
			have to be repainted.

			When the entire maze is painted you win the level. Unlike the original arcade version the Neo Geo Pocket
			Color version has multiple levels.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Dark Arms - Beast Buster 1999 (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Dark Arms - Beast Buster 1999 (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Noise Factory</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Dark Arms: Beast Buster 1999 is a RPG for the Neo Geo Pocket Color. It's a spin-off from the arcade game
			Beast Busters.

			Parallel to our world we find the Dark Realm. As the player, you find access to this parallel dimension
			after signing a pact with the Master of the Dark Realm. In his realm, you are supposed to catch monsters.
			These can be fed to your biological weapons: Dark Arms. You weapons gain abilities from consumed monsters
			and can evolve into more powerful equipment. You can also find seeds in the Dark Realm that turn into new
			weapons.

			The game features puzzles that have to be solved and a wide array of undead monsters that can be fed to your
			Dark Arms.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Delta Warp (Japan) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Delta Warp (Japan) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Iosys</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Delta Warp is a puzzle game released in 2000 for the Neo Geo Pocket Color. The game involves the player
			moving triangular shaped tiles across a board whilst avoiding hazards such as ice. Delta Warp was released
			only in Japan but features English text menus and the simple gameplay style means it can be played by
			non-Japanese readers.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Densetsu no Ogre Battle Gaiden - Zenobia no Ouji (Japan)">
		<description>Densetsu no Ogre Battle Gaiden - Zenobia no Ouji (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Quest</developer>
		<publisher>Quest</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>A side story to the original Ogre Battle game for the SNES, Zenobia no Ouji's side-story takes place
			during the fourteenth chapter ("The Capital of Milano") of the original game.

			Much like its predecessor, the game is a unique blend of traditional RPG and strategy gameplay. As the hero
			of the game, you lead a growing army of troops as you progress through the game in a series of pivotal
			battles. Before each battle you are given the option to setup your army into distinct groups. Then you are
			given a mission on the map and you can then set your army out to do your bidding. As your unit groups travel
			along the map on the way to their given objective, they'll happen along enemy unit groups. When they meet,
			the game switches to an isometric-view of the automated turn-based battle that ensues.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Densha de Go! 2 on Neo Geo Pocket (Japan)">
		<description>Densha de Go! 2 on Neo Geo Pocket (Japan)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>The 1998 sequel of the popular Japanese train driving game by Taito has once again been ported to various
			home systems. For the first time on the PlayStation, it is possible to drive through the snow, and take a
			seat in the cockpit of a Shinkansen bullet train.

			The gameplay is more arcade than simulation. The focus is on stopping at the stations at the perfect moment
			and position, keeping up with the schedule, obeying signals and speed limits, and ensuring the safety and
			comfort of the passengers. Mistakes result in points being deducted from a counter. If it reaches 0, the
			game is over.

			The following routes are available:

			1. Hokuhoku Line from Naoetsu to Uragawara
			2. Tohoku Shinkansen from Morioka to Shin-Hanamaki
			3. Akita Shinkansen from Akita to Omagari
			4. Keihin-Tohoku Line from Shinagawa to Ueno
			5. Osaka Loop Line from Osaka to Tennoji (not in the Arcade original)
			6. Kagoshima Main Line from Hakata to Kokura (only in PlayStation and Windows versions)</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Dive Alert - Becky's Version (USA, Europe)">
		<description>Dive Alert - Becky's Version (USA, Europe)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Sacnoth</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.55</score>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Dive Alert: Becky's Version is an RPG for the Neo Geo Pocket Color. There is another version of Dive
			Alert called Dive Alert: Matt's Version. The two games are rather like joint Pokemon releases (Red/Blue,
			etc) wherein they are overall the same game with a variety of smaller differences.

			The player takes control of a character named Becky. The game takes place in the future and the world is
			primarily surrounded by water. The only land is a small patch called Terra. The player must prove their
			worth to be accepted on to Terra by proving their skill as a submarine commander and destroying enemy
			vessels.

			Becky's version features different characters, items and boats from Matt's Version. These are logged in a
			device similar to a Pokédex (from Pokemon). Battles take place against enemy ships and a radar view is used
			to help the player guide torpedoes towards the enemy vessels. Much of the game is text-based with animated
			cutscenes.

			The game features the ability for two players to link up Neo Geo Pocket Color units to exchanges ships and
			data, and to battle one on one. The game also features battery back-up and a training mode.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Dive Alert - Matt's Version (USA, Europe)">
		<description>Dive Alert - Matt's Version (USA, Europe)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Sacnoth</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.5</score>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>The player takes control of a character named Matt. The game is set in the future and the world is
			primarily surrounded by water. The only small patch of land called is called Terra. The player must show
			their worth to be accepted on to Terra by proving their skill as a submarine commander and destroying enemy
			vessels.

			Matt's version features different characters, items and boats to Becky's version. These are logged in a
			device similar to a Pokédex. The battles take place against other ships. A radar view is used to help
			players guide torpedoes against the enemy. A large part of the game is text based with animated cutscenes.
			Two players can link-up with the cable to battle, exchange ships and accumulate other data.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Dokodemo Mahjong (Japan)">
		<description>Dokodemo Mahjong (Japan)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>ADK</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Board Games</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>Jeu de Mahjong ou l'on prend part à des parties de 4 joueurs, et ou l'on joue de l'argent.
			La partie se termine une fois notre cave de depart epuisé.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Dynamite Slugger (Japan, Europe) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Dynamite Slugger (Japan, Europe) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.45</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Dynamite Slugger is a video game. It was released in 2000 for the Neo Geo Pocket Color handheld game
			console. The game is similar to other Baseball videogames on the Neo Geo Pocket Color such as Baseball Stars
			and Baseball Stars Color. Due to Dynamite Slugger being the latest baseball videogame to be released for the
			Neo Geo Pocket Color it features better graphics than other sports titles.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Evolution - Eternal Dungeons (Europe)">
		<description>Evolution - Eternal Dungeons (Europe)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>ESP</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>A portable version of Evolution: The World of Sacred Device. Eternal Dungeon tells the story of the young
			explorer Mag Launcher and his quest for the fabled Evolutia, an item of immense power.

			The basic premise of the game is to take quests in the town and then assemble your party and attempt to
			clear out the many dungeons in the game, grinding your characters and getting the loot and experience needed
			to advance the plot and buy items, equipment, and upgrades for your Cy-frame, a robotic attachment that
			enables Mag to enhance his combat abilities.

			As expected for a portable version, the gameplay has been significantly downgraded from its original
			Dreamcast version. Town navigation is menu-driven and all graphics are now top-down 2D sprites, with all
			dungeons being pre-designed instead of randomly generated. Combat is turn-based using a menu system from
			which you select your actions for each party member (up to 3) and execute them, but otherwise remains
			unchanged.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Fantastic Night Dreams - Cotton (Europe)">
		<description>Fantastic Night Dreams - Cotton (Europe)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Fantastic Night Dreams: Cotton is a 2D side-scrolling shooter in which the player takes the role of the
			young witch Cotton, who sets out on her magical broom on a quest to get her favorite candy. Fortunately for
			us her obsession gets her in the way of several world-threatening terrors that she must destroy in standard
			shooter fare.

			The game features an experience-earning system in which the more enemies the player kills the more he can
			upgrade his weapon by collecting power crystals. Players can also charge their weapon for special attacks
			and enlist the aid of Silk, Cotton's magical fairy friend who can form up in different "option"
			configurations.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Faselei! (USA, Europe)">
		<description>Faselei! (USA, Europe)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Sacnoth</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.85</score>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Faselei! is one of the last titles to be released for the Neo Geo Pocket Color and even features
			digitised lyrics to the game's main theme. Heavily story driven, this strategy RPG takes place in a time
			when mechs known as TS are the weapon of choice for combat. Gameplay revolves around the battles and
			customising your TS between those battles.

			Battles are part turn based and part realtime. The player inputs their actions at the beginning of the turn.
			The amount of actions they can input is dependant on their type of TS. Once they have finished their
			selection everything is played out in realtime for the duration of the turn. This makes thinking about what
			your opponents and allies will do in advance essential before taking your turn.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Fatal Fury F-Contact - Pocket Fighting Series (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Fatal Fury F-Contact - Pocket Fighting Series (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Fighter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Using the world-famous Japanese "SD" (Super-Deformed) artwork style, this is the only title of the Fatal
			Fury series to be released on SNK's color handheld.

			The game is based on its arcade/console counterpart Real Bout Fatal Fury 2: The Newcomers, and has its main
			characteristics, like the possibility of execute special moves while blocking (a.k.a. Breakshots), the
			execution of high-strength blows (a.k.a. S. Power and P. Power moves) and the starring of two new combatants
			(Li Xiangfei and Rick Strowd).

			Due to NGPC hardware limitations, some characters have been removed from the main cast (as well as the
			background/foreground battle plane system). With this, the fighters initially available for this contest
			are: Andy Bogard, Terry Bogard, Joe Higashi, Mai Shiranui, Kim Kaphwan, Ryuji Yamazaki, Rick Strowd, Li
			Xiangfei, Billy Kane, Wolfgang Krauser and Geese Howard.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Ganbare Neo Poke-kun (Kari) (Japan)">
		<description>Ganbare Neo Poke-kun (Kari) (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>In this unique game you keep watch on the wacky Neo Poke-kun, a cartoony programmer...thing that lives
			locked in his small Tokyo apartment. You don't have direct control of his actions but instead interact with
			him indirectly by switching stuff in his apartment on and off, which triggers different reactions from him.
			More importantly you can invite different characters to visit Neo Poke-kun, which will also trigger
			different reactions from him. Depending on the time of day and the visitor you may get different reactions
			from Poke-kun, and if you make him happy enough he'll get to work and code a mini-game for you.

			These collection of 30 games form the bulk of the gameplay, and include different clones of other games,
			shooters, short platformers, and compact puzzle challenges similar to Wario Ware

			The game has a distinctly bizarre sense of humor with tons of wacky animations played whenever something
			happens to your Poke-kun, and while some games use basic vector graphics, most use 2D sprites.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Infinity Cure (Japan)">
		<description>Infinity Cure (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Kindle Imagine Develop</developer>
		<publisher>Kindle Imagine Develop</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>A port of the visual novel "Infinity" for the Neo-Geo Pocket Color</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Kikou Seiki Unitron - Sono Tsuide. Hikari Umareru Chi Yori. (Japan)">
		<description>Kikou Seiki Unitron - Sono Tsuide. Hikari Umareru Chi Yori. (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.85</score>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Kikou Seiki Unitron (English: Armor Chronicles Unitron) is the sequel to Biomotor Unitron.
			It was only released in Japan.
			The game takes place 400 years after Biomotor Unitron.
			Kikou Seiki Unitron plays similar to Biomotor Unitron with top down dungeons and menu-based combat.
			The game requires the player to upgrade their unitron robot with various weapons and accessories to compete
			against various enemies within the dungeon areas.
			Using a link cable two players can pit their unitrons against each other in a head-to-head battle.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="King of Fighters R-2 - Pocket Fighting Series (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>King of Fighters R-2 - Pocket Fighting Series (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Fighter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Using again the Japanese "SD" (Super-Deformed) artwork style (now reworked), the KOF Series makes your
			debut in the new SNK's color handheld. The title brings the same gameplay characteristics present in its
			arcade/console counter-part The King of Fighters '98, like the possibility of choose between two game modes
			(Advanced or Extra), an identical adaptation of the battle stages, the addition of "Advantage System"
			(directly related to the power gauges) and the chance to battle with a powered version of the "franchise
			boss", Rugal Bernstein.

			Unlike the previous game (The King of Fighters R-1), this sequence doesn't have a defined storyline, but
			it's implicit that Rugal is still alive and returns once again to try conquer the world and satisfy his evil
			ambitions.

			The teams included in the game were slightly reformulated and now are the following ones (this time, Leona
			Heidern and Iori Yagami are single entries):

			1. Team Kusanagi (Kyo Kusanagi, Saisyu Kusanagi and Shingo Yabuki)Super Babe Team (Athena Asamiya, Yuri
			Sakazaki and Kasumi Todo)
			2. New Southtown Team (Ryo Sakazaki, Mai Shiranui and Terry Bogard)
			3. Orochi Team (Yashiro Nanakase, Shermie and Chris)</story>
	</game>
	<game name="King of Fighters, The - Battle de Paradise (Japan)">
		<description>King of Fighters, The - Battle de Paradise (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Board Games</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>The King of Fighters: Battle De Paradise is a board based, two player party game that plays in a similar
			manner as sugoroku. The player can either link with another user to play or challenge the CPU. Each side
			choose one of four original characters to represent their place on the board as well as an accompanying
			Striker character (the Extra Strikers from The King of Fighters '99: Evolution). If they're unsatisfied with
			their avatar's name, an option to rename their character is also given.

			Players roll a dice and move along the board with various squares. Specially marked squares can trigger one
			of many mini-games for the player's striker to participate in for coins. Mini-games themselves are a
			collection of memory games, dodging contests, quiz challenges, and other games common to the genre. Some of
			these mini-games refer to SNK's older games such as T.A.N.K or previous King of Fighters titles. The main
			goal of the game is to gather coins to buy stars; the player with the most stars wins.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Koi Koi Mahjong (Japan)">
		<description>Koi Koi Mahjong (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Visco</developer>
		<publisher>Visco</publisher>
		<score>0.5</score>
		<genre>Board Games</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>"Koi Koi Mahjong" est une simulation de Mahjong, reservé au marché japonnais.
			Le joueur peux choisir entre 4 protagonistes et 3 modes de jeu.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Last Blade, The - Beyond the Destiny (USA, Europe)">
		<description>Last Blade, The - Beyond the Destiny (USA, Europe)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Saurus</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>1863. History's hidden secret is revealed. During the age known as "Bakumatsu", 135 years ago, chaos
			rules! It's all yours: A new type of weapon fighting game in which Power and Speed weapons, in addition to
			various Repel moves can be used to experience a new sensation in video game thrills!</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Magical Drop Pocket (USA, Europe)">
		<description>Magical Drop Pocket (USA, Europe)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>SAS Sakata</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Magical Drop Pocket's core mechanics are similar to those of Magical Drop III. The only exception is that
			that the battlefield consists of six columns instead of seven, akin to the Super Famicom ports of the first
			two Magical Drop games.

			The game features Story, Self Challenge and Friend Challenge; these correspond to the standard 1P VS Com,
			Solo, and 2P VS modes featured in other Magical Drop games. Story features five difficulty modes while Self
			Challenge features three.

			Like many other handheld puzzle games of the time, Story does not feature a "true" AI opponent; instead, the
			player attempts to fill a gauge by creating chains. While the player attempts to fill this gauge, the AI
			attacks at random intervals.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Memories Off - Pure (Japan)">
		<description>Memories Off - Pure (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Kindle Imagine Develop</developer>
		<publisher>Kindle Imagine Develop</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Memories Off: Pure game takes place a few years prior to the events in Memories Off. (a Visual Novel
			released in 1999 on Playstation)
			Tomoya and Ayaka are neighbors who communicate with each other through their bedroom windows and who attend
			the same junior high school with Yue.
			One playthrough of Pure takes about 3-4 hours, but it has replay value through a pair of endings and during
			subsequent runthroughs to re-experience second-half scenarios from Ayaka's and Yue's points of view.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Metal Slug - 1st Mission (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Metal Slug - 1st Mission (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Ukiyotei</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>As a member of the elite forces squad "Peregrine Falcons," your mission is to eliminate the evil Colonel
			Bildegaarn. Using the Metal Slug multifunction tank and the Slug Flyer as well as your wits and handgun
			blast through up to 17 missions in your quest to make the world safe from tyranny. Multiple stage
			progressions and a gameplay ranking system give reason to play through more than once. In-game save lets the
			player on the go turn off the Neo Geo Pocket and not lose progress.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Metal Slug - 2nd Mission (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Metal Slug - 2nd Mission (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Ukiyotei</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Take control of the Metal Slug tank on the NGPC once again, this time to defeat the rebel strike force
			"Phantom." Travel through 38 stages in a non-linear battle path defeating enemy troops and rescuing
			hostages. Pilot the Metal Slug tank, Slug Flyer combat jet, and the Slug Sub submarine and fire the heavy
			machine gun, rocket launcher, and fire gun. Two unique playable characters, a list of rescued hostages, and
			a time attack mode add depth to this side-scroller.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Mezase! Kanji Ou (Japan)">
		<description>Mezase! Kanji Ou (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Educational</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>A kanji-study game with a quiz-like approach.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Mizuki Shigeru no Youkai Shashinkan (Japan)">
		<description>Mizuki Shigeru no Youkai Shashinkan (Japan)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Ukiyotei</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>This is an RPG based on the works of the famous manga artist Shigeru Mizuki, known in Japan for his
			knowledge of youkai (supernatural ghosts of Japanese folklore). In this game, you explore various areas of
			Japan, taking pictures of youkai, and using these pictures in card battles. This is a very popular game
			among Japanese NGPC enthusiasts.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Neo 21 - Pocket Casino Series (World)">
		<description>Neo 21 - Pocket Casino Series (World)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Neo Baccarat - Pocket Casino Series (Japan, Europe) (v1.1)">
		<description>Neo Baccarat - Pocket Casino Series (Japan, Europe) (v1.1)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Dyna Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Dyna Corp.</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Experience the Thrills of NEO BACCARAT, the New Game in the Pocket Casino Series!

			Will the House win? Or maybe the Player? Guess on the winner and place your bets! "Baccarat" is the hottest
			game in the casino. And now you can find all its pulse-pounding excitement on NEOGEO POCKET COLOR! The
			Pocket Casino Series: NEO BACCARAT. Are you up for the challenge?!

			Thrill to the fun of "Original Mode" and "Casino Mode" in Single-Player Games!
			Use the NEOGEO POCKET LINK CABLE for 2-Player Showdowns!
			Be it American- or European-Style Baccarat, NEOGEO POCKET's got it!

			To see explanations of game rules, select the "Game Explanation" item in the Option Menu.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Neo Cherry Master Color - Pocket Casino Series (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Neo Cherry Master Color - Pocket Casino Series (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Neo Derby Champ Daiyosou (Japan)">
		<description>Neo Derby Champ Daiyosou (Japan)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>Dyna</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>Neo Derby Champ Daiyosou is a Sports game, developed and published by Dyna Corporation, which was
			released in Japan in 1999.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Neo Dragon's Wild - Pocket Casino Series (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Neo Dragon's Wild - Pocket Casino Series (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Neo Mystery Bonus - Pocket Casino Series (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Neo Mystery Bonus - Pocket Casino Series (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Neo Poke Pro Yakyuu (Japan) (v1.1)">
		<description>Neo Poke Pro Yakyuu (Japan) (v1.1)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NeoPoke Pro Yakyuu es un juego de deportes, desarrollado y publicado por SNK, que fue lanzado en Japón en
			1999.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Neo Turf Masters (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Neo Turf Masters (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.85</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Neo Turf Masters is a golf game that offers play in three different countries. You can play in the US,
			Germany, and Japan. There are 18 holes per course, just like in real life, which totals to 54 holes. The
			game features a two-player versus mode and three single player modes. You can choose from one of six
			different characters, who each have their own strengths and weaknesses. Like many other golf games, you use
			an accurate click type of play, where you click in an overhead map where you want to hit the ball, then
			adjust hook, slice, and power. In Versus mode, you can earn "super-clubs" that can only be used once. These
			can also be traded between friends.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="NeoGeo Cup '98 Plus Color - Pocket Sports Series (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>NeoGeo Cup '98 Plus Color - Pocket Sports Series (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Nige-ron-pa (Japan)">
		<description>Nige-ron-pa (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Dennou Eizou</developer>
		<publisher>Dennou Eizou</publisher>
		<score>0.3</score>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>A simple handheld RPG mostly made up of side- and fetch quests. As you move through the game you can
			recruit friends and receive various licenses that function similar to jobs, that allow you to perform more
			powerful skills and magic attacks.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pac-Man (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Pac-Man (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>One of the most popular and influential games of the 1980's, Pac-Man stars a little, yellow dot-muncher
			who works his way around to clear a maze of the various dots and fruit which inhabit the board.

			Pac-Man's goal is continually challenged by four ghosts: The shy blue ghost Bashful (Inky), the trailing red
			ghost Shadow (Blinky), the fast pink ghost Speedy (Pinky), and the forgetful orange ghost Pokey (Clyde). One
			touch from any of these ghosts means a loss of life for Pac-Man.

			Pac-Man can turn the tables on his pursuers by eating of the four Energizers located within the maze. During
			this time, the ghosts turn blue, and Pac-Man can eat them for bonus points. This only lasts for a limited
			amount of time, as the ghost's eyes float back to their center box, and regenerate to chase after Pac-Man
			again.

			Survive a few rounds of gameplay, and be treated to humorous intermissions between Pac-Man and the ghosts.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Azteca (Japan)">
		<description>Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Azteca (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<score>0.3</score>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Dekahel 2 (Japan)">
		<description>Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Dekahel 2 (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Delsol 2 (Japan)">
		<description>Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Delsol 2 (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<score>0.5</score>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - e-CUP (Japan)">
		<description>Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - e-CUP (Japan)</description>
		<year>2001</year>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Hanabi (Japan)">
		<description>Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Hanabi (Japan)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<score>0.3</score>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Ohhanabi (Japan)">
		<description>Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Ohhanabi (Japan)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Porcano 2 (Japan)">
		<description>Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Porcano 2 (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Aruze Corp</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Ward of Lights (Japan)">
		<description>Pachi-Slot Aruze Oukoku Pocket - Ward of Lights (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>Aruze Corp</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pachinko Hisshou Guide - Pocket Parlor (Japan)">
		<description>Pachinko Hisshou Guide - Pocket Parlor (Japan)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Vistec</developer>
		<publisher>Sankyo</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Casino</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Party Mail (Japan)">
		<description>Party Mail (Japan)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Picture Puzzle (Europe)">
		<description>Picture Puzzle (Europe)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Picture Puzzle (Oekaki Puzzle in Japan) is a paint-by-numbers puzzle game developed by Success for the
			Neo Geo Pocket Color. The game plays identical to Nintendo's Picross series. Picture Puzzle offers a total
			of 200 puzzles: 20 5x5 puzzles, 105 10x10's, and 75 15x15's. This is biased towards smaller puzzles because
			the grids in anything larger would be incredibly tiny on the NGPC's screen. Also, larger puzzles take much
			longer to solve; smaller puzzles allows you to pick up the Pocket for 10-20 minutes at a time and, on a good
			day, solve a complete puzzle.

			Upon completion of a puzzle, the game replaces it with a colored version of the same grid and gives it a
			title. Especially with the smaller puzzles, this is helpful in that it is sometimes otherwise unclear as to
			what exactly the completed picture is supposed to be. Because it colorizes them, the game requires the Neo
			Geo Pocket Color, i.e, it won't run on a monochrome Neo Geo Pocket.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pocket Love - if (Japan)">
		<description>Pocket Love - if (Japan)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>Kindle Imagine Develop</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>Pocket Love: If es un juego de aventuras, desarrollado y publicado por Kid, que fue lanzado en Japón en
			1999.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pocket Reversi (Europe)">
		<description>Pocket Reversi (Europe)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Success</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.5</score>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Pocket Reversi is an adaptation by Success of the classic strategy game. In single-player, you must make
			your way through Tournament Mode, competing against eight progressively difficult opponents. You can also
			take the 'Ability Level Test' which grades you based on your play. For beginners, 'Reversi Lesson' provides
			ten short tutorial sessions to teach you the basics of the game. There's also a 'Free Play' mode where you
			can choose to see all available moves and to even take back your last move. Finally, there's a two-player
			mode accessible via the link cable.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pocket Tennis Color - Pocket Sports Series (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Pocket Tennis Color - Pocket Sports Series (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>This sports favorite boasts eight playable characters and enough tennis action to keep any fan happy.
			Enjoy realistic play that gives you complete array of shots, including lobs, high-speed smashes and more.
			Exhibition mode sets up a single match against the computer, or, with the NeoGeo Cable Link (sold
			separately), a friend. Tournament mode pits you against stiff competition to see if you've got what it takes
			to earn the title. Save your match results so you can brag later. Record mode lets you relax and enjoy your
			on-court accomplishments by viewing your records and trophies.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="PP-AA01 - Pusher - Program - Hontai Controller Gawa (Japan)">
		<description>PP-AA01 - Pusher - Program - Hontai Controller Gawa (Japan)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Puyo Pop (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Puyo Pop (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>The object of this head-to-head puzzle game is to clear your grid of falling patterns called puyos by
			forming chains of four or more same-colored puyos in a straight line or one of several geometric patterns.
			What makes this a challenging two-player contest is the fact that when you clear a chain of puyos from your
			grid, it drops a random piece of filler onto your opponent's grid. The more puyos you clear, the more you
			fill your opponent's grid, and if you can clutter up his grid enough to fill it to the top, you've won the
			game.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Puzzle Link (USA, Europe)">
		<description>Puzzle Link (USA, Europe)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Puzzle Link is a game where blocks of matching color have to be dissolved. New blocks constantly scroll
			into the screen from the top. The game is over when the first blocks reach the bottom of the screen. You can
			dissolve blocks by shooting at them. The shots form a line where they impact. If that line connects
			otherwise unconnected blocks of the same color they will dissolve.

			There are three different modes: In "Normal" you have to link two special blocks that appear after some
			time. If you manage to finish the level within the time limit you will unlock one of 50 collectible cards.
			In "Clear Mode" you have to clear a given constellation of blocks. "Battle Mode" is a two player link-cable
			mode.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Puzzle Link 2 (USA, Europe)">
		<description>Puzzle Link 2 (USA, Europe)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>The gameplay of Puzzle Link 2 is generally identical to the first game: Puzzle Link is a game where
			blocks of matching color have to be dissolved. New blocks constantly scroll into the screen from the top.
			The game is over when the first blocks reach the bottom of the screen. You can dissolve blocks by shooting
			at them. The shots form a line where they impact. If that line connects otherwise unconnected blocks of the
			same color they will dissolve.

			There are new modes in Puzzle Link 2. Like the original, there are the standard challenge and puzzle rounds.
			But new to the series is the marathon-style game where you continue eliminating pieces as the game gradually
			increases speed. In this mode, more power-ups appear as the player performs faster. Here, you get three
			shots that will eliminate the same color tile from the board. The game also has link cable support for two
			players.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Rockman - Battle &amp; Fighters (Japan)">
		<description>Rockman - Battle &amp; Fighters (Japan)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Fighter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Rockman Battle &amp; Fighters is a fighting game similar to the two arcade titles Mega Man: The Power
			Battle, and Mega Man 2: The Power Fighters.
			Playing as one of four characters (Mega Man, Proto Man, Bass, and Duo), the player chooses between three
			sets of boss battles with various Robot Masters from the series.
			The battles are fought linearly in any order, and after each boss is defeated, a special weapon is added to
			the player's arsenal.
			Each boss is weak to one specific weapon, so the player is encouraged to strategize the order in which the
			bosses are faced.
			Two players can use a link cable to transfer database information between systems, but no co-op or versus
			play is supported.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Samurai Shodown! 2 - Pocket Fighting Series (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Samurai Shodown! 2 - Pocket Fighting Series (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Fighter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>One of SNK's legendary fighting game series has made a return! In Samurai Shodown II, you can take on one
			of the roles of 15 warriors as you fight your way through the land to defeat the evil Mizuki! Slash, kick,
			and slice your opponents in half...do whatever it takes...live by the sword, and die by its blade.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Shanghai Mini (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>Shanghai Mini (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Shanghai Mini is a release for one more platform in the for ever continuing series of Activision's tile
			matching game.

			Included are classic, tournament and dynasty modes. Classic is normal game with six different board layouts.
			In tournament game player challenges the Tower of Shanghai and tries to beat the Shanghai Master by solving
			different board layouts within time limit. Dynasty is two player competition - against computer or human
			(requires link cable) opponent.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Shougi no Tatsujin Color (Japan)">
		<description>Shougi no Tatsujin Color (Japan)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>ADK</developer>
		<publisher>ADK</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Board Games</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>Shogi no Tatsujin Color es un juego misceláneo, desarrollado por ADK y publicado por SNK, que fue lanzado
			en Japón en 1999.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="SNK Gals' Fighters (USA, Europe)">
		<description>SNK Gals' Fighters (USA, Europe)</description>
		<year>2000</year>
		<developer>Yumekobo</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Fighter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Organized and sponsored by a mysterious fighter nicknamed as "Miss X", the first Queen of Fighters
			Tournament is officially open, but this competition differs of the others for allowing ONLY women as
			participants. Meanwhile, after have passed for several and tough fights (including a final showdown with
			Miss X), the winner will be rewarded with a mystical artifact known as the "K Talisman", that has the
			capacity to grant any wish. With this rare-unique possibility of accomplish their pessoal dreams and
			ambitions, 8 powerful femme fatale fighters were invited to face the biggest combat of their lives...

			Behind this simple storyline, the title brings a cast of 8 all-female characters taken from SNK's fighting
			series The King of Fighters (Mai Shiranui, Yuri Sakazaki, Athena Asamiya, Leona Heidern, Shermie), The Last
			Blade (Akari Ichijyou) and Samurai Shodown (Shiki, Nakoruru); all with the same blows (parodied or not) of
			their origin games.

			The gameplay is identical to KOF's Advanced Mode (e.g. Emergency Evasion and Run commands), but without
			SDMs. To increase the replay factor, a power-up mode was included: depending on your combat performance,
			you'll be favored with several random items (e.g. Start with full MAX gauge, Speed Up etc.) that can be used
			to improve your character for a while.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="SNK vs. Capcom - Card Fighters 2 - Expand Edition (Japan)">
		<description>SNK vs. Capcom - Card Fighters 2 - Expand Edition (Japan)</description>
		<year>2001</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Card Battle</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>SNK vs. Capcom: Card Fighter's Clash 2 Expand Edition continues the mascot packed trading card game
			action that began with the original.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="SNK vs. Capcom - Card Fighters' Clash - Capcom Version (USA, Europe)">
		<description>SNK vs. Capcom - Card Fighters' Clash - Capcom Version (USA, Europe)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<score>0.9</score>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Compete in the SC Card Fighters' Clash tournament with your Capcom deck in this NGPC card game. Collect
			the 300 cards from both SNK and Capcom franchises and duel and trade with your friends using the extensive
			link mode. With mechanics similar to CCGs such as Yu-Gi-Oh and popular characters from both SNK and Capcom,
			Card Fighters clash offers both collection and strategy gameplay. This game also allows linking with SNK vs.
			Capcom: Match of the Millennium to transfer collectible points.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="SNK vs. Capcom - Card Fighters' Clash - SNK Version (USA, Europe)">
		<description>SNK vs. Capcom - Card Fighters' Clash - SNK Version (USA, Europe)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<score>0.9</score>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Compete in the SC Card Fighters' Clash tournament with your SNK deck in this NGPC card game. Collect the
			300 cards from both SNK and Capcom franchises and duel and trade with your friends using the extensive link
			mode. With mechanics similar to CCGs such as Yu-Gi-Oh and popular characters from both SNK and Capcom, Card
			Fighters clash offers both collection and strategy gameplay. This game also allows linking with SNK vs.
			Capcom: Match of the Millennium to transfer collectible points.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="SNK vs. Capcom - The Match of the Millennium (World) (En,Ja)">
		<description>SNK vs. Capcom - The Match of the Millennium (World) (En,Ja)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<score>0.9</score>
		<genre>Fighter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>With 18 starting characters (26 total after unlocking), numerous battle modes and varied minigames, this
			may be the largest fighting game for the Neo Geo Pocket Color. Choose the fighting style that suits you from
			the available Single, Tag and Team modes. The SC Olympic mode grants access to minigames from a music game
			featuring Felicia to a whack-a-mole style game with Jubei. The Olympic mode also allows players to compete
			for gold, silver and bronze medals in various fighting challenges. Link features include NGPC-to-NGPC
			battles and NGPC-to-Dreamcast data exchange with other SNK titles.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Sonic The Hedgehog - Pocket Adventure (World)">
		<description>Sonic The Hedgehog - Pocket Adventure (World)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<score>0.9</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Sonic the Hedgehog Pocket Adventure, or Sonic Pocket Adventure for short, is a 1999 platform video game
			in the Sonic the Hedgehog series developed by SNK. It was released in December 1999 in North America, and
			May 2000 in Japan, exclusively for the Neo Geo Pocket Color handheld game console. It is also only the
			second game of the Sonic series ever to be released on a non-Sega video game console, the first being Sonic
			Jam on the Game.com. The game was praised by critics, receiving perfect scores from multiple reviews.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Soreike!! Hanafuda Doujou (Japan)">
		<description>Soreike!! Hanafuda Doujou (Japan)</description>
		<year>1999</year>
		<developer>Dyna Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Dyna</publisher>
		<score>0.4</score>
		<genre>Board Games</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>¡¡Soreyuke !! Hanafuda Dōjō es un juego Hanafuda de tarjetas de flores japonesas tradicionales. Cuenta
			con el tipo de juego Koi-Koi, una configuración completa de reglas y tres modos de juego diferentes:
			1. Batalla (cable de enlace de dos jugadores versus)
			2. Certificación (clasifique sus habilidades)
			3. Torneo (versus ocho jugadores de computadora diferentes)</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Super Real Mahjong - Premium Collection (Japan)">
		<description>Super Real Mahjong - Premium Collection (Japan)</description>
		<year>2001</year>
		<developer>SETA Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>SETA Corporation</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Board Games</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>Super Real Mahjong Premium Collection es la primera entrega portátil de la serie Super Real Mahjong. Como
			de costumbre, juegas strip mahjong con chicas guapas, esta vez varias de muchos de los juegos. Sin embargo,
			debido a las limitaciones del sistema, solo algunas escenas de tira están animadas. También tiene algunas
			cualidades similares a las de una novela visual, en particular un modo historia en el que intentas
			concentrarte en una chica cada vez que se juega. Esto se logra eligiendo las opciones correctas cuando se le
			presentan. Si logras concentrarte en una sola chica, su CG se desbloquea en la galería.</story>
	</game>
</menu>