<?xml version="1.0"?>
<menu>
	<game name="32 in 1 (Australia)">
		<description>32 in 1 (Australia)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Ace of Aces (USA)">
		<description>Ace of Aces (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Alien Brigade (USA)">
		<description>Alien Brigade (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Asteroids (USA)">
		<description>Asteroids (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Atari 7800 Development Card (USA)">
		<description>Atari 7800 Development Card (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Ballblazer (USA)">
		<description>Ballblazer (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Barnyard Blaster (USA)">
		<description>Barnyard Blaster (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Basketbrawl (USA)">
		<description>Basketbrawl (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Centipede (USA)">
		<description>Centipede (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Choplifter! (USA)">
		<description>Choplifter! (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Commando (USA)">
		<description>Commando (USA)</description>
		<year>1988</year>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Several levels await your super-tough Commando in this arcade conversion. Armed with only a standard
			rifle and a few grenades you must take on hordes of Nazis. Some are wandering around in the open, while
			others have picked out hiding places, which you must approach from certain angles. Trees, rivers and bridges
			create a varied combat-like terrain and must be incorporated into your thinking. Extra grenades can be
			collected, and will definitely be required, as they allow you to kill form distance and thus avoid some
			enemy shots.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Crack'ed (USA)">
		<description>Crack'ed (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Crossbow (USA)">
		<description>Crossbow (USA)</description>
		<year>1987</year>
		<developer>Exidy, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>In Crossbow, you and several friends are trying to cross many treacherous landscapes in order to retrieve
			stolen treasures from the castle of the Evil Master. All of the members of your party are unarmed, however
			you carry a crossbow. Using this, you need to shoot any obstacles or hostile enemies that may get in the way
			of your friends as they cross the screen. You see the landscape from a first person point of view, and one
			by one each member of the party will walk from the left to right on the screen. There are many different
			landscapes that need to be crossed, each with its own variety of dangers. There are deserts with scorpions,
			ice caverns, jungles with hostile monkeys, a lava spewing volcano, and even the heavily guarded castle. The
			game starts with two friends in your party, with additional friends joining after clearing certain parts of
			the game. The game ends when everyone in your party has been killed.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Dark Chambers (USA)">
		<description>Dark Chambers (USA)</description>
		<year>1988</year>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Dark Chambers is an arcade action game similar to Gauntlet. You are an explorer in an underground maze;
			your goal is to survive the 26 different levels and collect as many of the hidden treasures as you can.
			Hidden somewhere in each of the levels is an exit which will take you on to the next level. Trying to stop
			you from completing your quest are a wide variety of creatures, including zombies, wraiths, skeletons,
			wizards, and the grim reaper. Each of the creatures in the game has a different strength; when you shoot a
			creature, it will transform into the next weaker creature. Eventually a creature will become the weakest one
			(a zombie) at which point it can be destroyed. In addition to the creatures and treasures, other items that
			can be found in the maze are keys (to open doors), potions (to restore health), poison (drains health), guns
			(increases your firing rate), traps, shields, and bombs. The game is played from an overhead point of view,
			and is for one player or two players simultaneously.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Desert Falcon (USA)">
		<description>Desert Falcon (USA)</description>
		<year>1987</year>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Desert Falcon is an arcade style shooter. Many of the Pharaoh's great treasures are lost throughout the
			desert, and your goal is to steal as many as you can to earn points. The game features a scrolling,
			isometric point of view as you control your falcon through the various desert landscapes. The treasures you
			are after are guarded of course. Many desert creatures including vultures, warriors, flying fish, sphinxes
			and more will all attempt to stop you from succeeding in your task. Also, at the end of each level you will
			need to face a large, howling sphinx before you can continue on. Your falcon isn't completely unarmed, and
			has the ability to fire darts which can be used to destroy the assorted enemies and the sphinx. In the sand,
			you will occasionally come across some hieroglyphs. Several different superpowers can be gained by landing
			and hopping over three of these hieroglyphs. Depending on which hieroglyphs are collected, you may become
			invincible, warp to the end of the level, earn free points, trick enemies into attacking a decoy instead of
			you, or even get an air bomb which destroys all airborne enemies.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Diagnostic Test Cartrige (USA)">
		<description>Diagnostic Test Cartrige (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Dig Dug (USA)">
		<description>Dig Dug (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Dig Dug is a 1-2 player arcade game in which you have to use your shovel to dig your way through the
			earth. Stopping you from doing this are two monsters, called Pooka and Fygar, who will continually chase you
			around. The only weapon that you carry is an air pump, which you can use to inflate the monsters to the
			point where they explode. (if you start to inflate them but stop doing so, the monsters will get turned back
			to their normal selves.) Furthermore, rocks are scattered throughout the earth, and you can use these rocks
			to squash them. If the monsters do not find you for several seconds, they will eventually get turned into
			ghosts, which are able to walk through the earth. They are invincible and cannot be killed. From time to
			time, vegetables will appear in the center, and you can get these for points.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Donkey Kong (USA)">
		<description>Donkey Kong (USA)</description>
		<year>1981</year>
		<developer>Ikegami Tsushinki</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco Industries, Inc.</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Released in the arcades in 1981, Donkey Kong was not only Nintendo's first real smash hit for the
			company, but marked the introduction for two of their most popular mascots: Mario (originally "Jumpman") and
			Donkey Kong.

			Donkey Kong is a platform-action game that has Mario scale four different industrial themed levels
			(construction zone, cement factory, an elevator-themed level, and removing rivets from girders) in an
			attempt to save the damsel in distress, Pauline, from the big ape before the timer runs out. Once the rivets
			are removed from the final level, Donkey Kong falls, and the two lovers are reunited. From there, the levels
			start over at a higher difficulty.

			Along the way, Mario must dodge a constant stream of barrels, "living" fireballs, and spring-weights.
			Although not as powerful as in other future games, Mario can find a hammer which allows him to destroy the
			barrels and fireballs for a limited amount of time. Additionally, Mario can also find Pauline's hat, purse
			and umbrella for additional bonus points.

			Donkey Kong is also notable for being one of the first complete narratives in video game form, told through
			simplistic cut scenes that advance the story. It should also be noted that in versions of the game for early
			1980's consoles, Donkey Kong only used 2-3 of the original levels, with the cement factory usually omitted.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Donkey Kong Junior (USA)">
		<description>Donkey Kong Junior (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco Industries, Inc.</publisher>
		<score>0.35</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Mario has kidnapped Junior's Papa!

			Donkey Kong Jr. was originally released in the arcades in 1982 as a sequel to Donkey Kong. In this game,
			Mario plays the antagonist, finally having captured Donkey Kong, and has put the ape in a locked cage. As
			Donkey Kong Jr., players will have to make their way through four different levels (Vines, Springboard,
			Chains and Mario's Hideout) in an attempt to find keys to free the little monkey's Father.

			Along the way, Mario will send out Snapjaws, swooping purple birds, and electric sparks in an attempt to
			stop Junior. Junior can defend himself by dropping fruit found around the levels on the heads of his foes.
			The more foes a piece of fruit hits in a falling sequence, the higher bonus points can be scored.

			Junior can also avoid enemies more easily by grabbing hold of two chains or vines at a time to climb away
			faster, or by jumping over his foes. However, any long fall or falling into the water on certain levels will
			mean the loss of a life for Junior.

			In the final cut scene, Junior will free Donkey Kong and both will escape after giving Mario the boot. Once
			all four levels are cleared, the game levels will start over at a higher difficulty.

			Like the original Donkey Kong, the earlier 1980's console versions do not have all of the levels and
			animations from the arcade.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Double Dragon (USA)">
		<description>Double Dragon (USA)</description>
		<year>1988</year>
		<developer>Technos Japan Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<score>0.5</score>
		<genre>Beat-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Set in a post-apocalyptic New York, Double Dragon is the story of Billy and Jimmy Lee, twin brothers
			trained in the fighting style of Sou-Setsu-Ken. Together, they manage a small martial arts training school,
			teaching their students in self-defense. One day, Billy's girlfriend, Marian, is kidnapped off the street by
			the "Black Warriors", a savage street gang led by a man named Willy. The Black Warriors demand the Lee
			brothers disclose their martial arts secrets in exchange for Marian's freedom. The Lee brothers set out on a
			rescue mission to crush the Black Warriors and save Marian.

			Using whatever techniques they have at their disposal, from the basic punches and kicks to the invulnerable
			elbow strike, as well any weapon that comes into their hands, the Lee brothers must pursue the gang through
			the city slum, industrial area and the forest before reaching their hideout to confront the big boss, Willy.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="F-18 Hornet (USA)">
		<description>F-18 Hornet (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Fatal Run (USA)">
		<description>Fatal Run (USA)</description>
		<year>1990</year>
		<developer>Sculptured Software</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.45</score>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>In this post-apocalyptic driving/racing game you must travel to various towns delivering medicine, while
			on your way to a missile base which houses a rocket that can save the world.

			While driving through the 32 levels, you'll meet countless enemies who want to stop you from achieving your
			goal. Your car boasts many weapons to help you out, including dynamite, rockets, oil slicks, smoke screens,
			and machine guns. You can also upgrade your vehicle within the city shops. Upgrading your gas tank provides
			better mileage while upgrading your bumper protects you during collisions.
			A password feature let's you continue where you left off.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Fight Night (USA)">
		<description>Fight Night (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Food Fight (USA)">
		<description>Food Fight (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Galaga (USA)">
		<description>Galaga (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Hat Trick (USA)">
		<description>Hat Trick (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Ikari Warriors (USA)">
		<description>Ikari Warriors (USA)</description>
		<year>1989</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>You are a member of those elite combat specialists, the Ikari Warriors. Your buddy and you are on a
			special mission behind enemy lines, and you've been sleeping, eating, and breathing jungle combat for the
			last two weeks. Your tired, but that never affect your razor-sharp judgement and your will to survive.

			Your main weapons are machine guns, grenades, and your own cunning in the face of danger. Sometimes you'll
			have a tank at your disposal, which comes in handy when enemy fire is particularly brutal.

			You move swiftly through the jungle, wading through rivers and resting from time to time with the ruins of
			bombed-out buildings. You're turning out of ammunition and grenades but you know the battle can't last
			forever. Sooner or later, one side is going to emerge victorious. Let's just hope it's yours!</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Impossible Mission (USA)">
		<description>Impossible Mission (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Jinks (USA)">
		<description>Jinks (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Joust (USA)">
		<description>Joust (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Williams</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.65</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>In Joust, players take control of a knight with a lance who rides their flying ostrich (or stork, for
			Player 2) to do battle against computer-controlled evil knights who ride atop vultures.

			Players must flap their steed's wings to hit the enemy from a higher jousting point to destroy the vulture
			and its rider. Once the enemy has been hit, an egg falls to one of the platforms below. The heroic knights
			must destroy the eggs before they hatch and release new and increasingly more difficult knights. The three
			strengths of enemy knights are Bounder (red knight), Hunter (white knight), and Shadow Lord (blue knight).
			These enemy knights are not the only challenge to be found in the game. Players must also contend with
			crumbling platforms, lava trolls who attempt to pull knights into the fire, and the dreaded "unbeatable"(?)
			pterodactyl.

			The game was novel for its time for being one of the few two-player simultaneous games in the arcade.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Karateka (USA)">
		<description>Karateka (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Kung-Fu Master (USA)">
		<description>Kung-Fu Master (USA)</description>
		<year>1987</year>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>A conversion of the arcade game of the same name, which itself is loosely based on a movie, Kung-Fu
			Master is a side scrolling action game for one or two players, who alternate turns.

			Mr. X has captured the pickpocket Sylvia and it is up to Thomas, a kung-fu master who owns a restaurant, to
			get her back. She is located on the top floor of Mr. X's castle and Thomas will need to fight his way to the
			top. Of course, this won't be easy as each floor has many opponents to get past and a floor boss at the end
			of each level.

			Thomas is able to move left and right, jump, duck, and punch and kick. Enemy projectiles such as knives can
			be kicked in the air to rebound them towards the enemy. On the top floor resides Mr. X himself.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Mario Bros. (USA)">
		<description>Mario Bros. (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.65</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Mario and Luigi, the best plumbers in the world, have a real job on their hands. A host of characters
			have taken over the sewers, and the brothers must clear them out of the pipes.

			The platform puzzle which first introduced Luigi to the world has both single and multiplayer action with
			two differing game types, but with the same objective.
			Crabs, turtles and fighter flies must be cleared out by jumping underneath the platform they sit on, then
			kicking them away. Each level is cleared when a set number of coins is collected.

			For the two player mode, the first to collect the set amount of coins wins.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Mat Mania Challenge (USA)">
		<description>Mat Mania Challenge (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Mean 18 Ultimate Golf (USA)">
		<description>Mean 18 Ultimate Golf (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Meltdown (USA)">
		<description>Meltdown (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Midnight Mutants (USA)">
		<description>Midnight Mutants (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Motor Psycho (USA)">
		<description>Motor Psycho (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Ms. Pac-Man (USA)">
		<description>Ms. Pac-Man (USA)</description>
		<year>1982</year>
		<developer>General Computer Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>In 1982, a sequel to the incredibly popular Pac-Man was introduced in the form of his girlfriend, Ms.
			Pac-Man. This sequel continued on the "eat the dots/avoid the ghosts" gameplay of the original game, but
			added new features to keep the title fresh.

			Like her boyfriend, Ms. Pac-Man attempts to clear four various and challenging mazes filled with dots and
			ever-moving bouncing fruit while avoiding Inky, Blinky, Pinky and Sue, each with their own personalities and
			tactics. One touch from any of these ghosts means a loss of life for Ms. Pac-Man.

			Ms. Pac-Man can turn the tables on her pursuers by eating one of the four Energizers located within the
			maze. During this time, the ghosts turn blue, and Ms. Pac-Man can eat them for bonus points (ranging from
			200, 400, 800 and 1600, progressively). The Energizer power only lasts for a limited amount of time, as the
			ghost's eyes float back to their center box, and regenerate to chase after Ms. Pac-Man again.

			Survive a few rounds of gameplay, and the player will be treated to humorous intermissions showing the
			growing romantic relationship between Pac-Man and Ms. Pac-Man, leading all the way up to the arrival of
			"Junior".</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Ninja Golf (USA)">
		<description>Ninja Golf (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="One-on-One Basketball (USA)">
		<description>One-on-One Basketball (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pete Rose Baseball (USA)">
		<description>Pete Rose Baseball (USA)</description>
		<year>2002</year>
		<developer>Absolute Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Absolute Entertainment</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<story>This baseball game licenses former Cincinnati Reds player Pete Rose. It allows the player to play every
			position on the field. Different batting and pitching styles are available.

			It has digitized voice and sound, and provides a variety of play options including One or Two-player action,
			season play or exhibition. In a somewhat ahead-of-its-time move, eight different perspectives are offered.

			There are also some team management capabilities, as you select and order your team, and hire new players.
			This can run over ten seasons, making for one of the first Career modes.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Planet Smashers (USA)">
		<description>Planet Smashers (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pole Position II (USA)">
		<description>Pole Position II (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Rampage (USA)">
		<description>Rampage (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="RealSports Baseball (USA)">
		<description>RealSports Baseball (USA)</description>
		<year>1982</year>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.4</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Baseball is an action game which can be played by two players or one player against the computer. The
			game allows you to bunt the ball or try for a homerun, steal bases, and throw several types of pitches from
			a fast ball to a curve ball. Several game variations are included which allow you to select whether the home
			or visiting team is at bat first, and whether or not a player can swing only at pitches that are a strike,
			or they can swing at any pitch.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Robotron - 2084 (USA)">
		<description>Robotron - 2084 (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Scrapyard Dog (USA)">
		<description>Scrapyard Dog (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Sentinel (Europe)">
		<description>Sentinel (Europe)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Summer Games (USA)">
		<description>Summer Games (USA)</description>
		<year>1987</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>Epyx</publisher>
		<score>0.3</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<story>Summer Games allows up to eight players to compete in a series of summer themed Olympic events. The
			gameplay is similar to the other entries in Epyx "games" series. Each player can choose a country to
			represent, and then takes turns competing in various events to see who will win the gold medal! The game
			allows you to compete in all of the events sequentially, choose a few events, choose just one event, or
			practice an event. The events available vary slightly depending on the platform, and may include:

			1. Pole vault
			2. Platform diving
			3. 4x400 meter relay
			4. 100 meter dash
			5. Gymnastics
			6. Freestyle swimming
			7. Skeet shooting
			8. 100 meter freestyle
			9. Rowing</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Super Huey UH-IX (USA)">
		<description>Super Huey UH-IX (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Super Skateboardin' (USA)">
		<description>Super Skateboardin' (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Tank Command (USA)">
		<description>Tank Command (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Title Match Pro Wrestling (USA)">
		<description>Title Match Pro Wrestling (USA)</description>
		<year>1987</year>
		<developer>Absolute Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Absolute Entertainment</publisher>
		<score>0.35</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>The screams of the crowd shake the arena as the Title Belt contenders circle one another. Mad Dog makes
			the first move smashing his fists into Skin Head's chest who gasps for air, then retaliates with a shin
			cracking kick.

			Mad Dog growls and grabbing from behind drags Skin Head across the ring whipping him around in an airplane
			spin; letting go so he flies into the ropes and bounces back to meet Mad Dog's concrete forearm across his
			neck... a perfectly executed clothesline.

			Wasting no time Mad Dog elbow drops him. Skin Head's face winces in pain as he fights his way up and
			staggers to his corner to tag his partner in.

			Big Chief takes the tag, grabs Mad Dog lifting him over his head and body slams him into the mat. Mad Dog's
			stunned, he's not getting up.

			Big Chief, looking for the pin, climbs the ropes for a dive. As he lunges into the air, Mad Dog scrambles to
			his feet and Big Chief's sweaty red skinned body splatters on the empty mat.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Tomcat - The F-14 Fighter Simulator (USA)">
		<description>Tomcat - The F-14 Fighter Simulator (USA)</description>
		<year>1988</year>
		<developer>Absolute Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Absolute Entertainment</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>To be born with wings...

			Become a F-14 Naval Aviator undergoing seek and destroy missions while dodging and gunning enemy bogeys in
			deadly dogfights with your 20mm cannon and air-to-air missiles.

			You cockpit comes with state of the art technology, courtesy of the U.S. Air Force: Display and main
			computer, Bogey Alert Indicator, G-Force Indicator, Electronic Counter Measures, and a Cannon Overheat
			Indicator (yes, it can overheat!)...and if your feeling up to it, give the ol'bird a boost to Mach 1.0!

			The gameplay like other simulation games consists of taking off, flying, combat and landing. Though most of
			the gameplay focuses around dogfighting with enemy bogeys (dodging missiles). In addition to that, there are
			also night-flying missions that add difficulty due to limited vision.

			Taking off and landing however, also required additional skill as your doing it on the USS Enterprise (No
			relation to Star Trek), not on your standard airstrip. Pay attention to the F.D. officer as your preparing
			to take off (since he's the boss when it comes to this stuff...and try no to run over him...yet).

			Your weaponry consists of a M 61 Machine Gun and 3 different AIM Missiles (AIM 7, 9, 54) each packed with 15
			missiles (that's a lot of missiles!).

			After each mission you will receive a Mission Rating which is based on your flying skill, number of bogey
			kill and number of weapons fired.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Touchdown Football (USA)">
		<description>Touchdown Football (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Tower Toppler (USA)">
		<description>Tower Toppler (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Water Ski (USA)">
		<description>Water Ski (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Winter Games (USA)">
		<description>Winter Games (USA)</description>
		<year>1987</year>
		<developer>Action Graphics</developer>
		<publisher>Epyx</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
		<story>WINTER GAMES is a series of seven exciting competitive events. Up to eight players can enter this
			international contest, each choosing a country for which to compete (no two players can choose the same
			nation to represent).

			The object is to see your country come out on top. You'll compete in pure speed events like skating and in
			speed-and-control events like slalom, biathlon, bobsled and luge. You'll test your skill against competitors
			in distance and style events like ski jumping and hot dog skiing. You'll win by scoring the fastest time or
			by earning the most points. And the nation that wins the most events takes home the gold medal!</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Xenophobe (USA)">
		<description>Xenophobe (USA)</description>
		<year>1990</year>
		<developer>Bally Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Xenos. The very name strikes fear into every colonist's heart. A distress call is received from space
			stations orbiting your homeworld, then silence. A single ship escapes, piloted by a battered man who tells
			the tale of pods that hatch into acid-spitting Xenos.

			A small band of engineers has been dispatched to combat the Xeno threat before it takes over all the space
			stations and, eventually, your homeworld. Assemble your band of engineers and fight the Xenos on each
			station, striving to either clear it or abandon it. You start out with a standard issue laser, but can pick
			up additiona weapons as you find them, including Phasers, Lightning Rifles, Poofer guns, and bombs.

			Xenophobe was originally an arcade coin-op by Bally/Midway, released in 1987. Gameplay premise and setting
			is heavily inspired/influenced by the movie Aliens.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Xevious (USA)">
		<description>Xevious (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
</menu>