<?xml version="1.0"?>
<menu>
	<game name="Activision Decathlon, The (USA)">
		<description>Activision Decathlon, The (USA)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
		<story>The Activision Decathlon is a series of Olympic games similar to the Epyx games series. Up to four
			players can compete in the ten different events of a real-life decathlon, either in sequence or
			individually. Included are the 100-meter dash, long jump, shot put, high jump, 400-meter race, 110-meter
			hurdles, discus throw, pole vault, javelin throw, and 1500-meter race.

			The flat running events involve simple joystick waggling, which must be balanced with accurately-timed
			button presses to clear the hurdles - hitting them or breaking stride causes a loss of momentum and thus
			time. For jumping and throwing events, you must build momentum by waggling and then press the button to
			throw or jump at what you feel is the appropriate moment.

			For each event, points are earned based on how well you do (this can be based on your running time, or how
			far you throw the javelin or discus, etc...), and the player with the most points at the end of the
			decathlon wins the gold medal.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Astro Chase (USA)">
		<description>Astro Chase (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Atari PAM - Pete's Test (USA)">
		<description>Atari PAM - Pete's Test (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Atari PAM Diagnostics (USA) (v2.3)">
		<description>Atari PAM Diagnostics (USA) (v2.3)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Atari PAM System Test (USA) (v1.02)">
		<description>Atari PAM System Test (USA) (v1.02)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Ballblazer (USA)">
		<description>Ballblazer (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Beamrider (USA)">
		<description>Beamrider (USA)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<score>0.65</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Beamrider is a 3-D arcade action game. You control a beam riding spaceship on a mission to clear 99
			sectors of space from hostile aliens. The spaceship is located at the bottom of the screen and it can only
			stop on one of five beams. You are armed with both lasers and torpedoes; torpedoes are more powerful and can
			destroy more enemies compared to lasers, however you only get three per level. To complete a sector, you
			need to destroy fifteen white flying saucers. After all saucers are destroyed, the sector sentinel passes by
			which can be destroyed for extra points. Each even number sector up until sector 16 will add a new type of
			enemy to deal with. These additional enemies will just try to slow your mission, though, only the saucers
			need to be destroyed to advance. Occassionally a rejeuvinator will appear; if this is collected, you can
			earn an extra life. But be careful, because if you accidentally shoot the rejeuvinator it will turn into an
			enemy!</story>
	</game>
	<game name="BerZerk (USA)">
		<description>BerZerk (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Blue Print (USA)">
		<description>Blue Print (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Bounty Bob Strikes Back! (USA)">
		<description>Bounty Bob Strikes Back! (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Buck Rogers - Planet of Zoom (USA)">
		<description>Buck Rogers - Planet of Zoom (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>It's the 25th century. You are Buck Rogers fighting the battle of Planet Zoom. This is a race against
			death. Your ultimate and most powerful enemy is the deadly MOTHER SHIP!

			There are 16 levels of increasing difficulty - each with four rounds of challenging space combat. Before you
			meet the MOTHER SHIP, your pilot skills and nerve are tested against deadly ELECTRON POSTS, ALIEN SAUCERS
			and smashing SPACE HOPPERS. This is a battle of speed, accuracy and endurance. Your time consumption is
			crucial to your survival.

			If you deplete your time you lose one of your five fighter ships. The faster you fly, the sooner you'll get
			to the MOTHER SHIP, allowing yourself more time to destroy it. You begin with a full time line when you
			destroy the MOTHER SHIP.

			Be aggressive but don't be reckless. This is do or die cosmic combat and it's the MOTHER SHIP or YOU!
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Carol Shaw's River Raid (USA)">
		<description>Carol Shaw's River Raid (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Centipede (USA)">
		<description>Centipede (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Choplifter! (USA)">
		<description>Choplifter! (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Congo Bongo (USA)">
		<description>Congo Bongo (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>0.35</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>An extremely faithful port of the famous jump-n-run platform arcade game. Run, jump, and climb your way
			through a dangerous jungle while avoiding various animals and projectiles.

			Includes the introductory animations and features the arcade version's sliding screen transitions.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Countermeasure (USA)">
		<description>Countermeasure (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="David Crane's Pitfall II - Lost Caverns (USA)">
		<description>David Crane's Pitfall II - Lost Caverns (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Defender (USA)">
		<description>Defender (USA)</description>
		<year>1981</year>
		<developer>Sears</developer>
		<publisher>Williams</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Defender put players in charge of a ship sent to protect mankind from wave after wave of attacking alien
			forces.

			Armed with "smart bombs", and the ability to use hyperspace to move quickly around the planet, the player
			ship must fight against Bombers, Pods, Swarmers, Baiters, and Landers - that can capture the humanoids and
			transform them into deadly and relentless Mutants. Fail to save the humanoids from freefall or Mutant
			transformation, and the planet is destroyed.

			Eugene Jarvis' Defender has been widely regarded as one of the most popular and addictive space shooters of
			the early 1980's</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Dig Dug (USA)">
		<description>Dig Dug (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Dig Dug is a 1-2 player arcade game in which you have to use your shovel to dig your way through the
			earth. Stopping you from doing this are two monsters, called Pooka and Fygar, who will continually chase you
			around. The only weapon that you carry is an air pump, which you can use to inflate the monsters to the
			point where they explode. (if you start to inflate them but stop doing so, the monsters will get turned back
			to their normal selves.) Furthermore, rocks are scattered throughout the earth, and you can use these rocks
			to squash them. If the monsters do not find you for several seconds, they will eventually get turned into
			ghosts, which are able to walk through the earth. They are invincible and cannot be killed. From time to
			time, vegetables will appear in the center, and you can get these for points.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Dreadnaught Factor, The (USA)">
		<description>Dreadnaught Factor, The (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Frogger (USA)">
		<description>Frogger (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Your task in this arcade conversion is to guide a frog across a treacherous road and river, and to safety
			at the top of the screen. Both these sections are fraught with a variety of hazards, each of which will kill
			the frog and cost you a life if contact is made.

			The road is full of cars and trucks, at variable speeds. The river water itself is fatal, as are the snakes
			which hover within on later levels. Frogger must use the arrangement of logs, turtles (which are only there
			for a short time) and alligators (but stay away form their faces), and then jump into one of the open
			home-cells, ideally one containing a fly for extra points. Once all holes have been filled, you move onto
			the next, harder, level.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Frogger II - Threeedeep! (USA)">
		<description>Frogger II - Threeedeep! (USA)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Parker Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>In Frogger II, you need to guide your frog to safety in three different locations. Starting out
			underwater, reach the top of the pond while avoiding dangerous alligators and fish (you can ride a turtle
			for safety!). Once on top of the pond, hop across logs, birds, and even a whale to the life preserver
			trailing behind a tugboat. In the third location you have to hop across a flock of birds to reach a cloud at
			the top of the screen. Each frog has a time limit to safely reach one of the homes on each of the three
			screens. You move on to the next level when a frog has safely reached each of the homes on all screens.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Galaxian (USA)">
		<description>Galaxian (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Galaxian is a shoot 'em up in which the player is at the bottom of the screen, with an arrangement of
			aliens at the top. The player moves left and right to aim at an alien, then shoots a bullet up the screen,
			and the alien it hits is killed. The aliens are classed as Drones, Emissaries, Hornets and Commanders, with
			those higher up the screen scoring more points when destroyed. At set intervals an enemy will move down the
			screen towards you, escorting a bomber, which is a moment of high danger. Clear a wave and another is
			generated.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Gorf (USA)">
		<description>Gorf (USA)</description>
		<year>1982</year>
		<developer>Bally Midway</developer>
		<publisher>CBS Electronics</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Gorf is a game similar to Space Invaders, alien vessels approach closer and closer in their threatening
			row formation.

			The game itself consists of four levels:

			1. The first level has you behind a defensive shield, defending against an alien attack. The level is a
			top-down view, with your ship &amp; shield on one side and the aliens on the other side;

			The second level is similar to the first, only your defensive shield is gone, and the enemies tend to swoop
			down over the level as opposed to those row formations. Bonus ships also tend to appear in this level;

			The third level is a change, and has you entering hyperspace. Your only goal is to survive to the end of
			your journey. The viewpoint switches from a top-down view to a behind-the-ship view and in effect you are
			heading "towards" your destination. Alien vessels flying in circular formation try to stop you;

			The fourth and final level is similar to the first again, with some key differences. You do not fight a wave
			of enemies, but a single one. A mothership with a glowing weak spot. Hitting the weak spot will instantly
			destroy it. The mothership also has that same shield that was yours in the first level.

			Finishing the game increases your rank and starts the game over at level 1 with a faster game speed for more
			challenge.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Gremlins (USA)">
		<description>Gremlins (USA)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>This game is based on the Steven Spielberg movie of the same name but is different than the other
			versions.

			In this version, on the first screen, Mogwai are jumping from the roof to get at hamburgers on the ground.
			You, as Billy, must catch them before the hit the ground. If you get them all, it is off to the next,
			faster, level. If you miss eight, then you go to a shooting screen.

			On the shooting screen, gremlins are approaching from the distance. You must shoot them before they reach
			you. If one reaches you, you lose a life. After they are all dead, it is back to the first screen at a
			faster level. In later levels, puddles of water will divide the gremlins in two.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Gyruss (USA)">
		<description>Gyruss (USA)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Parker Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Shoot-'Em-Up</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>The entire solar system is being attacked by the vicious Gyrusians, and it's up to you to save the day!
			You will need to fly your spaceship to each of the nine planets and then clear three stages of enemies to
			rid that planet of the Gyrusians. You start the game with a single canon, and can gain a double canon after
			shooting a power up satelite. After clearing each planet, there is another bonus stage where additional
			weapons and bonus points can be collected. Gyruss is an arcade action shooter, however instead of piloting
			your spaceship horizontally or vertically, you move in a circle around the perimeter of the screen. The NES
			version of Gyruss adds to the original arcade version additional music, additional weapons, new enemies, and
			a large boss at the end of each level.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="H.E.R.O. (USA)">
		<description>H.E.R.O. (USA)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>There is trouble in the mines! Volcanic activity has trapped numerous miners, and it is your job to save
			them. As Roderick Hero, you need to make your way through the dangerous mineshaft avoiding the dangerous
			creatures and lava, and find out where the miners are located before you run out of energy. To help on your
			mission, Roderick Hero has several useful types of equipment. A prop pack will allow you to hover and fly
			around the mineshaft and (hopefully) avoid the many dangers within. Your helmet features a short range
			microlaser beam which can be used to destroy the bats, spiders, snakes, and other creatures you'll encounter
			in the mines. From time to time, your path through the mine may be blocked by stone or lava walls. You begin
			each mission with six sticks of dynamite which can be used to destroy these obstacles (be careful you don't
			blow yourself up, though!) If you run out of dynamite, your laser beam can also be used to destroy the
			walls, though this will take longer and use up more energy. As the levels progress, the mine shaft will
			become longer and more maze-like, creatures will more frequently block the path, and lava walls and pools
			will appear which are dangerous to the touch.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="James Bond 007 (USA)">
		<description>James Bond 007 (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>On Time Software</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<score>0.55</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>In James Bond 007 you control James Bond in his multi purpose craft. This craft can travel on both land
			and sea, can jump over danger, or fire at enemies on the many different levels. Each horizontally scrolling
			level in the game is loosely based on a different James Bond movie. The levels included are Diamonds Are
			Forever, The Spy Who Loved Me, Moonraker, and For Your Eyes Only. Each level has a variety of enemies trying
			to destroy you, and a unique goal that must be accomplished to continue on (for example, you may have to
			land on a hidden oil rig to stop Seraffino, or find Stromberg's undersea laboratory and destroy it). If you
			can complete all the missions, you win the game! Good luck, Mr. Bond.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Joust (USA)">
		<description>Joust (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Williams</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.65</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>In Joust, players take control of a knight with a lance who rides their flying ostrich (or stork, for
			Player 2) to do battle against computer-controlled evil knights who ride atop vultures.

			Players must flap their steed's wings to hit the enemy from a higher jousting point to destroy the vulture
			and its rider. Once the enemy has been hit, an egg falls to one of the platforms below. The heroic knights
			must destroy the eggs before they hatch and release new and increasingly more difficult knights. The three
			strengths of enemy knights are Bounder (red knight), Hunter (white knight), and Shadow Lord (blue knight).
			These enemy knights are not the only challenge to be found in the game. Players must also contend with
			crumbling platforms, lava trolls who attempt to pull knights into the fire, and the dreaded "unbeatable"(?)
			pterodactyl.

			The game was novel for its time for being one of the few two-player simultaneous games in the arcade.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Jungle Hunt (USA)">
		<description>Jungle Hunt (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Taito</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Jungle Hunt offers four unique adventure experiences, which repeat with greater difficulty once all four
			have been survived. If you don't survive these adventures, you will not only lose your own life but that of
			the lovely Penelope, who has been captured by cannibals!

			The first part challenges your Tarzan skills - can you swing on the vines without plummeting to your doom?
			The second part pits you against a whole bunch of nasty crocodiles in a mighty river. Fortunately, you have
			a knife to fight back with. Don't forget to go up for air! In the third part, you face a battle against
			oncoming boulders of varying sizes and physics. Once you've cleared all these treacherous hazards, you still
			must confront the dreaded cannibal, who is armed with a wicked spear. Can you get past him and save the
			lovely Penelope?

			Gameplay involves much strategic jumping and knife play (in the river/crocodile phase). The view is always a
			side view, much like Pitfall! and later platform games.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="K-Razy Shoot-Out (USA)">
		<description>K-Razy Shoot-Out (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Kaboom! (USA)">
		<description>Kaboom! (USA)</description>
		<year>1981</year>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>The mad bomber is on the loose! As he races back and forth at the top of the screen, you need to catch
			the bombs he drops in buckets of water. One point is earned for each bomb caught, but miss one of the bombs,
			and Kaboom! As the levels progress, the mad bomber will move faster and faster and drop more and more bombs.
			You start the game with three buckets, and lose one each time a bomb is missed. The game ends when all of
			your water buckets are gone.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Kangaroo (USA)">
		<description>Kangaroo (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.55</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Baby Roo has been kidnapped by monkeys, and it's up to Mama Roo to come to the rescue! Your kangaroo
			starts out at the bottom of the screen. You need to guide the kangaroo up the various ladders and platforms
			to the top where Baby Roo is being held captive. The monkeys will be trying to stop you by throwing or
			dropping apples and knocking you off the platforms. Your kangaroo has boxing gloves, however, and can knock
			out the monkeys with a single punch! Along the way various types of fruit can be collected to earn bonus
			points.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Keystone Kapers (USA)">
		<description>Keystone Kapers (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>The notorious thief Harry Hooligan is on the loose! You play the part of Officer Keystone Kelly, sent in
			to capture Harry. Harry is trapped in a four story mall, and is running as fast as he can to reach the exit
			at the top. Your job is to catch up to him and send him to prison. You will need to use either the
			escalators at the end of each floor, or the elevator in the middle to go from floor to floor. The escalators
			may be further away, but the elevator moves pretty slowly so you will need to decide which route will be
			faster in getting you closer to your goal. If Harry can make it to the top before you catch him, you will
			have to retry that level. Harry has no intention of letting you catch him easily, and is hurling everything
			he can find in an attempt to slow you down. Shopping carts, bouncing balls, biplanes, and more will all be
			flying past on the screen and will either slow you down or send you back to the beginning if you get hit. As
			the levels progress, Harry will run faster and faster, and more objects will be tossed your way to duck and
			jump over.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Mario Bros. (USA)">
		<description>Mario Bros. (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.65</score>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Mario and Luigi, the best plumbers in the world, have a real job on their hands. A host of characters
			have taken over the sewers, and the brothers must clear them out of the pipes.

			The platform puzzle which first introduced Luigi to the world has both single and multiplayer action with
			two differing game types, but with the same objective.
			Crabs, turtles and fighter flies must be cleared out by jumping underneath the platform they sit on, then
			kicking them away. Each level is cleared when a set number of coins is collected.

			For the two player mode, the first to collect the set amount of coins wins.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="MegaMania (USA)">
		<description>MegaMania (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Meteorites (USA)">
		<description>Meteorites (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Miner 2049er Starring Bounty Bob (USA)">
		<description>Miner 2049er Starring Bounty Bob (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Missile Command (USA)">
		<description>Missile Command (USA)</description>
		<year>1981</year>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Aliens from the planet of Krytol are attacking your cities!! As the commander of a missile base, it is
			your responsibility to defend them. A variety of enemy weapons and planes will be incoming trying to destroy
			the six cities at the bottom of the screen. You need to fire missiles to destroy the incoming weapons. If
			anything gets through, one of your cities could be destroyed. When all of the cities are gone, the game is
			over. On each level you have a limited amount of ammo, so make sure most (if not all) of your shots are
			accurate or you could run out of ammo and leave your cities at risk! As the levels progress, there are more
			and more enemy weapons to destroy which come in at an increasingly faster rate.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Montezuma's Revenge - Featuring Panama Joe (USA)">
		<description>Montezuma's Revenge - Featuring Panama Joe (USA)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Parker Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>You play as a treasure hunter named Panama Joe, whose goal is to find an ancient treasure hidden by Aztec
			warrior deep inside catacombs. But beware, the catacombs are a large maze inhabited by monsters. Bouncing
			and rolling skulls, dancing spiders, disappearing and re-appearing chains and tons of fire await you. You'll
			have to find many keys and unlock doors in order to reach your goal. Panama Joe can jump and climb ladders,
			but doesn't have much to offer in terms of combat. That's why the monsters in the game should be avoided: a
			collision with an enemy leads to a premature death.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Moon Patrol (USA)">
		<description>Moon Patrol (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>The moon is under attack from a horde of aliens, and you must stop them in your armed buggy. Drive along
			the surface shooting the aliens and avoiding their bullets. The surface is not flat, there are craters and
			rocks to avoid contact with, and landmines on the surface. Flying saucers create new craters when they
			crash. The 25 restart points are letter-coded.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Mountain King (USA)">
		<description>Mountain King (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>VSS, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>CBS Electronics</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Deep within a multi platformed diamond mine is a valuable crown. Your goal is to locate and retrieve the
			crown, then make it to the top of the mine alive! There are several steps that need to be completed before
			you can retrieve the crown. First you need to collect enough diamonds to earn 1,000 points. After you have
			enough points, you need to locate the flame spirit which is hidden somewhere within the mine. Since the mine
			is rather dark, you carry a flashlight with you which can be used to locate objects (such as treasure chests
			full of diamonds and the flame spirit.) Once you have the flame spirit, you need to find the entrance to the
			temple the crown is in. Offer the flame spirit to the skull spirit guarding the entrance, and you can get in
			and take the crown. Once you have the crown, you need to make it to the top of the mine before time runs
			out. To make this task more challenging, numerous cave bats fly around which can steal the crown. If this
			happens, you need to begin again! At the very bottom of the mine is a deadly spider; if you're not careful
			while exploring this region of the mine, you could become caught in it's web and be eaten. Each level has a
			time limit, and the more levels you complete the shorter the time limit becomes!</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Mr. Do!'s Castle (USA)">
		<description>Mr. Do!'s Castle (USA)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>Parker Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<score>0.75</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Mr. Do!'s Castle is an action platform game which has you in a castle consisting of several floors, each
			of which contain a variety of blocks. You control Mr. Do! the clown who has a hammer which can be used to
			knock out the blocks in the floor. Wandering throughout the castle are deadly unicorns which are constantly
			trying to catch you. Your goal is to earn as many points as possible and to progress through the
			increasingly difficult castles.

			There are two ways to complete a castle; you can either destroy all of the deadly unicorns by crushing them
			with blocks, or you can knock out all of the blocks which have a cherry symbol on them. In addition to the
			cherry blocks, there are three blocks with a key. If all three key blocks are knocked out, the door on the
			roof of the castle unlocks. If you make it to the door, all of the unicorns will temporarily become harmless
			and will contain a letter. If you hit a letter unicorn, you will earn a letter in the word EXTRA. Spell the
			complete word, and you will earn an extra life.

			The last type of block you'll encounter has a skull on it. If you knock out two skull blocks, all of the
			blocks between them will also be knocked out and replaced with a bridge. As the castles progress, the castle
			layout will become trickier and the unicorns become faster and more numerous.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Ms. Pac-Man (USA)">
		<description>Ms. Pac-Man (USA)</description>
		<year>1982</year>
		<developer>General Computer Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>In 1982, a sequel to the incredibly popular Pac-Man was introduced in the form of his girlfriend, Ms.
			Pac-Man. This sequel continued on the "eat the dots/avoid the ghosts" gameplay of the original game, but
			added new features to keep the title fresh.

			Like her boyfriend, Ms. Pac-Man attempts to clear four various and challenging mazes filled with dots and
			ever-moving bouncing fruit while avoiding Inky, Blinky, Pinky and Sue, each with their own personalities and
			tactics. One touch from any of these ghosts means a loss of life for Ms. Pac-Man.

			Ms. Pac-Man can turn the tables on her pursuers by eating one of the four Energizers located within the
			maze. During this time, the ghosts turn blue, and Ms. Pac-Man can eat them for bonus points (ranging from
			200, 400, 800 and 1600, progressively). The Energizer power only lasts for a limited amount of time, as the
			ghost's eyes float back to their center box, and regenerate to chase after Ms. Pac-Man again.

			Survive a few rounds of gameplay, and the player will be treated to humorous intermissions showing the
			growing romantic relationship between Pac-Man and Ms. Pac-Man, leading all the way up to the arrival of
			"Junior".</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pac-Man (USA)">
		<description>Pac-Man (USA)</description>
		<year>1981</year>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<score>0.55</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>One of the most popular and influential games of the 1980's, Pac-Man stars a little, yellow dot-muncher
			who works his way around to clear a maze of the various dots and fruit which inhabit the board.

			Pac-Man's goal is continually challenged by four ghosts: The shy blue ghost Bashful (Inky), the trailing red
			ghost Shadow (Blinky), the fast pink ghost Speedy (Pinky), and the forgetful orange ghost Pokey (Clyde). One
			touch from any of these ghosts means a loss of life for Pac-Man.

			Pac-Man can turn the tables on his pursuers by eating of the four Energizers located within the maze. During
			this time, the ghosts turn blue, and Pac-Man can eat them for bonus points. This only lasts for a limited
			amount of time, as the ghost's eyes float back to their center box, and regenerate to chase after Pac-Man
			again.

			Survive a few rounds of gameplay, and be treated to humorous intermissions between Pac-Man and the ghosts.
		</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pengo (USA)">
		<description>Pengo (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Go skating on thin ice! Race Pengo, the lovable penguin, around a frozen lake. Rearrange huge blocks of
			ice. Your goal: line up three jewel-embedded blocks for dazzling points! Your enemies: SNO-BEES! Their touch
			puts you in deep freeze.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pitfall! (USA)">
		<description>Pitfall! (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Pole Position (USA)">
		<description>Pole Position (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.65</score>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Pole Position is the conversion of the arcade racing game. Enter the Grand Prix, race against other
			racing cars to achieve the highest score possible in the shortest amount of time.

			Before the player can enter the Grand Prix, the player must first qualify by competing in the Qualifying Lap
			within 73 seconds or less. If the player however, does not qualify in the Qualifying Lap, the player may
			continue to race until the Race Timer runs after 90 seconds. The player will score 50 point per 5 meters and
			additionally 50 points for every racing car passed. When the time runs out - Game Over. The player will have
			to restart the Qualifying Lap.

			Qualifying will enable the player to start in one of the eight available positions. The faster the lap time
			was, the better the starting position in addition to bonus score points. The number one starting position,
			is the Pole Position.

			During the Grand Prix, the player will compete against the Race Timer as well as against other racing cars.
			If the player fails to beat the Race Timer in any lap, the player drops out of the race - Game Over.
			Completing the race by reaching finishing line will grant the player 200 points per each second left on the
			Race Timer, bonus score for distance covered, and passing bonus points.

			Scoring

			1. Every 5 meters driven: 50 points
			Passing Car Bonus: 50 points per racing car
			Time Bonus: 200 points per second left on the Race Timer

			Positions

			1. Pole Position - Lap Time: 58"50 seconds - 4,000 points
			2nd Position - Lap Time: 60"00 seconds - 2,000 points
			3rd Position - Lap Time: 62"00 seconds - 1,400 points
			4th Position - Lap Time: 64"00 seconds - 1,000 points
			5th Position - Lap Time: 66"00 seconds - 800 points
			6th Position - Lap Time: 68"00 seconds - 600 points
			7th Position - Lap Time: 70"00 seconds - 400 points
			8th Position - Lap Time: 73"00 seconds - 200 points</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Popeye (USA)">
		<description>Popeye (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<score>0.5</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Popeye is a conversion of the arcade action/platform game. As Popeye, you are trying to win Olive Oyl's
			love! She is at the top of the screen dropping tokens of her love, and you need to collect them before they
			hit the ground. After you have collected the required number of items, you can move on to the next, more
			difficult level. There are many obstacles trying to stop you from completing your task, though! Brutus
			wanders around the screen and is constantly trying to catch you. If you collect a can of spinach, you can
			temporarily knock him out, otherwise Brutus will knock you out. Other objects such as bottles or birds are
			also flying around the screen and will cause you to lose one of your lives if you are hit. Each level
			features a different layout of platforms and ladders, and will have you collecting different items as they
			float towards the bottom of the screen!</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Q-bert (USA)">
		<description>Q-bert (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Western Technologies</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Q*bert is an isometric platform game with puzzle elements where the player controls the titular
			protagonist from a third-person perspective. Q*bert starts each game at the top of a pyramid of cubes, and
			moves by jumping diagonally from cube to cube. Landing on a cube causes it to change color, and changing
			every cube to the target color allows the player to progress to the next stage.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="QIX (USA)">
		<description>QIX (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Quest for Quintana Roo (USA)">
		<description>Quest for Quintana Roo (USA)</description>
		<year>1984</year>
		<developer>VSS, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sunrise Software</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>You are Yucatan Sam on a quest to explore the temple of Quintana Roo. Your goal is to find the vault
			which is hidden somewhere within and return with the treasure that is inside. You begin your quest outside
			the temple; climb your way up the side of the temple in order to get inside. Poisonous snakes and deadly
			lightning bolts will block your progress here. Once inside the temple, you have a limited air supply so you
			need to explore quickly. Hidden in various rooms of the temple are numerous keys which are needed to unlock
			the vault. The keys and some other useful items are hidden in secret rooms which you need to locate by using
			your trusty pick axe or the flasks of acid you carry. To help figure out which rooms may contain hidden
			objects, you carry a geiger counter with you; the higher the reading, the closer you are to something of
			interest! The rooms you'll be exploring are guarded by snakes, spiders, and even mummies! To deal with these
			enemies you carry a gun, and you can also use the acid flasks against them (ammo is limited, so use it
			wisely). If you are successful in your mission, you may receive a secret code which can be used to begin the
			game at later levels. Good luck!</story>
	</game>
	<game name="RealSports Baseball (USA)">
		<description>RealSports Baseball (USA)</description>
		<year>1982</year>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.4</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Baseball is an action game which can be played by two players or one player against the computer. The
			game allows you to bunt the ball or try for a homerun, steal bases, and throw several types of pitches from
			a fast ball to a curve ball. Several game variations are included which allow you to select whether the home
			or visiting team is at bat first, and whether or not a player can swing only at pitches that are a strike,
			or they can swing at any pitch.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="RealSports Basketball (USA)">
		<description>RealSports Basketball (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="RealSports Football (USA)">
		<description>RealSports Football (USA)</description>
		<year>1982</year>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.4</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>RealSports Football is a one or two-player football simulation played on a horizontal scrolling field,
			with five players on each team. As in real football, the goal is to march down a 100-yard field using a
			combination of passing and running plays. There are three ways to score: crossing the defensive team's goal
			line is a touchdown worth seven points, kicking the ball through the defense's goal post is a field goal
			worth three points, and tackling the ball carrier inside the end zone is a safety worth two points.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="RealSports Soccer (USA)">
		<description>RealSports Soccer (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.3</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>The game is played from an angled overhead point of view of the field which scrolls to follow the action.
			If your team has the ball, you control whichever player is currently dribbling the ball, otherwise you can
			control any one player at a time while the computer controls the rest of your team. Various time lengths can
			be selected for each game, you can kick the ball low, medium or high, and there are throw-ins, corner kicks,
			goal kicks. When playing against the computer several different skill levels are available.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="RealSports Tennis (USA)">
		<description>RealSports Tennis (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.55</score>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Realsports Tennis is a tennis game for two players or one player against the computer. The game follows
			standard tennis rules, and allows you to hit forehand or backhand shots to all areas of the court as well as
			serves and lobs. You can play a game of singles or doubles, and multiple skill levels are included.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Rescue on Fractalus! (USA)">
		<description>Rescue on Fractalus! (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Robotron 2084 (USA)">
		<description>Robotron 2084 (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Space Dungeon (USA)">
		<description>Space Dungeon (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Space Invaders (USA)">
		<description>Space Invaders (USA)</description>
		<year>1980</year>
		<developer>Taito</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Earth is under attack from rows of bomb dropping aliens, and you need to defend it! The rows of aliens
			begin at the top of the screen, and you control a laser cannon at the bottom of the screen. Your goal is to
			earn points by shooting the aliens before they can land. The aliens march back and forth, and each time the
			end of the screen is reached they will drop one row closer to the bottom. Shoot them all, and you move on to
			the next (tougher) level, but if even one of them lands the game is over. From time to time a flying saucer
			will pass by along the top of the screen; shoot this to earn extra points. Just above your laser canon are
			three shields; these can be used to hide from the alien's bombs, but will also block your own shots. You
			begin the game with a limited number of laser canons, and if all of them are bombed the game ends.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Space Shuttle - A Journey Into Space (USA)">
		<description>Space Shuttle - A Journey Into Space (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Star Raiders (USA)">
		<description>Star Raiders (USA)</description>
		<year>1982</year>
		<developer>Atari</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>As the pilot of an interstellar starship, your mission is to destroy all of the Krylon fighters which are
			closing in on your starbases! There are three different types of fighters roaming throughout the galaxy;
			cruisers, fighters, and basestars. With the help of your galactic map, you can find the sectors of the
			galaxy where these fighters are located and then warp there to destroy them. When all of the fighters in a
			sector are destroyed, you can warp to a new location for the next battle. Be sure to keep an eye on your
			starships energy; warping to new locations, being hit by enemy fire, or colliding with an asteroid will
			drain your energy. If you completely run out of energy, your starship will be destroyed, however you can
			warp back to a starbase to refuel at any time. Returning to a starbase will also repair other types of
			damage your starship can receive, such as faulty engines, loss of your shield, and faulty photon torpedoes.
			When all of the Krylon that are visible on your galactic map have been destroyed, you win this round and can
			advance in rank (or even be demoted if you performed poorly on a mission). The games difficulty will
			gradually increase as you rise in rank from ships cook up to captain.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Star Trek - Strategic Operations Simulator (USA)">
		<description>Star Trek - Strategic Operations Simulator (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>SEGA</publisher>
		<score>0.7</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Star Trek: Strategic Operations Simulator is an arcade action game where you take control of the Starship
			Enterprise. Your mission is to save the Federation from NOMAD! Before you get a chance at destroying NOMAD,
			you'll have to battle your way through ten levels (each consisting of multiple rounds). In each round you
			may encounter Klingon fighters, deadly anti-matter saucers, asteroid fields, and deadly meteors, all of
			which are capable of depleting the Enterprises energy. The game ends when your energy supply has completely
			run out. To fight these dangers, the Enterprise is equipped with an unlimited supply of phasers and a
			limited supply of photon torpedoes. Each round also contains one or more starbases; if you dock at a
			starbase, some of your supplies (such as energy and torpedoes) will be replenished. The game is played from
			two points of view; the top of the screen contains a third person view of the Enterprise (along with the
			ships gauges), and on the bottom of the screen is a first person point of view</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Star Wars - Return of the Jedi - Death Star Battle (USA)">
		<description>Star Wars - Return of the Jedi - Death Star Battle (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Parker Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<score>0.55</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>"Death Star Battle" is loosely based on the events of "Star Wars, Part 6: Return of the Jedi". Your task
			is to destroy the Death Star before its construction is finished. You start the task outside the shield
			perimeter of the Death Star. There you'll have to combat different imperial vessels and avoid the death ray
			while waiting for an opportunity to slip through one of the random openings in the energy shield. After
			reaching the Death Star you must reduce its structure up to the point where you can hit the core. In the
			following blow up of the station you must avoid collision with Death Star debris.

			After successful destruction the game will restart with increased difficulty (faster enemies, faster Death
			Star build up, etc).

			Overall difficulty can also be adjusted before starting the game.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Star Wars - The Arcade Game (USA)">
		<description>Star Wars - The Arcade Game (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Parker Brothers</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<score>0.6</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>You're at the controls of LUKE's X-WING FIGHTER, heading straight for the DEATH STAR. Your mission: to
			destroy it before the EMPIRE seeks its revenge on the REBEL base. Lock your sights on attacking TIE FIGHTERS
			and blast them with your proton torpedoes. Race along the DEATH STAR's surface, firing on giant towers.
			Finally, dive full throttle into the DEATH STAR's equatorial trench. You'll need split-second timing to
			avoid all the obstacles as you streak through the trench in search of the main reactor. Hit it and you've
			blown the DEATH STAR out of existence! MAY THE FORCE BE WITH YOU.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Super Breakout (USA)">
		<description>Super Breakout (USA)</description>
		<year>1978</year>
		<developer>Turner, Nick / Shaw, Carol</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.65</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Super Breakout features similar gameplay to the original, but with several new game variations. Your goal
			is to earn as many points as possible by destroying the bricks at the top of the playfield. To do this, you
			need to use the paddle at the bottom of the screen to keep a bouncing ball within the playfield. There are
			four different game variations included. The first is 'Breakout', and plays the same as the original game.

			This leaves three new gameplay concepts. In 'Progressive' the brick walls will slowly drop towards the
			bottom of the screen and the ball moves progressively faster and faster. When there's room, a new layer of
			bricks will appear at the top.

			The other two games add a second paddle. In 'Double Breakout' you have two balls to keep in play and score
			with. In 'Cavity' there is a single ball in play when you start, but two additional balls trapped within the
			bricks. These are freed when their surrounding bricks are destroyed.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Super Cobra (USA)">
		<description>Super Cobra (USA)</description>
		<year>1983</year>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Parker Brothers</publisher>
		<score>0.25</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<story>Super Cobra is a side scrolling shooter based on the arcade game. You're a chopper pilot on a
			surveillance mission in enemy territory; your goal is to make it through the various obstacle courses alive
			and score as many points as possible. Tall buildings, mountains, narrow tunnels, and various enemies (such
			as tanks, rockets, mines, and more) can all get in the way and destroy your chopper if you aren't careful.
			To help defend yourself, the chopper is armed with a machine gun and bombs which can be used to destroy the
			enemy tanks and rockets. To make the task more difficult, your chopper has a limited amount of fuel.
			Throughout the landscapes are fuel tanks; if one of these is shot or bombed, you will be awarded extra fuel.
			As the levels progress, the enemies become more aggressive, fuel becomes more scarce, and the landscape
			becomes trickier to navigate.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Vanguard (USA)">
		<description>Vanguard (USA)</description>
		<year>1982</year>
		<developer>SNK</developer>
		<publisher>Atari</publisher>
		<score>0.8</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Vanguard is an arcade style shooter for one or two players. Your goal is to pilot your spaceship to the
			City of Mystery which is located at the end of a heavily guarded tunnel, and once there destroy the creature
			Gond. The tunnel is broken up into several different zones, called the mountain zone, rainbow zone, stick
			zone, stripe zone, bleak zone, and City of Mystery. Each zone features different types of enemy spaceships
			to deal with, and can scroll either horizontally or vertically. In the mountain zone or stripe zone, you may
			also come across an energy pod marked with an 'E'. If you fly through this, your ship temporarily becomes
			invincible to the deadly cave walls and numerous enemies which are trying to stop you. When not invincible,
			your space ship is equipped with lasers to help destroy enemies. You can fire in four different directions,
			however your speed is decreased when firing. You also need to keep an eye on your fuel gauge; your fuel will
			deplete at a rapid rate, and your ship will crash if it runs out. Fuel is gained each time you destroy an
			enemy, so make sure you destroy as many as you can! When you finally make it through all the various zones
			of the tunnel and defeat Gond, the game will repeat at a more difficult skill level.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Wizard of Wor (USA)">
		<description>Wizard of Wor (USA)</description>
		<year>1982</year>
		<developer>Bally Midway</developer>
		<publisher>CBS Electronics</publisher>
		<score>0.55</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>Wizard of Wor is an arcade shooter played from a top-down point of view.

			The player controls a warrior who is trapped in a dungeon. The goal is to earn as many points as possible by
			shooting the numerous enemy creatures which wander about the maze like corridors. The creatures wander about
			at various speeds, may shoot darts at the player, and some even have the ability to disappear temporarily.
			At the bottom of the screen the player has a radar which can be used to locate creatures that are invisible.

			When the the player completes a maze, a Worluk sometimes appears. This creature moves rapidly and will only
			be on the screen momentarily. If the player destroys the creature before it escapes, the next dungeon will
			become a double score dungeon and all creatures will be worth twice as many points. Occasionally the Wizard
			of Wor himself may appear! He moves quickly and can teleport around the maze. If they destroy him, the
			player will earn a large amount of points.

			The game may be played by one player or two players simultaneously.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Zaxxon (USA)">
		<description>Zaxxon (USA)</description>
		<year>1982</year>
		<developer>SEGA</developer>
		<publisher>Coleco Industries, Inc.</publisher>
		<score>0.55</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<story>The Zaxxon defence system must be destroyed in this isometric-viewed shoot 'em up which was originally
			hugely successful in the arcades. The game has 3 stages, first taking you through Asteroid City, which is
			heavily protected by aircraft, guns and missiles. Many barriers are alarmed, leaving you with limited space
			to progress through, and fire must constantly be dodged.

			Stage two is a space shoot out against hordes of enemy aircraft - those you failed to destroy in the first
			part of the task. Complete this and you reach the final battle with Zaxxon, with the game looping with
			increased difficulty if you can survive the first time. There are 3 distinct skill levels, while controls
			involve using forward to dive and back to climb, in the manner of flight simulation.</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Zenji (USA)">
		<description>Zenji (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
	<game name="Zone Ranger (USA)">
		<description>Zone Ranger (USA)</description>
		<year>NA</year>
		<developer>NA</developer>
		<publisher>NA</publisher>
		<score>NA</score>
		<genre>NA</genre>
		<players>NA</players>
		<story>NA</story>
	</game>
</menu>