<?xml version="1.0"?>
<menu>
    <game name="007 Legends (USA)">
        <description>007 Legends (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Eurocom</developer>
        <publisher>Activision</publisher>
        <score>0.6</score>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <players>2-12</players>
        <story>Taking place after the opening but prior to the events of Skyfall, James Bond is shot and left for dead
            during a botched assignment in Istanbul. As his life hangs in the balance, he begins to remember his
            previous adventures ? foiling Operation Grand Slam, the assault on Piz Gloria, his vendetta against drug
            kingpin Franz Sanchez, his encounter with Gustav Graves, and thwarting billionaire industrialist Hugo Drax's
            plot to kill the entire human race.

            Straight after his return to the present day, Bond realizes that he's still alive. He tracks down Patrice,
            whom he was after in the very beginning of the game, to Shanghai where he stops an assassination plot and
            eliminates the hitman. The game presents a What if? scenario where all of the "classic" Bond adventures have
            taken place during the six-year gap between the storylines of Quantum of Solace and Skyfall.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Adventure Time - Explore the Dungeon Because I Don't Know! (USA)">
        <description>Adventure Time - Explore the Dungeon Because I Don't Know! (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Adventure Time - Finn and Jake Investigations (USA)">
        <description>Adventure Time - Finn and Jake Investigations (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Vicious Cycle Software</developer>
        <publisher>Little Orbit</publisher>
        <score>0.7</score>
        <genre>Puzzle-Game-Casual Game-Adventure</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>What time is it? It's time to crack a case!

            Adventure Time: Finn and Jake Investigations is an all-new, story-driven graphic adventure game. Strange
            stuff is happening in the Land of Ooo (stranger than usual anyway). Luckily, Finn and Jake are on the case.
            This mysterious adventure will put their detective skills to the test as they search for clues, interrogate
            witnesses and piece together the evidence to save the day. They might even have to bust up a few goons along
            the way, but it's nothing that Finn and Jake Investigations can't handle!

            Game Features:nn? Sleuth your way through five cases set in the Land of Ooo, each of which plays out a
            separate chapter (like your own personal episode of the show).
            ? See the Adventure Time characters and familiar locations for the first time in 3D.
            ? Tackle puzzles by creatively using inventory objects and Jake's shape-shifting abilities.
            ? Combat evildoers as Finn using a variety of unique swords and Jake's awesome attack forms.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Amazing Spider-Man 2, The (USA)">
        <description>Amazing Spider-Man 2, The (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Activision</developer>
        <publisher>Beenox Studios</publisher>
        <score>0.75</score>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>The Amazing Spider-Man, this all-new third-person action-adventure video game builds on the story of the
            previous game with an alternative take on the events of the upcoming movie, while also giving players an
            enhanced, free-roaming web-slinging experience through a greatly expanded New York City.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Amazing Spider-Man, The - Ultimate Edition (USA)">
        <description>Amazing Spider-Man, The - Ultimate Edition (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Angry Birds Star Wars (USA)">
        <description>Angry Birds Star Wars (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Rovio</developer>
        <publisher>Activision</publisher>
        <score>0.35</score>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Angry Birds: Star Wars is a Star Wars themed edition of the Angry Birds series. The gameplay mechanics
            are the same as with other Angry Birds games, where the goal in each of the levels is to take out all of the
            pigs with the allocated amount and types of Angry Birds. The space and gravity mechanics from Angry Birds:
            Space are also implemented.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Angry Birds Trilogy (USA)">
        <description>Angry Birds Trilogy (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Rovio</developer>
        <publisher>Activision</publisher>
        <score>0.5</score>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Rovio's monstrously popular game about foul-tempered fowl migrates from the mobile platform to consoles
            for the first time with Angry Birds Trilogy. As always, players load a variety of uniquely skilled birds
            into a slingshot and fire them at green, egg-stealing pigs in an attempt to knock the thieving swine off
            their pedestals, or crush them beneath falling debris.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Animal Crossing - amiibo Festival (USA)">
        <description>Animal Crossing - amiibo Festival (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players>1-4</players>
        <story>You party animal!

            nnThe Animal Crossing: amiibo Festival game is a brand-new way to play with your favorite Animal Crossing
            characters. Your amiibo figures are front-and-center in this party game, and you'll get to use them with fun
            content. Bring to life an expansive and dynamic board game where the board is based on the months of the
            year like the core Animal Crossing series. The goal? Make your villager the happiest in town and party hard
            with your friends.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Art Academy - Atelier (Europe)">
        <description>Art Academy - Atelier (Europe)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Headstrong Games</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Various</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Art Academy Atelier is a drawing software on Wii U. It allows to use the Gamepad as canvas and as a
            palette, and the stylus as a multifunction tool (pencil, brush, charcoal ...) to create works of all kinds.
            These can then be shared via Miiverse, just like the videos of his creations in accelerated. 30 lessons
            teach you how to draw and improve.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Assassin's Creed III (USA)">
        <description>Assassin's Creed III (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Adventure-Fight-Platform-Action</genre>
        <players>1-4</players>
        <story>The American Colonies, 1775. A brave young warrior fights to save his homeland. But what begins as a
            struggle over territory turns into an extraordinary journey that will transform him into a Master
            Assassin-and will forever change the destiny of a nation. You are Connor, warrior son of a Native American
            mother and British father. As the colonies draw closer to revolution, you will dedicate your life to the
            freedom of your clan - becoming the spark that ignites the revolution into full blaze. Your crusade will
            take you through blood-soaked battlefields to crowded city streets, to perilous wilderness and beyond. You
            will not only witness history - you will make it.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Assassin's Creed IV - Black Flag (USA)">
        <description>Assassin's Creed IV - Black Flag (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Adventure</genre>
        <players>1-8</players>
        <story>Abstergo Industries - modern-day front for the organization of the Templars - has opened an entertainment
            subsidiary in Montreal, Quebec, using advanced technology that allows reliving fragments from the lives of
            people from the past. The unnamed protagonist is hired by the company to connect to the life of Edward
            Kenway, a Welsh privateer living in the eighteenth century. Through a series of events Edward assumes the
            identity of a rogue member of the Assassins reporting to Laureano Torres, the Governor of Cuba and also the
            Grand Master of the Templars. Initially motivated by greed, Edward finds himself at odds with both the
            Templars and the Assassins, who are both pursuing a mysterious man known as the Sage in order to gain access
            to the secret technology of the First Civilization.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Baila Latino (Europe)">
        <description>Baila Latino (Europe)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher>O2 GAMES</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Music and Dance</genre>
        <players>1-4</players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Barbie and Her Sisters - Puppy Rescue (USA)">
        <description>Barbie and Her Sisters - Puppy Rescue (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Little Orbit</developer>
        <publisher>Little Orbit</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Rejoignez Barbie et ses sœurs (Skipper, Stacie et Chelsea) pendand qu'elles résolvent des énigmes afin de
            trouver et sauver les chiots perdus dans le besoin. Faites un contrôle aux chiots chez Skipper au Roberts
            Sisters Puppy Rescue, toilettez les chiots chez Chelsea à Puppy Day Care ou enseignez-leur de nouveaux trucs
            avec Stacie à Pup Camp ! Nourrissez et jouez avec les chiots jusqu'à ce qu'ils puissent retourner à leurs
            confortables maisons !</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Barbie Dreamhouse Party (USA)">
        <description>Barbie Dreamhouse Party (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Little Orbit</developer>
        <publisher>Little Orbit</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Adventure</genre>
        <players>1-4</players>
        <story>Explore the Dreamhouse and play through fabulous mini-games as Barbie and her friends.

            Raquelle flipped a switch in the Dreamhouse that turned every room into a party game! Barbie and her friends
            must play their way through the house and turn things back to normal.

            Explore the Dreamhouse and play fun mini games

            Collect fab fashions to dress and style Barbie and her friends</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Batman - Arkham City - Armored Edition (USA)">
        <description>Batman - Arkham City - Armored Edition (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Warner Bros. Interactive</developer>
        <publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
        <score>0.9</score>
        <genre>Adventure</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Batman: Arkham City - Armored Edition is a conversion of Batman: Arkham City for the Wii U platform. Next
            to the base game it incorporates all the DLC previously featured in Batman: Arkham City - Game of the Year
            Edition</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Batman - Arkham Origins (USA)">
        <description>Batman - Arkham Origins (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Warner Bros. Interactive</developer>
        <publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Adventure</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Batman: Arkham Origins is a prequel to Batman: Arkham Asylum and is set about one year after Bruce Wayne
            became Batman. The main villain is the drug lord Black Mask who assigns eight powerful villains - e.g. Bane
            or Firefly - to assassinate Batman once and for all. During the course of the story, Batman also has to deal
            with Joker for the first time. It is also long before Arkham City was established and therefore Batman can
            explore the whole city; the new city part has about the same size as the known area. However, the different
            setting does not make a whole lot of difference - because of a curfew there are no civilians to be found.
            Batman can use the Batwing for fast traveling (there is no active flying involved) and visit his Batcave.
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Bayonetta (USA)">
        <description>Bayonetta (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Platinum Games</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.9</score>
        <genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Bayonetta is a cinematic and stylish action game from the creative mind of Hideki Kamiya. As a
            gun-wielding witch with powers beyond the comprehension of mere mortals, Bayonetta faces-off against
            countless enemies in a game of 100% pure all-out action. Outlandish finishing moves are performed with
            acrobatic grace as Bayonetta flows from one fight to another. Bayonetta pushes the limits of the action
            genre with magnificent over-the-top action and fast-paced, dynamic climax combat.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Bayonetta 2 (USA)">
        <description>Bayonetta 2 (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Ben 10 - Omniverse (USA)">
        <description>Ben 10 - Omniverse (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Monkey Bar Games</developer>
        <publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
        <score>0.3</score>
        <genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
        <players>1-2</players>
        <story>Ben 10 Omniverse est un beat'em all sur Wii U. Suite à une expérience ratée, le continuum espace-temps
            est déréglé et Korbo voyage entre deux époques. Allié à un Ben 10 tentôt enfant tantôt ado, ils doivent tous
            deux se défaire de nombreux ennemis. On débloque de nouveaux combos et des pouvoirs supplémentaires en
            gagnant de l'expérience.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Ben 10 - Omniverse 2 (USA)">
        <description>Ben 10 - Omniverse 2 (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
        <publisher>High Voltage</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players>1-2</players>
        <story>Ben 10 Omniverse 2 est un jeu d?action disponible sur Wii U. Incarnez Ben et ses différentes formes
            rendues possibles par l?Omnitrix afin de combattre l?empereur Mileous, et ses sbires, les Incursean. Un mode
            multijoueur coopératif et 10 formes différentes pour le héros sont disponibles. Les combos sont de la
            partie, et des combos multi-alien font leur apparition.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Brunswick Pro Bowling (USA)">
        <description>Brunswick Pro Bowling (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Cabela's Big Game Hunter - Pro Hunts (USA)">
        <description>Cabela's Big Game Hunter - Pro Hunts (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Activision</developer>
        <publisher>Activision</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Simulation-Lightgun Shooter</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Hunt with the pros! Take down the the world's biggest game with some of the foremost hunting pros as your
            guide!

            Bring home bigger game faster using advice from our pros, including Wade Middleton, Jim Shockey, and Ralph
            &amp; Vicki Cianciarulo.
            The most authentic hunting ballistics ever in a Cabela's game!
            Track, scout and target your trophy animal in all new ways!
            Traverse maps 4x the size of any previous Cabela's Big Game Hunter game!</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Cabela's Dangerous Hunts 2013 (USA)">
        <description>Cabela's Dangerous Hunts 2013 (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Activision</developer>
        <publisher>Activision</publisher>
        <score>0.3</score>
        <genre>Hunting and Fishing-Hunting-Lightgun Shooter</genre>
        <players>1-4</players>
        <story>Powered by the all-new Prowler AI system, predators in Dangerous Hunts 2013 are now smarter, and deadlier
            than ever before. Animals now have the ability to form pack social hierarchies, coordinate complex group
            tactics and take advantage of the surroundings to set up deadly ambushes. No two scenarios are alike and
            what worked before will not work so well the next time around.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Call of Duty - Black Ops II (USA)">
        <description>Call of Duty - Black Ops II (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Activision</developer>
        <publisher>Treyarch</publisher>
        <score>0.65</score>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <players>18</players>
        <story>Call of Duty : Black Ops 2 est un FPS sur Wii U. Incarnez deux personnages dans un scénario scindé en
            deux parties. Le mode solo se compose de missions classiques et de niveaux optionnels nommés Strike Force,
            intégrant des éléments stratégiques. On y retrouve aussi des modes multijoueurs et le fameux mode Zombie.
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Call of Duty - Ghosts (USA)">
        <description>Call of Duty - Ghosts (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Activision</developer>
        <publisher>Infinity Ward</publisher>
        <score>0.6</score>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <players>1-4</players>
        <story>Outnumbered and Outgunned, but Not Outmatched: Call of Duty: Ghosts is an extraordinary step forward for
            one of the largest entertainment franchises of all-time. This new chapter in the Call of Duty franchise
            features a new dynamic where players are on the side of a crippled nation fighting not for freedom, or
            liberty, but simply to survive. Fueling this all new Call of Duty experience, the franchise's new next-gen
            engine delivers stunning levels of immersion and performance.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Captain Toad - Treasure Tracker (USA)">
        <description>Captain Toad - Treasure Tracker (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.7</score>
        <genre>Platform-Puzzle-Game</genre>
        <players>1-2</players>
        <story>Captain Toad Treasure Tracker est un jeu de réflexion et de plates-formes sur Wii U. Toad se lance dans
            sa première aventure solo inspirée des stages spéciaux de Super Mario 3D World. L'objectif est de déjouer
            les pièges de l'environnement en modifiant les perspectives à l'aide de la caméra pour atteindre la sortie
            des niveaux avec un maximum de pièces et de gemmes cachées.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Cocoto Magic Circus 2 (Europe)">
        <description>Cocoto Magic Circus 2 (Europe)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Bigben Interactive</developer>
        <publisher>Bigben Interactive</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
        <players>1-5</players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Croods, The - Prehistoric Party! (USA)">
        <description>Croods, The - Prehistoric Party! (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Darksiders II (USA)">
        <description>Darksiders II (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>THQ</developer>
        <publisher>Vigil Games</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Adventure</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Awakened by the End of Days, Death, the most feared of the legendary Four Horsemen, embarks on a quest to
            undo Armageddon. Along the way, Death discovers that there are far worse things than an earthly Apocalypse,
            and that an ancient grudge may threaten all of Creation. Become the terrifying force which everything fears
            but nothing can escape. Death Lives, in Darksiders II.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Deus Ex - Human Revolution - Director's Cut (USA)">
        <description>Deus Ex - Human Revolution - Director's Cut (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Square Enix</developer>
        <publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>RPG</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Deus Ex: Human Revolution - Director's Cut is an expanded re-release of Deus Ex: Human Revolution and
            includes all DLC (download content):

            The Missing Link (integrated into the storyline)nn Explosive Mission Pack (including the Tracer Tong
            pre-order mission)nn Tactical Enhancement Packnn It also includes the making-of documentary which was
            originally released with the Augmented Edition</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Devil's Third (USA)">
        <description>Devil's Third (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer>Valhalla Game Studios</developer>
        <publisher>Valhalla Game Studios</publisher>
        <score>0.7</score>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Devil's Third sur Wii U est un jeu d'action à la troisième personne créé par le talentueux Tomonobu
            Itagaki. Comme à son habitude, Itagaki nous propose un jeu nerveux et sanglant dans lequel les armes à feu
            côtoient les sabres et autres jouets coupants. De quoi s'adonner à des démembrements en règle dans un
            environnement urbain propice aux acrobaties de toutes sortes.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Disney Infinity (USA)">
        <description>Disney Infinity (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Disney Interactive</developer>
        <publisher>Avalanche Software</publisher>
        <score>0.75</score>
        <genre>Various</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Disney Infinity est un jeu d'action / plates-formes sur Wii U jouable grâce à des figurines, toutes
            venues de personnages de l'univers Disney, comme Jack Sparrow, les Indestructibles ou encore Bob et Sully de
            Monstres et Cie. Le mode Aventure permet de suivre une histoire avec notre personnage dans un monde ouvert
            alors que le mode ToyBox nous invite à créer un univers avec les objets collectés en jeu.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Disney Infinity 2.0 Edition (USA)">
        <description>Disney Infinity 2.0 Edition (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Disney Infinity 3.0 Edition (USA)">
        <description>Disney Infinity 3.0 Edition (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Donkey Kong Country - Tropical Freeze (USA)">
        <description>Donkey Kong Country - Tropical Freeze (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="DuckTales - Remastered (USA)">
        <description>DuckTales - Remastered (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer>Wayforward</developer>
        <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>DuckTales: Remastered is a hand-crafted, beautiful reimagining of one of the most cherished 8-bit titles
            of all time. Embark on an authentic DuckTales adventure, as Scrooge McDuck and his three nephews; Huey,
            Dewey and Louie travel to exotic locations throughout the world in their quest to retrieve the five
            Legendary Treasures.

            Go back to one of the golden ages of gaming, but now refined with a level of detail that will please the
            most devoted Disney or retro Capcom fan, alike. Featuring hand-drawn animated sprites, authentic Disney
            character voices talent and richly painted level backgrounds from the classic cartoon TV series, Scrooge
            McDuck and family come to life like never before. The gameplay retains the authenticity of its 8-bit
            predecessor, simple and fun, with slight modifications to improve gameplay flow and design.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Epic Mickey 2 - The Power of Two (USA)">
        <description>Epic Mickey 2 - The Power of Two (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="ESPN Sports Connection (USA)">
        <description>ESPN Sports Connection (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Family Party - 30 Great Games Obstacle Arcade (USA)">
        <description>Family Party - 30 Great Games Obstacle Arcade (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Art Co. Ltd.</developer>
        <publisher>D3 Publisher</publisher>
        <score>0.15</score>
        <genre>Casual Game</genre>
        <players>4</players>
        <story>Family Party: 30 Great Games Obstacle Arcade brings home wacky and wild competitions for kids of all
            ages.

            Exclusively for the Wii U™ system from Nintendo, Obstacle Arcade lets players participate in over 30 party
            games specifically designed for multiplayer. Delivering an unmatched combination of variety and value, it
            features dozens of hysterical obstacle courses, popular sporting events, and arcade and brain challenges.

            Family Party: 30 Great Games Obstacle Arcade takes players to “Family Party Land”, a magical island loaded
            with a combination of familiar games and over-the-top challenges. Dodge barrels, ride horses, skydive, shoot
            rockets, kick goals, and more. Rule the island by earning medals and high scores, and unlocking new games.

            Features

            • Over 30 fun party games that highlight the all-new Wii U™ system!
            –Use the all-new Wii U™ GamePad in special 1-on-3 multiplayer challenges
            –Aim and shoot with the Wii U™ GamePad to kick soccer balls or to act as a game master in hidden card games
            and obstacle course challenges.
            –Tilt the Wii U™ GamePad to roll giant balls, to fly through space in zero gravity, or to block projectiles
            as a shield
            –Track high scores and game progress on the Wii U™ GamePad's display

            • Loaded with fun games custom made for family play, including tons of extreme obstacle courses, sports, and
            arcade game challenges
            –Over the top obstacles: Giant bouncing balls, alligator jumping, crazy hurdles, jetpacks vs. rocket
            launchers, and other thrills!
            –Sports: Everything from air hockey to eating contests to rodeo
            –Fun for the whole family: Arcade games, card games, and more
            • An unmatched combination of variety and value!
            –All games designed for 4-player multiplayer and all-ages family competition –Win trophies and achieve high
            scores to unlock new games and characters
            –Less than $1 a game for over 30 fun party games that showcase the all-new Wii U™ system.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Fast &amp; Furious - Showdown (USA)">
        <description>Fast &amp; Furious - Showdown (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="FIFA Soccer 13 (USA)">
        <description>FIFA Soccer 13 (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Fit Music for Wii U (Europe)">
        <description>Fit Music for Wii U (Europe)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Oxygene Media</developer>
        <publisher>Oxygene Media</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Various</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Are you tired of the gym? Bored of the same exercises? Do you want to have a physique everyone will envy?
            There is Fit Music for you now!

            Train all of your muscles with DANCE music doing fun, professional exercises. Bring the gym into your living
            room, forget the stress and join the party!

            The champion of fitness, Patsy Salviato, will be your personal trainer, guiding you through different game
            stages, with personalized difficulty levels, created in collaboration with SHRO of Philadelphia and the
            Human Health Foundation with whom Fit Music participates in the Fight Obesity campaign. Each section offers
            all the typical phases of the workout with warm-up exercises, an intensive training phase and a final
            relaxation phase. Thanks to a simple and intuitive interface for the new Wii U and a rhythmic and involving
            soundtrack, burning calories and toning your body has never been so much fun.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Funky Barn (USA)">
        <description>Funky Barn (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>505 Games</developer>
        <publisher>Tantalus Media</publisher>
        <score>0.75</score>
        <genre>Simulation</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Its farming! but not as you know it...

            Slap on your straw hat and grubbiest coveralls and take hold of your Wii U GamePad - it's time to get your
            hands dirty! Devote yourself to your own slice of lush countryside and take up the challenge of creating a
            beautiful farmland full of animals, crops, trees and more then develop it into the craziest, most offbeat
            farm imaginable, overflowing with the whackiest contraptions and goofiest gizmos you and your animals have
            ever seen! This is not your ordinary farm...

            It's your farm - and it's like no farm you've seen before!</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Game &amp; Wario (USA)">
        <description>Game &amp; Wario (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.7</score>
        <genre>Casual Game</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Wario has gotten into the business of designing games. With the help of his development crew at
            WarioWare, Inc., he has set out to make the greatest collection of games Diamond City has ever seen. Game
            &amp; Wario features these fun and refreshingly unusual games that are played exclusively with the Wii U
            GamePad controller.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Game Party Champions (USA)">
        <description>Game Party Champions (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Phosphor Games Studio</developer>
        <publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
        <score>0.1</score>
        <genre>Casual Game</genre>
        <players>4</players>
        <story>Game Party Champions is the fifth and latest installment of the widely successful Game Party franchise
            and available exclusively for Wii U. The gameâs fun, pick-up and play style will appeal to experienced and
            new gamers alike. Using the systemâs innovative new GamePad, players tilt, turn and touch the controller to
            play arcade, sports and party games in entirely new ways.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Giana Sisters - Twisted Dreams - Director's Cut (USA)">
        <description>Giana Sisters - Twisted Dreams - Director's Cut (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Guitar Hero Live (USA)">
        <description>Guitar Hero Live (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Activision</developer>
        <publisher>Activision</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Music and Dance</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Hello Kitty Kruisers (USA)">
        <description>Hello Kitty Kruisers (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Hot Wheels - World's Best Driver (USA)">
        <description>Hot Wheels - World's Best Driver (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="How to Train Your Dragon 2 (USA)">
        <description>How to Train Your Dragon 2 (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Hunter's Trophy 2 - Europa (Europe)">
        <description>Hunter's Trophy 2 - Europa (Europe)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Hyrule Warriors (USA)">
        <description>Hyrule Warriors (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>OMEGA Force</developer>
        <publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
        <players>2</players>
        <story>Hyrule Warriors, known in Japan as Zelda Mus, is a hack and slash action video game released in Japan on
            August 14, 2014, and scheduled to be released in the West in September. Developed by Omega Force and Team
            Ninja for the Wii U video game console, the game is a collaboration between Koei Tecmo and Nintendo, and
            contains elements of Nintendo's The Legend of Zelda series and Koei Tecmo's Dynasty Warriors series.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Injustice - Gods Among Us (USA)">
        <description>Injustice - Gods Among Us (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Jeopardy! (USA)">
        <description>Jeopardy! (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>THQ</developer>
        <publisher>THQ</publisher>
        <score>0.3</score>
        <genre>Puzzle</genre>
        <players>4+</players>
        <story>Join Alex Trebek and play as a contestant on Americas Favorite Quiz Show!"

            Test your knowledge to make it to Final Jeopardy! and the coveted Winners Circle!

            -Use your quick wit to play 3,000 clues in Jeopardy!, Double Jeopardy! and Final Jeopardy!
            -The complete Jeopardy! Clue Crew of Jimmy, Kelly and Sarah bring the clues to life the first time in a game
            format
            -Vibrant HD graphics, improved menu interface and fresh in-game features!
            -Play in single player mode with the Wii U GamePad or connect your Wii U to the TV and play as a family
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Jett Tailfin (Europe)">
        <description>Jett Tailfin (Europe)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Maximum Family Games</developer>
        <publisher>Maximum Family Games</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Racing</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Join Jett and his Friends as they race through some wild worlds on their way to Top Fin!

            nnThis is the challenging and dangerous world of underwater racing! As a fast fish, you will run through
            several track trying to be first in the speed challenge. The player must be one of the first to qualify and
            proceed to the next race. Accumulate enough points through the 16 tracks and become the Champion! You can
            also face the other racers in special bonus rounds where they will do their best to let you eat their dust?
            or bubbles.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Just Dance - Disney Party 2 (USA)">
        <description>Just Dance - Disney Party 2 (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Music and Dance</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Just Dance and Disney are back together, bringing the greatest dance game for the whole family with music
            from the hottest Disney Channel shows, in Just Dance®: Disney Party 2.

            Dance like the stars from the most popular Disney Channel shows and movies. With a great selection of family
            favorite songs, fun dances, and kid-friendly gameplay, children of all ages can dance along with family and
            friends.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Just Dance 2014 (Europe)">
        <description>Just Dance 2014 (Europe)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Music and Dance</genre>
        <players>5</players>
        <story>Just Dance 2014 is the fifth main game in the dancing series where players are rated for their ability to
            mimic dance routines to popular songs. For Xbox 360 and Xbox One the whole body movement is analyzed through
            the Kinect peripheral. The PS3 and PS4 track movement through the PlayStation Eye (optional) and PlayStation
            Camera respectively along with the Move peripheral, which is optional for the PS4 version. For the Wii and
            Wii U the Wii Remote is used to track movement and for Wii U the GamePad can be used as a karaoke mike or to
            direct the scenes with a free-roaming camera. Up to four players dancing simultaneously are supported with
            up to six for Xbox One. For consoles supporting a microphone, a karaoke mode is supported. There the game
            does not rate the player's words, but the notes and pitch.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Just Dance 2014 (USA)">
        <description>Just Dance 2014 (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Music and Dance</genre>
        <players>5</players>
        <story>Just Dance 2014 is the fifth main game in the dancing series where players are rated for their ability to
            mimic dance routines to popular songs. For Xbox 360 and Xbox One the whole body movement is analyzed through
            the Kinect peripheral. The PS3 and PS4 track movement through the PlayStation Eye (optional) and PlayStation
            Camera respectively along with the Move peripheral, which is optional for the PS4 version. For the Wii and
            Wii U the Wii Remote is used to track movement and for Wii U the GamePad can be used as a karaoke mike or to
            direct the scenes with a free-roaming camera. Up to four players dancing simultaneously are supported with
            up to six for Xbox One. For consoles supporting a microphone, a karaoke mode is supported. There the game
            does not rate the player's words, but the notes and pitch.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Just Dance 2015 (Europe)">
        <description>Just Dance 2015 (Europe)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Music and Dance</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Just Dance 2015 is the sixth main game in the dancing series where players perform dance routines,
            mimicking the moves of on-screen performers, to earn points. The controls are different for each platform.
            For Wii and Wii U movement is tracked through the Wii Remote, Xbox 360 and Xbox One require the Kinect
            peripheral, and PS3 and PS4 use the Move controllers along with the PlayStation Eye and PS Camera
            respectively. You can also download an app to an iOS or Android phone to use it as a controller. The app
            connects through the local Wi-Fi network and detects the console for the phones to register, based on the
            technology used in the game Just Dance Now. That way platform-specific peripherals are no longer required.
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Just Dance 2015 (USA)">
        <description>Just Dance 2015 (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Music and Dance</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Just Dance 2015 is the sixth main game in the dancing series where players perform dance routines,
            mimicking the moves of on-screen performers, to earn points. The controls are different for each platform.
            For Wii and Wii U movement is tracked through the Wii Remote, Xbox 360 and Xbox One require the Kinect
            peripheral, and PS3 and PS4 use the Move controllers along with the PlayStation Eye and PS Camera
            respectively. You can also download an app to an iOS or Android phone to use it as a controller. The app
            connects through the local Wi-Fi network and detects the console for the phones to register, based on the
            technology used in the game Just Dance Now. That way platform-specific peripherals are no longer required.
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Just Dance 2016 (Europe)">
        <description>Just Dance 2016 (Europe)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Various</genre>
        <players>4+</players>
        <story>Introducing Just Dance 2016 - the newest game from the top-selling franchise - with a brand new way to
            play! All you need is your smartphone and the Just Dance Controller App to play Just Dance 2016 on PS4
            system, no PlayStationCamera or PlayStationMove needed.

            Bust a move to Uptown Funk by Mark Ronson Ft. Bruno Mars and feel the beat in All About That Bass by Meghan
            Trainor - Just Dance 2016 features an amazing tracklist with visuals that are more creative and
            breath-taking than ever before. Join over 100MM players and dance to fun favorites and hot hits, today!
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Just Dance 2016 (USA)">
        <description>Just Dance 2016 (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Various</genre>
        <players>4+</players>
        <story>Introducing Just Dance 2016 - the newest game from the top-selling franchise - with a brand new way to
            play! All you need is your smartphone and the Just Dance Controller App to play Just Dance 2016 on PS4
            system, no PlayStationCamera or PlayStationMove needed.

            Bust a move to Uptown Funk by Mark Ronson Ft. Bruno Mars and feel the beat in All About That Bass by Meghan
            Trainor - Just Dance 2016 features an amazing tracklist with visuals that are more creative and
            breath-taking than ever before. Join over 100MM players and dance to fun favorites and hot hits, today!
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Just Dance 4 (Europe)">
        <description>Just Dance 4 (Europe)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Music and Dance</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Just Dance 4 features more than 40 new tracks, ranging from chart-topping Billboard hits to classic dance
            party tracks. Whether it's pop, Hip-Hop, rock, R&amp;B, country or funk, there is something for everyone.
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Just Dance 4 (USA)">
        <description>Just Dance 4 (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Music and Dance</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Just Dance 4 features more than 40 new tracks, ranging from chart-topping Billboard hits to classic dance
            party tracks. Whether it's pop, Hip-Hop, rock, R&amp;B, country or funk, there is something for everyone.
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Just Dance Kids 2014 (USA)">
        <description>Just Dance Kids 2014 (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Music and Dance</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Just Dance Kids 2014 is the third game in the Just Dance Kids sub-series of the Just Dance franchise. The
            game contains thirty music tracks for a younger audience where players need to mimic the dance routines
            shown on the screen. The music selection is a mix of covers and original recordings with both older and
            newer songs and artists such as Harry Belafonte and One Direction, but also Mary Had a Little Lamb. Each
            song has its own dance routine shown by performers on the screen. Next to dance moves for each song there is
            also a difficulty level with a different type of effort required and they are marked either for a younger or
            an older player.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Kirby and the Rainbow Curse (USA)">
        <description>Kirby and the Rainbow Curse (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Kung Fu Panda - Showdown of Legendary Legends (USA)">
        <description>Kung Fu Panda - Showdown of Legendary Legends (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Legend of Kay Anniversary (USA)">
        <description>Legend of Kay Anniversary (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer>Unit 4 Games</developer>
        <publisher>Nordic Games</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Experience the unique blend of Martial Arts-combat, action adventure, Jump 'n' Run and puzzle solving.

            10 years after its initial release, Legend of Kay Anniversary is a thoroughly remastered version of the
            original game with high resolution textures, new &amp; more detailed character models, modern rendering
            techniques and crystal-clear surround sound which give this great classic a new shine.

            Full of fond allusions to old martial arts films and pop culture quotes, Legend of Kay Anniversary is both
            an incredibly funny game and a challenging action-adventure for young and old alike.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Legend of Zelda, The - The Wind Waker HD (USA)">
        <description>Legend of Zelda, The - The Wind Waker HD (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Legend of Zelda, The - Twilight Princess HD (USA)">
        <description>Legend of Zelda, The - Twilight Princess HD (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="LEGO Batman 2 - DC Super Heroes (USA)">
        <description>LEGO Batman 2 - DC Super Heroes (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Travellers Tales</developer>
        <publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Adventure</genre>
        <players>1-2</players>
        <story>LEGO Batman 2: DC Super Heroes is an action game and the sequel to LEGO Batman: The Videogame. Just like
            the first game it draws elements from the Batman universe but built entirely in LEGO-style bricks. It starts
            when a "Man of the Year" award ceremony in Gotham City is interrupted by the Joker and a gang of bandits.
            Bruce Wayne is a candidate for the award and changes into Batman to pursue them, teaming up with members of
            the Justice League.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="LEGO Batman 3 - Beyond Gotham (USA)">
        <description>LEGO Batman 3 - Beyond Gotham (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>TT Games</developer>
        <publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players>1-2</players>
        <story>LEGO Batman 3: Beyond Gotham is the third LEGO game based on DC Comics characters. While it prominently
            features Batman and his supporting cast, as indicated by the subtitle it moves beyond Gotham City into all
            corners of the DC universe, featuring the Justice League, the Legion of Doom and several Lantern Corps, with
            all sorts of heroes and villains making an appearance, and the story moving from Earth to outer space and
            several other planets.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="LEGO City Undercover (USA)">
        <description>LEGO City Undercover (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>TT Games</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>For the first time, LEGO City vehicles and play sets come to life in the LEGO City: Undercover game,
            exclusively for the Wii U console.

            Explore the vast and open city filled with humorous LEGO characters any way you want. You can commandeer any
            one of over 100 different vehicles on the street or fly a helicopter through the air on your missions.
            Assume the identity of Chase McCain, an undercover officer armed with clever disguises each with their own
            special abilities and try to put a stop to the fiendish Rex Fury and end his crime wave in LEGO City.

            Use the Wii U GamePad controller as the ultimate detective device to seamlessly connect to the in-game
            action using it as an indispensable map, communicator, and high-tech scanning device. Look into the screen
            of the GamePad to get new views of crime scenes and use its motion sensing capabilities to scan for hidden
            clues and hiding criminals.

            It?s up to you to save the good people of LEGO City.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="LEGO Dimensions (USA)">
        <description>LEGO Dimensions (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Warner Bros. Interactive</developer>
        <publisher>Travellers Tales</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>LEGO Dimensions is a multi-franchise toys-to-life game featuring characters and levels from 14 licensed
            franchises with additional franchises due to arrive in the future. The game contains elements from the
            Middle Earth franchise, The LEGO Movie, DC Comics, The Wizard of Oz, The Simpsons, Back to the Future,
            Scooby-Doo, Doctor Who, Portal 2, the Midway Arcade franchise, LEGO Legends of Chima, LEGO Ninjago,
            Ghostbusters, and Jurassic World.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="LEGO Jurassic World (USA)">
        <description>LEGO Jurassic World (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Warner Bros. Interactive</developer>
        <publisher>Travellers Tales</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>LEGO Jurassic World is an action game based on the four Jurassic Park movies and released alongside the
            2015 movie Jurassic World. As with many other Tt Games titles it adapts a licensed franchise to a world
            built up out of LEGO bricks. The game consists of 20 levels, five for each of the movies, played in
            succession. The game borrows many iconic moments from the films using the original audio clips and often
            adds a humorous twist.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="LEGO Marvel Super Heroes (USA)">
        <description>LEGO Marvel Super Heroes (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Warner Bros. Interactive</developer>
        <publisher>TT Games</publisher>
        <score>0.75</score>
        <genre>Adventure</genre>
        <players>2</players>
        <story>Lego Marvel Super Heroes is an action game, reuniting about one hundred and a half Marvel heroes and
            villains coming from several Marvel franchises, having the player control the good ones in order to save the
            Earth from a team of the vicious (headed by Galactus, also named as The Devourer of the Worlds); all in the
            fashion of LEGO adventures blocky cartoonish visual style and gameplay.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="LEGO Marvel's Avengers (USA)">
        <description>LEGO Marvel's Avengers (USA)</description>
        <year>2016</year>
        <developer>Warner Bros. Interactive</developer>
        <publisher>Travellers Tales</publisher>
        <score>0.7</score>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>LEGO Marvel Avengers is a spin-off of the successful LEGO Marvel Super Heroes focusing on the story of
            the films of the Marvel Cinematic Universe. The game covers the events of the cinematic universe up to
            'Avengers: Age of Ultron' and covers content seen in 'Captain America: The First Avenger', 'Avengers
            Assemble', 'Iron Man 3', 'Thor 2', and 'Avengers: Age of Ultron' with DLC packs available for other entries
            within the Marvel Cinematic Universe such as 'Ant-Man' and 'Marvel's Agents of SHIELD'.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="LEGO Movie Videogame, The (USA)">
        <description>LEGO Movie Videogame, The (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="LEGO The Hobbit (USA)">
        <description>LEGO The Hobbit (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>TT Games</developer>
        <publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
        <score>0.9</score>
        <genre>Adventure</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>LEGO The Hobbit is based on the first two films in The Hobbit movie trilogy: The Hobbit: An Unexpected
            Journey and The Hobbit: Desolation of Smaug. Like the other LEGO Tt games it is an adaptation of the
            franchise to the LEGO universe. It allows players to play through different scenes from the films and follow
            Bilbo Baggins as he is recruited by Gandalf to aid Thorin Oakenshield and his Company of Dwarves. Bilbo
            leaves the comforts of the Shire on a journey to help the Dwarves reclaim their lost Kingdom of Erebor
            within the Lonely Mountain. Many dangers and adventures await and unexpected discovery of a certain ring.
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Luv me Buddies Wonderland (Europe)">
        <description>Luv me Buddies Wonderland (Europe)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Oxygene</developer>
        <publisher>Oxygene</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Educational</genre>
        <players>1-4</players>
        <story>Play and have fun with the fantastic Luv Me Buddies puppets and experience an exciting adventure along
            with your nice, new friends! In a colorful world, you will discover many mini-games designed for children,
            which will entertain, amuse and involve the whole family for beautiful moments of pure relaxation!

            The Luv Me Buddies game is challenging, fun, educational activities, with fancy and sparkling graphics. Each
            time you interact with one of the lovable and cute little animals, you increase your chances in the game,
            unlocking new mini-games, for a never ending experience.

            Bright colors, catchy music and magical settings. The game stimulates children's imagination and helps them
            to interact with their creativity. Luv Me Buddies is an immersive experience for children and adults.

            Enjoy and relax with "Luv Me Buddies"!</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Madden NFL 13 (USA)">
        <description>Madden NFL 13 (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>EA Sports</developer>
        <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
        <score>0.9</score>
        <genre>Sports</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>With beautiful HD graphics, an in-depth Career mode, and exclusive Touch Screen features, Madden NFL 13
            on the Wii U delivers the most authentic NFL experience ever on a Nintendo platform. Build your own legacy
            as a player or a coach-or relive the glory of an all-time legend-in Connected Careers. Immerse yourself in
            the Madden NFL experience with features exclusive to the Wii U, including streamlined playcalling, personnel
            management, and more-all directed from the Wii U gamepad's innovative Touch Screen. Madden NFL 13-bringing
            next generation innovation, gameplay, and graphics to a Nintendo platform like never before.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Mario &amp; Sonic at the Sochi 2014 Olympic Winter Games (USA)">
        <description>Mario &amp; Sonic at the Sochi 2014 Olympic Winter Games (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Mario Kart 8 (USA)">
        <description>Mario Kart 8 (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Mario Party 10 (USA)">
        <description>Mario Party 10 (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.6</score>
        <genre>Board Game</genre>
        <players>5</players>
        <story>Mario Party 10 is a 2015 party video game for the Nintendo Wii U. Developed by Nd Cube and published by
            Nintendo, it is the tenth "main" game in the Mario Party series, the fourteenth in the franchise, and the
            first game in the series for the Wii U. The game was released worldwide in March 2015.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Mario Tennis - Ultra Smash (USA)">
        <description>Mario Tennis - Ultra Smash (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Marvel Avengers - Battle for Earth (USA)">
        <description>Marvel Avengers - Battle for Earth (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score>0.5</score>
        <genre>Fighting</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>The Avengers: Battle for Earth is a versus fighting game designed around motion controls. It is based on
            the 2008 Marvel comics storyline Secret Invasion, in which the Skrulls, shapeshifting aliens, have taken the
            place of many of the Marvel universe's superheroes, with the remaining genuine heroes having to team up to
            defeat the menace.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Mass Effect 3 - Special Edition (USA)">
        <description>Mass Effect 3 - Special Edition (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Monster High - 13 Wishes (USA)">
        <description>Monster High - 13 Wishes (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Game Machine Studios</developer>
        <publisher>Little Orbit</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Go a on monstrous adventure inside the lantern.

            It's up to YOU to help Frankie Stein and her ghoulfriends track down the 13 magical mirror shards needed to
            set things right -before it's too late!</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Monster High - New Ghoul in School (USA)">
        <description>Monster High - New Ghoul in School (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Welcome, new ghoul!
            Come roam the halls of Monster High and get to know your new classmates. Join clubs, make friends and dress
            up in fierce fashions. But be aware, there's something strange going on at Monster High! Cleo's new amulet
            has been cursed by the spirit of Spookenhamen, and the student body is falling under his spell. Use your
            skills and savvy to help save the school and all your new classmates from the mummy's curse! Be Yourself. Be
            Unique. Be a Monster.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate (USA)">
        <description>Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Capcom</developer>
        <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
        <score>0.9</score>
        <genre>RPG</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>The popular fantasy action franchise Monster Hunter is now one of the most iconic gaming series in the
            world selling over 21 million copies worldwide since the series began in 2004. Players take on the role of a
            hunter and are sent to explore a settlement within the Monster Hunter universe, completing quests on their
            journey to seek and slay monsters whilst improving their skills and earning equipment upgrades. With many
            challenging monsters and over 200 quests the latest edition to the series is set to be the most expansive
            offering to date. Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate utilizes the functionalities of the Nintendo 3DS system to
            provide players with a truly intuitive hunting experience. The touch screen feature allows players to
            quickly access in-game books, weapons, field maps and mini games whilst the high quality graphics 3D visuals
            of Nintendo 3DS powered by the latest iteration of Capcom's MT Framework deliver a unique and stunning world
            for players to explore. Taking advantage of the portability of Nintendo 3DS, players can exchange their
            guild card that contains all their hunter's information with other players via StreetPass. Players can
            experience the world of Monster Hunter alone or in four player local play using Nintendo 3DS. Finding nearby
            hunters to adventure on quests with is now even easier via the local Nintendo 3DS search feature. Wii U
            players will be able to enjoy the hunt with Nintendo 3DS players via a local wireless connection. Gamers
            that own both a Wii U and Nintendo 3DS can take advantage of the inter compatibility of save data between
            the two consoles, taking the hunt from the living room wherever they go.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="NBA 2K13 (USA)">
        <description>NBA 2K13 (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Visual Concepts</developer>
        <publisher>2K Games</publisher>
        <score>0.75</score>
        <genre>Sports</genre>
        <players>10</players>
        <story>With more than 5 million copies sold worldwide and more than 25 Sports Game of the Year awards won, NBA
            2K12 was another monster release for the biggest NBA video game simulation franchise in the world. This
            year, 2K Sports has joined forces with the legendary JAY Z as Executive Producer to transcend sports video
            games and take virtual hardwood to the next level. Featuring an enhanced MyCAREER mode and all-new gameplay
            features, NBA 2K13 will let gamers pit the best players in NBA history against the new dynasty of talent,
            including the much-debated matchup between the 2012 U.S. Men's National Team and the 1992 "Dream Team."
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Need for Speed - Most Wanted U (USA)">
        <description>Need for Speed - Most Wanted U (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Criterion Studios</developer>
        <publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Racing</genre>
        <players>2</players>
        <story>Need for Speed: Most Wanted is a Wii U racing game that offers you the opportunity to challenge law
            enforcement through various chases. The goal here is to collect the offences while avoiding the police in
            order to top the list of the most wanted drivers. Several types of cars are available (sports, super cars,
            muscle cars) and an open environment serves as a playground.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="NES Remix Pack (USA)">
        <description>NES Remix Pack (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="New Super Luigi U (USA)">
        <description>New Super Luigi U (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>New Super Luigi U is a platform game on Wii U. Offered in stand-alone or as an extension of the game New
            Super Mario Bros. U, it allows to control Luigi in 82 revamped levels and adapted to the game play of Luigi.
            Carottin is now playable in multiplayer and each stage must be completed in less than 100 seconds.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="New Super Mario Bros. U (USA)">
        <description>New Super Mario Bros. U (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="New Super Mario Bros. U + New Super Luigi U (USA)">
        <description>New Super Mario Bros. U + New Super Luigi U (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Ninja Gaiden 3 - Razor's Edge (USA)">
        <description>Ninja Gaiden 3 - Razor's Edge (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Team Ninja</developer>
        <publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Ninja Gaiden 3: Razor's Edge is an update of Ninja Gaiden 3. It includes all the downloadable content
            made available on other platforms as well as some new changes. A new playable character is available, Ayane
            from the Dead or Alive series, with her own story mode chapters. An online co-operative mode has been added
            where both Ryu and Ayane are playable. The controls make use of the Wii U Game Pad for tasks such as
            executing Ninpo, as well as displaying the combo chart. The Karma functionality from previous games in the
            series is reintroduced in this version, allowing players to upgrade weapons, Ninpo, character health and
            move set. There have been other changes to aspects such as AI, as well as additional weapon and attack
            types, enemies and battle arenas.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Nintendo Land (USA)">
        <description>Nintendo Land (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Casual Game</genre>
        <players>1-5</players>
        <story>Nintendo Land is a fun and lively theme park filled with 12 different attractions, each with its own take
            on a Nintendo franchise. Each attraction features unique and innovative game-play experiences made possible
            by the Wii U GamePad controller. Depending on the attraction, players can compete solo or against other
            players, or even team up to play cooperatively. Up to five players can participate in dynamic multiplayer
            modes in select attractions.* The experiences change every time, depending on whether players are using the
            GamePad, holding a Wii Remote or just watching others play on the TV screen.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="One Piece - Unlimited World Red (Europe)">
        <description>One Piece - Unlimited World Red (Europe)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Ganbarion</developer>
        <publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Adventure</genre>
        <players>1-2</players>
        <story>One Piece: Unlimited World R is an action game based on the Japanese anime and manga series One Piece by
            Eiichiro Oda. It follows Monkey D. Luffy and his Strawhat pirate crew as they take on a new adventure unique
            to the game, all the while facing off against familiar faces from the anime and manga. These include Dracule
            Mihawk and Boa Hancock of the Shichibukai, Smoker and Tashigi of the Marines, and mysterious newcomer
            Patrick Redfield. Additionally, some allies to the Strawhats also make playable appearances, such as Portgas
            D. Ace and Trafalgar Law.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures (USA)">
        <description>Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Monkey Bar Games</developer>
        <publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players>1-4</players>
        <story>Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures is a 3D platform game based on the cartoon TV series of same name.
            Pac, Cylindria and Spiral are called to the lab of Sir C. He shows them three golden globes he found and
            explains that they need to be recharged with Globe energy orbs. And asks if you can help him with collecting
            the energy orbs. At this point four ghosts appear to warn them that Betrayus, lord of the ghosts, and his
            army have invaded the city of Pacoplis. Betrayus seems to have stolen some kind of freeze machine from the
            science center. It's up to you to stop him and his army and collecting the energy orbs needed to power the
            globes of Sir C along the way.

            Pac-Man can enter several modes to help him defeat enemies and overcome obstacles. The modes are: Chameleon
            Pac, Fire Pac, Granite ball Pac, Ice Pack, Metal Pac, Spin Pac.

            The game offers a multiplayer mode of up to four players.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures 2 (USA)">
        <description>Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures 2 (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Monkey Bar Games</developer>
        <publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures 2 is a 3D platform game based on the cartoon TV series of same name
            and it is the sequel to Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures. Betrayus, lord of the ghosts, and his servants
            come up with a plan to let Pac-Man steal the repository holding the Pac world bodies of all the ghosts in
            the Netherworld. It is now up to you to thwart this evil plan.

            Pac-Man can enter two new modes:
            PacKong: transforms you in to a ape like creature with great strength;
            PacZilla: this transforms you into a giant.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Peanuts Movie, The - Snoopy's Grand Adventure (USA)">
        <description>Peanuts Movie, The - Snoopy's Grand Adventure (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Penguins of Madagascar (USA)">
        <description>Penguins of Madagascar (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Phineas and Ferb - Quest for Cool Stuff (USA)">
        <description>Phineas and Ferb - Quest for Cool Stuff (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Pikmin 3 (USA)">
        <description>Pikmin 3 (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Strategy</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Pikmin 3 is a fully reimagined, mass-action strategy title from the critically acclaimed Pikmin series.
            Players will discover a beautiful world filled with strange creatures and take command of a swarm of
            ant-like Pikmin trying to survive. The world is densely packed with treasures and enemies, which makes the
            game much more action focused and fills it with layers of potential strategies and paths, adding greater
            replayability to challenge modes.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Planes (USA)">
        <description>Planes (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Planes - Fire &amp; Rescue (USA)">
        <description>Planes - Fire &amp; Rescue (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Pokken Tournament (USA)">
        <description>Pokken Tournament (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
        <publisher>The Pokémon Company</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Fighting</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Pokkén Tournament est un jeu de combat dans l'univers Pokémon. Utilisant les éléments de gameplay de la
            série de combat Tekken, il permet aux joueurs d'incarner différents pokémon dans des batailles dynamiques.
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Project Zero - Maiden of Black Water (Europe)">
        <description>Project Zero - Maiden of Black Water (Europe)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Rabbids Land (USA)">
        <description>Rabbids Land (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score>0.5</score>
        <genre>Casual Game</genre>
        <players>4</players>
        <story>The Rabbids Land Rabbits on Wii U is a party-game featuring Ubisoft's white rabbits. The cretin invasion
            takes place in an amusement park where a board game takes place in which you have to overcome by alternating
            mini-games and quizzes. Some videos can then be unlocked and a score of events.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Rapala Pro Bass Fishing (USA)">
        <description>Rapala Pro Bass Fishing (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer>Activision</developer>
        <publisher>Activision</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Simulation</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Rapala Pro Bass Fishing is a fishing simulator on Wii U in which you drive your boat to find the right
            fish spots or challenges scattered around the map. You have the opportunity to choose your environment and
            the weather conditions you want. It is also possible to participate in tournaments to put your talent to the
            test.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Rayman Legends (USA)">
        <description>Rayman Legends (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score>0.9</score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players>5</players>
        <story>Developed by Ubisoft Montpellier, Rayman Legends is the follow-up to last year's highly-acclaimed Rayman
            Origins. Rayman Legends takes full advantage of the Wii U controller to bring players innovative multiplayer
            interactions that go beyond those found in traditional platform games. Players can use the Wii U
            controller's touch screen to take out enemies or clear paths and use the gyroscope technology to manipulate
            and rotate platforms on the TV screen. The Wii U controller also allows players to continue the adventure of
            Rayman and his friends on the controller's screen even while the television is off.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Resident Evil - Revelations (USA)">
        <description>Resident Evil - Revelations (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Capcom</developer>
        <publisher>Capcom</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Resident Evil: Revelations on Wii U is a survival horror. The player must face monsters who are victims
            of a variant of the T Virus while trying to get out alive from a gigantic liner. In addition to the Campaign
            mode, there is also a Commando mode playable in cooperative.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Rise of the Guardians (USA)">
        <description>Rise of the Guardians (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
        <score>0.25</score>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <players>1-4</players>
        <story>Les Cinq Légendes raconte l'aventure fantastique d'un groupe de héros, tous dotés de pouvoirs
            extraordinaires.

            Lorsque Pitch, un esprit maléfique, décide de régner sur le monde, ces cinq légendes vont devoir, pour la
            première fois, unir leurs forces pour protéger les espoirs, les rêves et l'imagination de tous les enfants.

            Revivez l'aventure du film Les Cinq Légendes dans une aventure vidéoludique magique, formez votre équipe de
            quatre aventuriers et jouez avec vos amis. Améliorez vos armes, apprenez de nouveaux pouvoirs et changez de
            personnage à tout moment. Collectez des runes afin de débloquer des pouvoirs uniques pour chacun des
            personnages.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Rodea the Sky Soldier (USA)">
        <description>Rodea the Sky Soldier (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Prope</developer>
        <publisher>NIS America</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>A thousand years ago, Emperor Geardo of the Naga Empire sent an army of machine soldiers to invade the
            sky kingdom of Garuda. Thanks to the efforts of Princess Cecilia and Rodea, a machine soldier who promised
            to protect Garuda, Emperor Geardo's assault was thwarted. In present day, a spirited inventor named Ion
            discovers an abandoned robot that has fallen into disrepair in the heart of a scorching desert. Upon
            completing her repairs, the robot stirs to life and reveals itself to be none other than Rodea. Stunned to
            find himself in the future, Rodea learns that the Naga Empire is no more and that Garuda has known peace for
            a thousand years. But this peace was not meant to last, for the forces of Naga have returned to wage war
            against Garuda. Remembering the promise he made 1,000 years ago, Rodea takes to the skies to defend Garuda
            from the Naga Empire once again.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Scribblenauts Unlimited (USA)">
        <description>Scribblenauts Unlimited (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>5th Cell</developer>
        <publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
        <score>0.75</score>
        <genre>Puzzle</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Scribblenauts Unlimited features a huge side-scrolling open world with new, high-definition hand-drawn
            scenery and objects where players can help the game's hero, Maxwell, solve robust puzzles and challenges by
            summoning any object they can imagine. And for the first time, players learn the backstory of Maxwell's
            parents, his twin sister Lily, and how he acquired his magical notepad.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Scribblenauts Unmasked - A DC Comics Adventure (USA)">
        <description>Scribblenauts Unmasked - A DC Comics Adventure (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>5th Cell</developer>
        <publisher>Warner Bros. Interactive</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Various-Puzzle-Game-Adventure</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Scribblenauts Unmasked : A DC Comics Adventure est un jeu de puzzle / création / aventure disponible sur
            la Nintendo Wii U. Le soft vous propose d?incarner Maxwell, et de le faire évoluer dans l?univers de DC
            Comics. Vous êtes accompagné de votre s?ur jumelle Lily, et vous pouvez parcourir les lieux emblématiques de
            cet univers, comme Gotham City, Metropolis ou Atlantis. Près de 2.000 variations des super-héros seront
            disponibles.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Shovel Knight (USA)">
        <description>Shovel Knight (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Yacht Club Games</developer>
        <publisher>Yacht Club Games</publisher>
        <score>0.9</score>
        <genre>Adventure</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Shovel Knight is a sweeping classic action adventure game with awesome gameplay, memorable characters,
            and an 8-bit retro aesthetic. It's a hot mashup of new and old! You play as the eponymous Shovel Knight, a
            small knight with a huge quest. Shovel Knight has come to this land with two goals: to defeat the evil
            Enchantress and quest for his lost beloved. He wields a Shovel Blade: a multipurpose weapon whose techniques
            have now been lost to the ages. Always honest and helpful, Shovel Knight is a shining example of the code of
            Shovelry: Slash Mercilessly and Dig Tirelessly!

            But, between Shovel Knight and his beloved stands a cadre of villainous knights. These terrible foes, known
            as The Order of No Quarter, have been dispatched to prevent Shovel Knight from reaching the Enchantress, and
            will pursue their mission at any cost. If you love games with perfect platforming, beautiful art, infectious
            music, crazy bosses, humor and levity, and real heart? Shovel Knight is for you!</story>
    </game>
    <game name="SiNG Party (USA)">
        <description>SiNG Party (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Freestyle Games</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.75</score>
        <genre>Music and Dance</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>SiNG is a new interactive musical performance game for Wii U that gets everyone at the party involved in
            the music. With dozens of popular songs to choose from, everyone from novice singers and dancers to budding
            stars can join in on the fun. The main performer holds the GamePad while others in the room sing, dance and
            clap along with the music.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Skylanders Giants (USA)">
        <description>Skylanders Giants (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Toys For Bob</developer>
        <publisher>Activision</publisher>
        <score>0.7</score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>FROZEN IN OUR WORLD. ALIVE IN THEIRS. Thousands of years ago, the Skylanders Giants fought epic battles
            in Skylands but were banished to Earth. With a new threat looming, it's time to bring them back to join
            forces with the Skylanders. Only you can put them on the Portal of Power® to unleash their strength in the
            ultimate battle to save Skylands.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Skylanders SuperChargers (USA)">
        <description>Skylanders SuperChargers (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Activision</developer>
        <publisher>Vicarious Visions</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>In Skylanders SuperChargers, Kaos' quest to rule over Skylands reveals his most sinister weapon ever – a
            massive "Doomstation of Ultimate Doomstruction" capable of eating the sky itself. Fortunately, a special
            team of Skylanders known as the SuperChargers has been assembled to pilot an incredible fleet of vehicles
            with the power to travel through the destruction – over land, sea, and sky! But with Skylands on the verge
            of collapse, the Skylanders have reached out across all dimensions to call for reinforcements. Answering the
            call is the most unexpected duo – Donkey Kong and Bowser! Using their own elite vehicles to magically travel
            between worlds, they have joined the epic battle against Kaos and The Darkness!

            Key Features:

            * Skylanders SuperChargers introduces 20 new SuperCharger Skylanders and 20 new Vehicles and supports all
            300+ Skylanders toys from previous games, enabling any Skylanders character to pilot land, sea or sky-based
            vehicles.

            * Vehicles-to-Life – For the first time, players can take their Skylanders vehicles straight from the real
            world into the videogame via the Portal of Power to explore the land, sea and skies of Skylands.

            * Customized Vehicles –SuperChargers will have the ability to customize vehicles in-game with super cool
            modifications and upgradeable weapons.

            * SuperCharged Combos – For the ultimate gaming experience, players can pair a SuperCharger Skylander with
            its unique signature vehicle to create a SuperCharged combination, unlocking an exclusive mod that revs up
            the performance of both the vehicle and character.

            Exclusive Features:

            * For the first time in Skylanders history, two of Nintendo's iconic characters -- Donkey Kong and Bowser --
            will guest star in Skylanders SuperChargers.

            * These special Skylanders will be playable in both Skylanders SuperChargers and select amiibo-compatible
            games with a simple twist of the character's base.

            * Turbo Charge Donkey Kong and Hammer Slam Bowser will be exclusively playable on the following Nintendo
            platforms: Wii U, Wii and the Nintendo 3DS family of systems.

            * Enjoy the full game in off-TV mode through the Wii U GamePad.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Skylanders Swap Force (USA)">
        <description>Skylanders Swap Force (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
        <publisher>Activision</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Embark on an exciting new adventure with the Skylanders and the SWAP Force. For generations, the SWAP
            Force protected the volcano that replenishes Skylands? magic. That is until an epic battle caught them in an
            eruption that blasted them apart, sent them to Earth and gave them the ability to swap powers. Only you can
            mix and match their tops and bottoms, put them on the new Portal of Power? and save Skylands.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Skylanders Trap Team (USA)">
        <description>Skylanders Trap Team (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Activision</developer>
        <publisher>Beenox Studios</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Kaos has blown up the walls of the feared Cloudcracker Prison freeing the most notorious villains in
            Skylands. it's up to you and the Skylanders to find and capture them. using Traptanium, a magic material
            that can harness the power of the Elements, you have the amazing ability to trap the villains and return
            them to Skylands to fight for you! Begin the ultimate adventure as you explore Skylands in search of the
            escaped villains!


            Starter Pack includes: 1-Video Game, 1-Traptanium Portal, 2-Skylanders Figures, 2-Traps, 1-Character
            Collector Poster, 2-Sticker Sheets with Secret Codes and 2-Trading Cards.


            Build the ultimate Trap Team - Over 60 Skylanders to collect and 40+ villains to capture. Sticker Sheets
            with Secret Codes ? Enjoy stickers of your favorite Skylanders. Place the names and codes on the Character
            Collect Poster to track your collection. The secret codes can be used in the Skylanders Lost Islands and
            Skylanders Collection Vault Apps. Trading Cards ? Learn more about each Skylander?s powers and abilities.
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Smurfs 2, The (USA)">
        <description>Smurfs 2, The (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Sniper Elite V2 (USA)">
        <description>Sniper Elite V2 (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Rebellion</developer>
        <publisher>505 Games</publisher>
        <score>0.6</score>
        <genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Sniper Elite V2 will be a modern take on the critically and publically acclaimed classic Sniper Elite for
            the current generation of consoles - revitalising a genre all of its own when it is released in 2012</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Sonic &amp; All-Stars Racing Transformed (USA)">
        <description>Sonic &amp; All-Stars Racing Transformed (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>SEGA</developer>
        <publisher>Sumo Digital</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Racing</genre>
        <players>4</players>
        <story>Sonic &amp; All-Stars Racing Transformed is the sequel to Sonic &amp; SEGA All-Stars Racing. As in the
            original game, players race a lineup of SEGA characters along with a few outside guests on tracks inspired
            by SEGA games. In this sequel the vehicles can transform into three different types when driven through
            special gates: Kart form, Watercraft form, and Aircraft form, with different control styles for each. In
            addition, many of the tracks transform, changing routes and vehicle types as the race continues.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Sonic - Lost World (USA)">
        <description>Sonic - Lost World (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>SEGA</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.75</score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Dr. Eggman has harnessed the power of six menacing creatures known as the Deadly Six, but when the Deadly
            Six rise up against their master, Sonic has to unite with his arch nemesis in order to take on the new
            enemies head-to-head. Using his dynamic new parkour moves and improved Colour Powers, Sonic must run, jump
            and race through a variety of ever changing terrains in order to defeat the Deadly Six.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Sonic Boom - Rise of Lyric (USA)">
        <description>Sonic Boom - Rise of Lyric (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>SEGA</developer>
        <publisher>Big Red Button</publisher>
        <score>0.45</score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Sonic Boom: Rise of Lyric follows Sonic the Hedgehog, Miles "Tails" Prower, Amy Rose, and Knuckles the
            Echidna as they battle the evil Dr. Eggman. In what seemed like a normal day of thwarting Dr. Eggman's
            plans, the group finds themselves on an island where they discover an ancient tomb sealed deep within the
            island for over 1000 years. Sonic accidentally unleashes a powerful villain named Lyric, a member of a
            robot-snake race called the Ancestors, who wants to get enough power to feed his war robot army with the
            Chaos Crystals to destroy all that is organic and create a world of twisted metal and robots. To stop
            Lyric's evil plan, the group must set aside their differences and find the Chaos Crystals before Lyric. The
            stakes have never been higher, and the only chance to beat Lyric is to come together and work as a team.
        </story>
    </game>
    <game name="Splatoon (USA)">
        <description>Splatoon (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
        <players>4+</players>
        <story>Splatter enemies and claim your turf as the ink-spewing, squid-like characters called Inklings in
            Nintendo's third-person action shooter game. Challenge your friends in chaotic four-on-four matches, in
            which the goal is to get your ink on as many places as possible and claim your turf, all while strategically
            submerging yourself in your team's colors and blasting your enemies.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="SpongeBob SquarePants - Plankton's Robotic Revenge (USA)">
        <description>SpongeBob SquarePants - Plankton's Robotic Revenge (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Star Fox Guard (USA)">
        <description>Star Fox Guard (USA)</description>
        <year>2016</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Strategy</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Star Fox Guard est un jeu de type "Tower Defense" en 3D dans lequel les joueurs doivent protéger diverses
            bases appartenant à l'oncle de Slippy Toad, Grippy. en surveillant les caméras de sécurité. L'écran de
            télévision affiche des images de toutes les caméras de sécurité disponibles tandis que le GamePad Wii U
            offre une vue aérienne de la base. Pour défendre le noyau de la base, les joueurs doivent surveiller
            attentivement les moniteurs pour détecter tout attaquant venant en sens inverse et basculer le contrôle sur
            l'une des caméras disponibles afin de tirer avec son arme. Les ennemis sont divisés en deux classes; Les
            robots de combat, qui doivent tous être vaincus pour progresser, et les robots du Chaos, qui gênent le
            joueur en altérant les caméras, comme en obscurcissant la vue ou en montrant de fausses images. Le jeu
            propose 100 missions et un mode éditeur qui permet aux joueurs de modifier le comportement des ennemis dans
            les niveaux et de les partager en ligne.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Star Fox Zero (USA)">
        <description>Star Fox Zero (USA)</description>
        <year>2016</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.7</score>
        <genre>Adventure</genre>
        <players>1-2</players>
        <story>O Lylat System está em apuros! Junta-te a Fox, Falco, Peppy e Slippy enquanto lutas para proteger a
            galáxia em Star Fox Zero, um épico shooter em 3D apenas para Wii U. Lidera a equipa de Star Fox por planetas
            exóticos com lutas renhidas e onde tu e os teus companheiros deverão competir contra Andross, o malévolo
            império invasor.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Super Mario 3D World (USA)">
        <description>Super Mario 3D World (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.9</score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players>4+</players>
        <story>Whilst exploring the Mushroom Kingdom, Mario, Luigi, Princess Peach, and Toad come across a strange clear
            pipe, which a curious green fairy-like creature, called a Sprixie, pops out of. Suddenly, Bowser appears and
            captures the fairy before escaping through the pipe. Thus, Mario and friends enter the pipe to pursue
            Bowser, and find themselves in the strange new Sprixie Kingdom as they search for the Sprixie, along with
            some of her other companions.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Super Mario Maker (USA)">
        <description>Super Mario Maker (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.9</score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Super Mario Maker lets people's imaginations run wild. For the first time ever, friends can have fun
            playing through levels they create for one another. The Wii U GamePad controller makes it so easy for anyone
            to create levels; it may feel like simply sketching out ideas on paper. Players can enjoy a seemingly
            endless supply of inventive Mario levels from players around the world.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Super Smash Bros. for Wii U (USA)">
        <description>Super Smash Bros. for Wii U (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Sora Ltd.</publisher>
        <score>0.9</score>
        <genre>Fighting</genre>
        <players>4+</players>
        <story>Mario! Link! Samus! Pikachu! All of your favorite Nintendo characters are back, along with plenty of new
            faces, in Super Smash Bros. for Wii U, the next entry in the beloved Super Smash Bros. series.

            Up to four players can battle each other locally or online across beautifully designed stages inspired by
            classic Nintendo home console games. With a variety of control options and amiibo compatibility, the
            timeless Super Smash Bros. battles come alive.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Tank! Tank! Tank! (USA)">
        <description>Tank! Tank! Tank! (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
        <publisher>Bandai Namco</publisher>
        <score>0.5</score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players>4</players>
        <story>TANK! TANK! TANK! is an action / arcade game on Wii U that invites the player to take control of a small
            tank to face hordes of opponents in closed arenas. It is possible to increase the characteristics of his
            tank according to his performances.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Tekken Tag Tournament 2 - Wii U Edition (USA)">
        <description>Tekken Tag Tournament 2 - Wii U Edition (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Teslagrad (Europe)">
        <description>Teslagrad (Europe)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Rain Games</developer>
        <publisher>Rain Games</publisher>
        <score>0.95</score>
        <genre>Platform-Puzzle-Game</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Teslagrad is a 2D puzzle platformer with action elements, where magnetism and other electromagnetic
            powers are the key to go throughout the game, and thereby discover the secrets kept in the long abandoned
            Tesla Tower. Gain new abilities to explore a non-linear world with more than 100 beautiful hand-drawn
            environments, in a steampunk-inspired vision of old Europe.

            You play as a young boy who suddenly finds himself embroiled in a long-forgotten conspiracy, involving the
            despotic king who has ruled the nation with an iron fist for several years. Jump into an outstanding
            adventure told through voiceless storytelling, writing your own part. Armed with ancient Teslamancer
            technology and your own ingenuity and creativity, your path lies through the decrepit Tesla Tower and
            beyond.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell - Blacklist (USA)">
        <description>Tom Clancy's Splinter Cell - Blacklist (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Transformers - Rise of the Dark Spark (USA)">
        <description>Transformers - Rise of the Dark Spark (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Activision</developer>
        <publisher>Edge Of Reality</publisher>
        <score>0.45</score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Transformers: Rise of the Dark Spark is an action game on Wii U. The player plays alternately Autobots
            and Decepticons in their quest for Dark Spark, a relic as powerful as evil. This leads them as well on Earth
            as on Cybertron.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Transformers Prime - The Game (USA)">
        <description>Transformers Prime - The Game (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Activision</developer>
        <publisher>Nowpro</publisher>
        <score>0.6</score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Transformers Prime: The Game is an action game on Wii U. Inspired by the TV series of the same name, it
            offers to follow the war between Autobots and Decepticons by incarnating alternately the members of Team
            Prime that are Optimus Prime, Ratchet, Arcee, Bumblebee and Bulkhead. Two players can also compete locally
            via the multiplayer mode included.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Turbo - Super Stunt Squad (USA)">
        <description>Turbo - Super Stunt Squad (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Voice, The - I Want You (USA)">
        <description>Voice, The - I Want You (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Walking Dead, The - Survival Instinct (USA)">
        <description>Walking Dead, The - Survival Instinct (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer></developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre></genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Warriors Orochi 3 Hyper (USA)">
        <description>Warriors Orochi 3 Hyper (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Tecmo</developer>
        <publisher>Tecmo</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Beat'em Up</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story></story>
    </game>
    <game name="Watch Dogs (USA)">
        <description>Watch Dogs (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher></publisher>
        <score>0.75</score>
        <genre>Adventure</genre>
        <players>8</players>
        <story>The storyline of Watch Dogs game is built around the concept of information warfare, data being
            interconnected, and the world's increasing use of technology?questioning who exactly runs the computers they
            depend on. The game is set in an alternate reality version of Chicago, Illinois, which is one of many cities
            to feature a supercomputer known as a "CtOS" (Central Operating System). The system controls almost every
            piece of technology in the city, and contains information on all of the city's residents and activities
            which can be used for various purposes. In the game's universe, the Northeast blackout of 2003 was found to
            be caused by a hacker, prompting the development of CtOS. The game will follow a man named Aiden Pearce, a
            highly skilled hacker described as a person who uses both "fists and wits." The gameplay demo shown at E3
            2012 depicted Aiden's attempt to assassinate a media mogul named Joseph DeMarco, who had been wrongly
            acquitted on charges of murder. In a demonstration shown at E3 2013, Pearce helps a fellow hacker named
            T-Bone escape after he is discovered attempting to steal a motherboard.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Wheel of Fortune (USA)">
        <description>Wheel of Fortune (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer>THQ</developer>
        <publisher>THQ</publisher>
        <score>0.5</score>
        <genre>Puzzle</genre>
        <players>4+</players>
        <story>Spin the wheel along with Pat Sajak and Vanna White on the virtual version of America's Game!</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Wii Fit U (USA)">
        <description>Wii Fit U (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Various</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Wii Fit U is a fitness game for the balance board peripheral. Game modes include Yoga, Strength training,
            Aerobics, Dance and Balance games.

            There are 18 Balance games of which Trampoline target, Hosedown, Desert course, Core Luge, Scuba Search,
            Climbing are all new games, the rest are the same games as in Wii Fit and Wii Fit Plus</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Wii Party U (USA)">
        <description>Wii Party U (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Casual Game</genre>
        <players>1-4</players>
        <story>Wii Party U is a multiplayer video game consisting of a standard board game with mini-games, similar to
            Mario Party. Over 80 different new mini-games will be available. Multiple people can play mini-games using
            the Wii U GamePad. "House Party" games also return from Wii Party, and focus on various implementations of
            the Wii U GamePad and Wii Remotes amongst a group of people.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Wii Sports Club (USA)">
        <description>Wii Sports Club (USA)</description>
        <year>2014</year>
        <developer>Nintendo</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.45</score>
        <genre>Sports</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Play your favorite Wii Sports games on the Wii U console! With Wii Sports Club, you can now take the
            competition online with tennis, bowling and golf - baseball and boxing are coming soon. Join a club, compete
            against other clubs from around your region, or play online multiplayer with your friends. You can also use
            all-new training modes to improve your skills and support your club.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Wipeout - Create &amp; Crash (USA)">
        <description>Wipeout - Create &amp; Crash (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Behaviour Interactive</developer>
        <publisher>Activision</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>Casual Game</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Wipeout Create &amp; Crash is a party game on Wii U inspired by the TV show Wipeout. In this game,
            candidates face an obstacle course in a colourful and lively world. For the first time, it is possible to
            create your own courses thanks to the editor provided for this purpose.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Wipeout 3 (USA)">
        <description>Wipeout 3 (USA)</description>
        <year></year>
        <developer>Activision</developer>
        <publisher>Activision</publisher>
        <score>0.4</score>
        <genre>Sports</genre>
        <players>4+</players>
        <story>Wipeout 3 gets gamers back on their favorite insane obstacle course game show, complete with updated
            features, even more wacky characters, and all the epic wipeouts players can handle.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Wonderful 101, The (USA)">
        <description>Wonderful 101, The (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>PlatinumGames</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.9</score>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>Earth is under attack from an invasion of enormous aliens, and the only thing that can protect the planet
            is a group of unlikely, yet mighty, heroes with special abilities. Unfortunately, the aliens are too
            powerful for the heroes to fight individually. They must join forces and work together to defeat their
            common enemy. These uniquely different heroes can morph into powerful weapons to crush the invaders or turn
            into objects like a giant fist or bridge to interact with and traverse the environments.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Xenoblade Chronicles X (USA)">
        <description>Xenoblade Chronicles X (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Monolith Soft</developer>
        <publisher>Monolith Soft</publisher>
        <score></score>
        <genre>RPG</genre>
        <players>1</players>
        <story>The next massive sci-fi role-playing game from Monolith Soft, creators of Baten Kaitos and Xenoblade
            Chronicles, comes exclusively to Wii U. In Xenoblade Chronicles X, a terrible intergalactic war leaves just
            a handful of Earth survivors trying to live in a beautiful yet hostile environment. Players engage in
            battles against powerful creatures of all forms and sizes using the deep battle system that builds on the
            triumphs of the team's previous RPG adventures.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Yoshi's Woolly World (USA)">
        <description>Yoshi's Woolly World (USA)</description>
        <year>2015</year>
        <developer>Good Feel</developer>
        <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
        <score>0.8</score>
        <genre>Platform</genre>
        <players>4+</players>
        <story>Yoshi's Woolly World is a platform game in which the player assumes the role of Yoshi. Similar to
            developer Good-Feel's previous title Kirby's Epic Yarn, the game is set in a world where the characters and
            environment are composed of yarn and cloth. Yoshi retains much of his moveset from the Yoshi's Island series
            of games, including using his tongue to swallow enemies and using his flutter jump to reach hard areas, and
            many elements such as flowers and mystery clouds return. However, unlike other games where swallowing
            enemies would produce eggs which Yoshi could then throw, Yoshi instead produces balls of yarn.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Your Shape - Fitness Evolved 2013 (USA)">
        <description>Your Shape - Fitness Evolved 2013 (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score>0.55</score>
        <genre>Sports</genre>
        <players></players>
        <story>Your Shape: Fitness Evolved 2013 is a coaching game available on Wii U. The player can create his sport
            program by choosing a specific goal, such as lose weight, relax or have fun. The exercises, varied, are
            based on dance, fitness, kickboxing, yoga or even muscle building and cardio training.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="ZombiU (USA)">
        <description>ZombiU (USA)</description>
        <year>2012</year>
        <developer>Ubisoft</developer>
        <publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
        <score>0.85</score>
        <genre>Action</genre>
        <players>1-4</players>
        <story>Developed by Ubisoft Montpellier, the studio behind critically acclaimed titles like From Dust, Beyond
            Good &amp; Evil and, Ghost Recon Advanced Warfighter, ZombiU puts players in the middle of London circa
            2012, where an outbreak has infected the population, destroying their humanity and turning them into
            mindless monsters preying on the flesh of the few remaining survivors. This fear-fueled first-person shooter
            invites takes all the horror, chaos and tension found in the best of the horror genre and adds original
            interactive elements, including a unique death mechanic that puts players in the body of a different
            survivor each time they die, allowing them to track and take down their old, infected characters, recover
            their equipment and see if they can stay alive just a little bit longer this time.</story>
    </game>
    <game name="Zumba Fitness World Party (USA)">
        <description>Zumba Fitness World Party (USA)</description>
        <year>2013</year>
        <developer>Zoë Mode</developer>
        <publisher>505 Games</publisher>
        <score>0.45</score>
        <genre>Music and Dance</genre>
        <players>2</players>
        <story>Zumba Fitness: World Party (a.k.a Zumba Fitness 4) is the fourth and final video game in the installment
            of the Fitness series, with this game being the sequel to Zumba Fitness Core</story>
    </game>
</menu>